Chapter 1305: Pearl of the Temple 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Everyone, prepare for battle.”

Blue Void’s was magnified through the Sound Amplification Spell, so that everyone could hear it.

The Warriors all put on their armor and helmets, picking up their weapons. The Wizards started giving them temporary Enchantments, the magic light from the many spells lighting up on their armor and weapons, temporarily increasing their power by one level.

With the Contractors standing in a ring at the center, they rapidly began to build a temporary fence around the campsite. The circles of white bone fencing were the masterpiece created by the Necromancer Wizards. Since there was so much negative energy here, it was very easy to unleash a spell like the White Bone Fence, and the sharp spikes on the fence were even tipped with poison. Even if regular Undead Zombies got pricked by these, their bodies would also rot away.

Spheres of illuminating light were released and made to float above the campsite.

Soon enough, a circular campsite with a hundred-meter radius constructed, taking up a large area on the plaza.

In the darkness, the wisps of black smoke and fog wafted over from the unseen shadows around them, and they could vaguely hear low roars coming faintly from within the dark fog.

The campsite was illuminated, making it an extremely obvious target in the dark plaza.

Blue Void and a few Great Wizards under his lead flew in the air, their expressions solemn, and they constantly held scrolls in their hands.

At times like these, it was best to use up the scrolls first, conserving their own spirit power lest they used up all their power and could not escape later.

As powerful nobles and royalty, it was only natural that they had a great many scrolls at their disposal.

Several scouts treaded lightly as they darted into the darkness nearby, and soon they heard the fine sounds of blades clashing, then the scouts rushed back out, hastily and hurriedly.

“The Undead!! So many Undead!!”

A scout cried out in panic.

Ever since they entered the ruins, he had gone out scouting many times, all over the place. But he had never been this panicked.

“There’s an Advanced Undead as well!” reported the other scout loudly as well.

“Ready!” said Blue Void in a loud voice, telling the scouts to return to the squad.

The slightly over ten Warriors remaining stood at the very front of the team, followed by the team’s Wizards who were starting to prepare their spells.

“Those who can use Holy Light Rays, please do use that. Those who can’t, please use Light of Lunia.”

Holy Light Rays and Light of Lunia were both Level One spells, but both were spells that used pure positive energy, so they were extremely effective in suppressing the Undead. The difference was that Holy Light Rays had a key condition that needed to be fulfilled, otherwise the Wizard would not be able to use it. The condition was that they needed to abstain from sex for at least three months.

If you wanted to use the pure positive energy from the Heavenly Mountain, this key condition was mandatory.

That was why Blue Void told those who could not use it to use the Light of Lunia instead.

The Light of Lunia was a type of Grade One wandering energy from the God of Light and Fire’s Divine Kingdom, the Heavenly Mountain. It had a special liveliness, so it could also suppress the Undead to a certain extent.

Brr…

A Wizard unleashed a ring of pale white forces. This was an Undead Detection Spell, and instantly, every place that the forces swept past began to glow with a dense concentration of many red dots.

Hiss…

When they saw how many red dots there were, the Wizards all began to take a sharp intake of breath.

“So many!!” Kevin had also seen the effect of the Undead Detection. This was a representation of the enemy proportional to the surrounding area, and the red dots indicated there were all the Undead surrounding the campsite.

At a glance, there were no fewer than several tens of thousands!

According to the two scouts just now, there seemed to be Advanced Undead among them as well. Now that would truly be troublesome.

Kevin stood with the team of Contractors. Although he was temporarily safe, his heart would still tremble whenever he thought about those countless red dots.

“Would all the Master Contractors please be prepared to summon your companions at any moment. If the situation turns dire, please summon the dragons as quickly as possible, in order to deal with the situation.” Blue Void’s order came from the frontlines.

The dozen or so Contractors all stepped out and stood in a line, abreast, each of them preparing materials for their spells in their hands.

Kevin stood without moving. He was damned in moved, and damned if he did not.

“Let’s get going, shall we? Master Kevin?” Gergenfor gave him a hard push from behind. Although he only pushed the Energy Field Rings on Kevin’s Wizard, Kevin still felt a force that made him take several steps forward.

“Father… Are you okay?” Maria leaned on him, almost unable to hide the concern on her face. She was no fool, and as a rare genius Wizard, there was no way she would not have noticed how strange her father was acting. She merely chose not to mention it.

“What’s with the push! I know that myself!” Kevin barked at Gergenfor in a deep voice. This bastard acted like he was watching a show, and he had always been looking at Maria so greedily throughout the whole journey.

“We’re both Contractors, I’m just worried that you’ll accidentally forget to summon your companion. The situation isn’t looking very good right now, and if we don’t have your very valuable contribution, that’ll just be too bad,” said Gergenfor with a creepy smile.

Kevin saw two Contractor Wizards who stood further away whispering to each other, their taunting gazes glancing over at him occasionally as they spoke.

His heart grew calmer. Now that it had come to this, the more he panicked, the more he would reveal himself.

Right now, they were just suspicious, but they could not be certain. With so many preparations in place, perhaps this really might end before he had to summon his dragon, just like before.

Only the unknown could represent uncertainty and continue to instill a certain sense of fear in the other Contractors.

He held Maria’s hand tightly, and Ice Orchid stood next to him as well. However, compared to the other female Wizards or Warriors who were following the other Contractors, she was regretting it deeply in her heart as well. She scolded herself for choosing such a Contractor to follow, but unfortunately, it had already been decided.

On the bright side, this Contractor did not ask her to pay with her body.

She had been prepared to do it, to use her body as a commodity. That was what she did to earn her right to learn in the past, it was what she did to obtain the tuition fees for the Arcane Art Academy and her research funding. Most impoverished female Wizards had such an experience or made such a decision. It was nothing special.

But to her surprise, Kevin never showed any such intention. That was her sole solace right now.

Boom!

All of a sudden, amidst a huge tide-like impact, the expressions of all the Wizards and Warriors, including Blue Void, changed.

From the darkness directly ahead of them, there were large hordes of Skeleton Soldiers surging into the plaza. Their numbers would not have been fewer than several thousands.

“They’re coming!”

Blue Void tore open a scroll.

There was a soft tearing sound, and then a blinding ball of golden light blossomed in the air. The ball of light grew a pair of golden wings, and then it swung slightly, flying straight downward. It crashed into the area with the highest concentration of Skeletons.

Bam!!

Amidst the periodic explosions, the golden light scattered everywhere, and at least a hundred rays of golden light twisted and shot out like threads of silk. Every ray of golden light landed on a Skeleton Soldier and burned a huge hole through it.

This one attack wiped off many Skeleton Soldiers, at least a hundred at once.

The Wizards, who had been slightly shocked, received an instant psychological boost.

They all began to unleash the Holy Light Rays and Light of Lunia that they had been preparing. The Light of Lunia was like an ocean of pure silver, lighting up and shooting into the sky. It was accompanied with a few golden rays of the Light of Lunia, utilizing an energy element that was exactly the same as that golden ball of light that Blue Void just unleashed.

“A compound Level Five spell made from merging the Level Four Heavenly Kingdom Light with the Glittering Web, as expected of Master Blue Void. This scroll was surely the hard work and intricate masterpiece of a Level Seven Royal Great Wizard, wasn’t it?” Two other Great Wizards levitating in the air sighed in sincere admiration.

Boom!

As soon as they spoke, the Skeleton Soldiers were completely obliterated by the sea of silver Holy Light, but they were followed by an even larger tide of pitch-black Zombies that rushed toward the campsite, staggering and tottering.

The area around these Zombies’ bodies was filled with black smoke and the plague. If they were approached, it could lead to the spread of terrible diseases.

“Long-range wide-area attacks,” roared Blue Void loudly.

The second wave of silver light rose into the sky, and all the Wizards aside from the Contractors began to unleash the Light of Lunia once more. The wave of silver light was like a silver liquid being splashed out and falling over the Zombies’ heads mercilessly.

There was the endless hiss of corrosion as the negative energy, the aura of death, and the plague constantly fought against the silver light. The two extreme types of energy canceled each other out and emitted a huge neutralized force. This began to disrupt the speed and strength of the Wizards’ spellcasting.

A horde of black Zombies crashed to the ground, and only a few several dozens were left walking toward the campsite. By now, however, they were no longer a threat.

The battle was over without the Warriors even having to fight at close range. Everyone’s hearts grew lighter, and they began to watch the Wizards as they easily cleaned up the remaining Undead.

“Just in case, would the Contractors please give the Warriors an Anti-Undead Energy Field?” Blue Void continued to lead. He was the only peak Level Six Warrior here, and he had just unleashed an advanced-level spell scroll, so it already took a great deal out of him. Right now, he seemed rather tired.

As soon as he spoke, another wave of deathly-pale Vampires dressed in grey clothes made of sackcloth actually appeared once more from the darkness before them. These all had deathly-pale skin and sharp fangs at the corners of their mouth. They leaped up, transforming into bats the size of human heads, and flew toward the campsite.

“The third round! There really are Advanced Undead!” said the Great Wizard beside Blue Void in a deep voice. “This is bad, Advanced Undead can constantly summon more cannon fodder from the Undead World, and wear us down endlessly!”

“We need to rush over there! I saw where these Undead are coming out from, it seems to be that one, the tallest statue in the plaza!” said another Great Wizard, panicked and hurried.

“Ae you sure, sir?” said Blue Void solemnly.

“Certain! For five consecutive tries, my Probing Spells have shown that that place is the core source of these Undead!” This Great Wizard waved his hand, unleashing golden rays that landed among the Vampires beneath him. The rays instantly hit two Vampires who were stacked on top of each other, and turned them into flying ash.

But almost a hundred Vampires flew and pounced at the campsite, even more and even faster.

Some Wizards hit them with the Light of Lunia, but it only made the skin of these large transformed bats rot, causing them to scream. It was not enough to kill them, so they continued to fly toward the campsite and high speeds.

Instantly, some of the Wizards started using the Fireball Spell.

The rumble of explosions and the firelight rushed into the sky. But they were rapidly extinguished by even more negative energy and could not sustain the combustion at all.

Broom!

Just then, the giant butcher statue in the middle of the plaza actually began to move slowly.

It gripped its giant broken-up cleaver, striding toward the campsite.

“Oh god! It’s a Level Seven Advanced Undead!!” The old Wizard in the air was the first to notice what had happened, and he yelled out loudly in disbelief.

Before the crowd beneath him began to panic, Blue Void flew out, completely calm. The boots on his feet twinkled with Magical Flying Light, preventing him from falling.

“Leave it to me!”

He was as cool as a cucumber, raising the Level Six Demon Core in his hand high into the air.

“Andihilna!! Come! I need your assistance!!!” he yelled loudly, using the Ancient Draconic language. There were even a few words from the language of the Abyss mixed within.

Chapter 1306: Pearl of the Temple 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bam!!

The Demon Core in his hand exploded instantly, turning into a storm of powder that scattered in the air.

In the Void directly underneath Blue Void, several transparent rings of forces appeared, and from the middle of the forces, a large Dual-Headed Black Dragon, the size of an elephant, flew out.

One of the Dual-Headed Black Dragon’s two mouths glowed with black-red firelight, and while the other had a blue-black chill emanating from the corners of its mouth.

Roar!!!

The gigantic Dual-Headed Black Dragon pounced straight at the statue of the butcher beneath it.

“Haha! An Advanced Undead, you sure know how to get me opponents, Blue Void!!” it responded loudly, pouncing fearlessly.

Bam!!! There was an enormous tremor produced from the clash between the two giants.

Black-red flames shot out of the Black Dragon’s mouth, burning the Butcher’s body mercilessly, but they did not leave a single trace. Similarly, the blue-black chill from the other side was completely ineffective as well.

“Damnit! It’s the type I hate the most, a Reinforced Undead that’s immune to both ice and fire! I demand more compensation this time, Blue Void!!”

“No problem!” Blue Void replied loudly, standing on the Dual-Headed Black Dragon’s back.

“I like a generous employer, haha!!” The Dual-Headed Black Dragon instantly laughed, satisfied.

The Butcher waved his cleaver, slashing down hard at the Black Dragon’s scales and leaving a tiny mark. The Black Dragon immediately lost it. Since both of the elements he was good at would not work, he decided to simply go head-to-head against the Butcher, fighting power with brute power, without using any fancy tricks whatsoever.

While these two giants were having a fierce go at each other on one hand, on the other side, the many Corpses and Vampires had also pounced out of hiding. The Corpses were an evolution of the Zombies, and they had the ghosts’ ability to dematerialize as well as travel through shadows. When they materialized, they also had the powerful defensive ability of Advanced Zombies.

There was a potent poison on their claws, one that was extremely destructive. With it, a serious injury would lead straight to death, and most Corpses were also partly immune to material attacks. Only weapons equipped with spells and effects that contained positive energy could deal them great damage.

The Warriors rushed at them, roaring loudly, and fought against the Vampires and Corpses that had flown into the campsite. The brutal beasts summoned by the Wizards also pounced on them, fighting against the horde of the Undead.

Skeleton Wizards and Zombie Wizards began to appear in the Undead Army opposite them. They unleashed negative energy spells and began to neutralize the human Wizards’ positive energy spells. The only silver lining was that the White Bone Fence could temporarily halt the advance of the Skeletons and Zombies. They tried their best to break the White Bone Fence, but could not fly in for now. Hence, the Warriors only needed to battle against a few Vampires and Corpses.

“Things’re looking bad! All Contractors, get ready!” The old Wizard in mid-air temporarily assumed command.

The Contractors at the core noticed something amiss as well. The Wizards at the outer ring had already given themselves many layers of defense, such as Wizard Armor, Shield Spells, Elemental Resistance Increase, Poison Barrier, Stoneskin Spells, and Lignified Skin. They just put spell after defensive spell, both high-level and low-level, over their bodies.

Boom!

A Contractor could not resist it and summoned his dragon first. The Green Dragon was the size of a horse, and it flew up, lowering its head and spraying out a mouthful of corrosive Dragon’s Breath. It half-melted away the heads of two Vampires, and then it reached out wildly with its Dragon Claws. Grabbing two Corpses, it threw its head back and tossed them straight into its mouth, swallowing them whole.

Green Dragons were known for liking poison and negative energy, but to think his Green Dragon would even devour corpses, now that was a dragon with a rare, extreme taste…

The appearance of the Colossal Dragon directly prevented the situation from falling apart.

The Wizards divided themselves into small teams and split up, destroying the Corpses and Vampires that were surging in. Thankfully, they had the protection of all those defensive spells, so only a very few Wizards sustained injuries. The rest retreated from the attacks of the Undead, completely unharmed.

But just then, more Undead appeared in the distance once more. Those were Advanced Undead, armed with all sorts of equipment and weapons. The Advanced Zombies, who clearly had a certain level of intelligence, all rushed toward the campsite, and they actually displayed well-rehearsed martial arts and combat techniques. These were that close to becoming Dark Knights!!

“Advanced Undead!! This is bad!”

A female Contractor Wizard gasped in terror.

The Demon Core in her hand disappeared instantly, and a Red Dragon appeared by her side soundlessly.

Like her, most of the Contractors began to silently summon their dragon companions.

More than ten Colossal Dragons all appeared within the camp, and their enormous Draconic Aura wove together. Rather than resisting each other, they gathered together and shot toward the outside as one.

The Draconic Aura directly suppressed all the Undead nearby, forcing them to slow down by two beats, their power dropping by at least one level. As for the weaker ones, the Soul Flames in their eyes actually began to jump intensely, and they began to sway even as they walked.

“Let’s destroy these filthy things!” The largest Black Dragon pounced out and caught an Advanced Zombie wildly with his claws, tearing it directly with his hands.

And then there were the remaining Green Dragons, Blue Dragons, White Dragons, and Red Dragons. There was even a rare Purple Dragon.

All of the summoned dragons joined the battle.

“Why aren’t you fighting? As a Contractor, you’re one of our most precious fighting forces. You should know that if you and your dragon companion fight for us, you might be able to save a few Warriors’ lives!!” Gergenfor’s voice instantly attracted the gazes of all the Contractors.

When they saw that there was still a Contractor who had not summoned his Colossal Dragon, the Contractors were all slightly unhappy with him.

“Are you still trying to conserve your energy at a crucial moment like this? There really are all sorts of selfish types!” said a Wizard icily.

“Conserving energy?” Gergenfor laughed coldly. “Kevin, didn’t you say that your companion was too strong, and that’s why you’re reluctant to summon it?”

Kevin acted calm, gripping his daughter’s hand.

“I did say that. I’m poor, so I can only summon my companion once. I’m not as rich as you are, that’s why I have to leave it until the most important moment.”

“Poor? Haha. This isn’t the time to be stingy with your expenses, every bit of fighting power will save lives. Here, I’ll give you this Level Six Demon Core, is that enough to summon your ‘powerful companion’?” Just then, one of the Wizards in mid-air descended from the sky and tossed Kevin a Demon Core impatiently. He truly believed that Kevin did not summon his companion because he lacked summoning materials. He would never have thought that there was another secret behind the scenes.

Kevin accepted it hurriedly.

“This is the summoning resource Master Blue Void gave me. My companion has already gone on ahead, so I’ll give you this Demon Core, hurry up and summon yours. For all we know, one more pair of fighting hands may be able to turn the tides,” said the old Wizard sincerely.

Kevin’s face turned slightly pale as he gripped the Demon Core. This was the first Level Six Demon Core he had ever seen, an Advanced Demon Core. The treasure he had always dreamed of was now in his hands, but he felt as though the Demon Core was scalding his skin, so much so that he could barely hold it.

“What are you waiting for?!” the old Wizard said, hurrying him. On the other side, the Advanced Undead were already approaching. If they arrived and the situation fell apart completely, then it would truly be over.

“I…” Kevin clenched his teeth. All the Contractors had summoned their companions.

Looking at the taunting gazes around him, Kevin finally decided to activate the Summoning Matrix. He tossed out his summoning materials, the powdered Demon Core’s tiny particles floating in the air.

Some transparent distorted waves appeared in mid-air.

Under these circumstances, where all the Contractors were required to fight, he no longer had any excuse to conserve his true power. Along the way here, others had sacrificed far too much to protect them, so if he still did not contribute at a time like this, the first ones to be dealt with and removed would be them. As all the Wizards around him watched glaringly, no matter how reluctant Kevin was, he had no choice but to summon his companion together with the other Contractors. He gripped that Level Six Demon Core tightly in his hand. The sharp edges nearly sliced his palm open.

Whoosh!

A petite White Dragon Whelp appeared before him, in stark contrast with the large, stout, horse-sized Young Blue and Red Dragons summoned by the other Contracts around them.

Among all the dragons, this little White Dragon was the smallest in size and had the weakest aura. It was even looking around curiously, as though it still was not very sure what was happening.

“A White Dragon? Haha, it’s a little White Dragon? How fascinating, so this is that oh-too-powerful Contract Dragon? Doth my eyes deceive me?” Gergenfor immediately started roaring with creepy laughter.

“And this is what you call a powerful dragon that can only be summoned with a Level Six Demon Core? Haha, that’s the biggest joke I’ve ever heard in my life.” Extreme displeasure twinkled in the eyes of one of the old Wizards.

“The Warriors and scouts who sacrificed themselves along the way have practically died for nothing. They died to protect a false Wizard who only knows how to lie, to protect a regular White Dragon that’s merely Level Four, and a trash Level Four Wizard. Both are only Level Four, and yet they enjoyed such high-class treatment for so long. What a combination.”

“Liar! You’re a disgrace to the noble character of the Wizards!”

“Chase him out, get him out of here! Make him fight at the frontlines with those Warriors!”

Several different voices rang out around them. Most of the Wizards just watched coldly, but their icy gazes showed just how ticked off they were.

As for the old Wizard who gave him the Demon Core, the disappointment that flashed through his eyes was even more indescribable. Shaking his head, he glanced at Kevin, then he turned around and walked away.

Kevin looked at the dazed little White Dragon and closed his eyes in despair.

He knew that everything was over. The furious Wizards would never let a liar and pretender like him go without punishment, and Blue Void would never pass up on a way to vent the frustration he had pent up along the way. This was a crucial moment right now, too. Once the battle ended, he and his daughter Maria would surely be dealt the harshest punishment!

Above them, the battle between the Dual-Headed Hell Black Dragon and the Undead Butcher was heating up. Blue Void stood on the Dual-Headed Hell Black Dragon’s back, loudly reciting a long and mysterious chant. In his hand, he actually held a shortsword that twinkled with golden light. But it was not golden light, because a close look would reveal that they were actually countless golden glyphs, flowing across the blade. And the chant seemed to be the musical notes activating the shortsword.

Roar!!

The many dragons roared and flapped their wings, taking to the air and pouncing toward the Undead Army behind the Undead Butcher. They began to tear each other apart brutally, the light of the spells from the Zombie, Skeleton, and human Wizards sparkling across the battlefield, lighting up here and extinguishing there.

Fireballs, Acid, the platinum silver light of positive energy– all of them constantly blinked and twinkled. Some of them were immediately extinguished as soon as they appeared, neutralized by the dark fog of negative energy. Many Arcane Art Projectiles leaped into the air in dense waves, there were no fewer than a hundred Projectiles in the storm of them, and they all pounced downward at the same time. Evidently, someone had activated an Advanced Scroll.

Chapter 1307: Treasure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With this many Undead here, this place was clearly the center of the Underground City. In other words, it was extremely likely that the Pearl of the Hall was just ahead. The more one contributed at a crucial moment like this, the larger their share of the profits would be.

All of the Wizards did their best to coordinate with their Contract companions, killing many of the Undead, but there were just too many Undead. They surged out of the darkness endlessly.

More than ten of the Contractors’ dragons had leaped into the air and joined the battle. Only Kevin’s little White Dragon was just staring wide-eyed at the two giant monsters fighting in the air above its head, the Dual-Headed Hell Black Dragon and the Undead Butcher.

“Has it been scared out of its mind?” Gergenfor’s mean-spirited voice reached their ears.

Maria’s expression twisted, and she gripped her father’s hand tightly, glaring angrily at Gergenfor. Although she was extremely disappointed as well, she knew that her father was doing this to protect her.

Kevin tried his best to keep his expression calm, but his ice-cold palm could not deceive the daughter who knew him best.

“Pearl of the Hall!!” someone roared suddenly.

“Grab it!!”

The Wizards and Contractors all looked up at a dark red pearl that had leaped into the air. There seemed to be the vague image of a giant palace in the pearl. More than ten Colossal Dragons all pounced at the pearl. They did not need the Wizards’ encouragement and pounced at it greedily without being told to. That was an Advanced Treasure that even Level Eight powerhouses could use! This opportunity may not even come once in a hundred years. There was no way they could let it pass.

“Campas! Meradona, if you guys get that thing for me, I’ll give you a piece of a Level Seven Holy Spirit!” roared one of the Red Dragons.

“All the treasures belong to me, Black Giantfang!!” The only Black Dragon roared violently. “For all those who help me, I’ll give them each a drop of Black Dragon Heartblood!!”

The Red Dragon, Betty, and the Black Dragon, Black Giantfang– both of them were the strongest among the Contractors’ Dragons. In an instant, with the two of them as the boundary, the dragons divided themselves into two opposing camps. Desperately, they rushed at the pearl.

When Garen witnessed this scene, he decided to just act stupid. Kevin was actually telling him to fight over a mere Pearl of the Hall, and he still remembered how the last time he had been sent crashing back, all beaten up and dusty. This time, he decided that he was not going to do Kevin any favors anymore. That was why he simply used the Shrinking Bone Technique to return to the size of a Dragon Whelp, and continued to play dumb.

Seeing Kevin’s and Maria’s expression of sorrowful despair, he felt his mood lighten considerably.

Garen glanced at the Pearl of the Hall floating in mid-air and recognized it nonchalantly.

“It’s just a Level Red Pearl of the Hall, only these Level Five and Six minnows would be willing to fight so hard over it. If I wasn’t bound by the terms of the summon…” Before he even finished those thoughts, Garen’s eyes widened suddenly.

That Pearl of the Hall actually began to change its color slowly, starting from dark red and gradually becoming darker and darker, deeper and deeper in color. The hall within it gradually disappeared as well.

“This… Thi-this…! This isn’t a Hall… It’s a Pearl of the Temple!!!” Garen stared, wide-eyed and slack-jawed, as the pearl turned black. Only a Pearl of the Temple, created by a demigod, would change like that.

A wave of ecstasy instantly washed over him. Garen had never thought that he would encounter such a huge opportunity the very first time he responded to a Summon.

How could the value of a Pearl of the Temple be compared to a Pearl of the Hall? Even a thousand or ten thousand of the latter would not match up to the terror of a Pearl of the Temple!!

It was not only him, Blue Void and some of the knowledgeable old Wizards in mid-air had all recognized the Pearl of the Temple for what it was. Their expressions all expressed their wild joy.

“It’s mine! I must get it!” Blue Void’s expression changed, and the golden shortsword in his hand instantly shone with a dark golden light. He shot into the air, flying straight toward the pearl.

All of the Colossal Dragons pounced at it as well, and some old Wizards even brought out the scrolls that they had been saving for last, tearing them open harshly.

There was a huge gathering of thunderclouds and storms, the element of fire spun madly, and the Weave here fell apart in an instant. It finally gave way in the face of such concentrated and large-scale elemental forces.

“This is the too-powerful dragon you were talking about? Haha, Kevin, if your daughter comes to my tent tonight and begs me to help you, I might still consider putting in a good word for you with Master Blue Void…” Gergenfor was standing beside Kevin conceitedly, threatening him.

Barroom!!

There was a buzz, and the ground shook violently.

A piercing dragon’s roar that made their eardrums tremble rose into the air from right under their noses, and clear circular sound ripples were brutally created on the surface of the ground.

Before he could even finish speaking, he saw Garen, who was a little White Dragon just a moment ago, suddenly dart forward. His body expanded, growing rapidly from its initial form as a Dragon Whelp, and instantly turning into an Adult Dragon the size of an elephant. And it did not stop there. His body actually continued to grow, and soon become a giant that was twice the size of a regular Colossal Dragon.

A pair of terrifying white wings covered the sky above the three of them.

“The Pearl of the Temple is mine! It’s all mine!!!” Garen’s wild and violent dragon’s roar brought with it was both immensely intimidating and greedy. His Level Seven Draconic Aura burst forth, but even more terrifying was his speed despite his giant size, so fast that it was completely unimaginable for a regular Adult Dragon. The ground split apart, and the momentum sent Garen shooting up at the Pearl of the Temple in the air.

Along the way, he forcefully pushed past four or five Colossal Dragons that blocked his path.

Bam bam bam!!

Amidst the series of dull thuds as a result of the collisions, there was also the intense sound of bones breaking.

All of the Wizards and Colossal Dragons stared blankly as Garen’s enormous body rushed up to the Pearl of the Temple, quick as lightning. His claw reached for the Pearl.

Compared to him, all the other dragons around him were practically like children. They were sent flying far away by just a light touch, as though they were toys.

All the humans and dragons who had witnessed Garen’s transformation were completely speechless. This change was just far too shocking.

Garen did not only send regular dragons flying, he also knocked away Black Giantfang, the Black Dragon who was the strongest physically. Even he had his bones instantly broken, falling from the sky and crushing a wave of Skeleton Undead.

The Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon and the Undead Butcher were trying to catch up to Garen at first, but they hurriedly stopped when they saw that scene.

Blue Void’s eyelid twitched madly as he watched Garen reach his claw toward the Pearl of the Temple. The enormous wind pressure had actually sent him flying, making him somersault in mid-air a few times. There was no need to describe just how furious he was.

“Level Nine!! This guy is definitely a Level Nine Colossal Dragon!!” he roared in agony. At a time like this, once anyone got the Pearl of the Temple, there was no way to force it out of them!

Swoosh!

The Pearl of the Temple was in his hands, and with one movement of Garen’s enormous body, he had instantly kept it into his Space Earring.

“How lucky, hahaha!!” he laughed wildly. “I’m taking this Pearl now, no one got any objections, right?” He looked around him, only the Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon, Black Giantfang, and the Red Dragon were the strongest ones here. They were all Level Six, but faced with his intimidating aura, all three chose to lower their heads and hold their tongues.

“O Great White Dragon, in order to obtain this treasure, I spent a great deal of manpower and material resources, as well as my precious treasures, sacrificing valiant Warrio…” Before Blue Void could complete his sentence, Garen shut him up with a glare.

“You should be honored that I’m taking your things!” Garen’s deep voice and unreasonable words echoed. “Are you saying I’m taking too much advantage of you?”

“No… No no no, that is not my intention at all…” Blue Void was terrified. The glare from the enormous Colossal Dragon was making his heart shudder like mad.

If the dragon were to fly off the handle here and kill them all, destroying their bodies and all the evidence, no one would even know that there had been a Pearl of the Temple here. They would definitely be in trouble then.

“As long as you get it!” Garen nodded, satisfied. He finally glanced at the last Undead Butcher and saw that thing actually had a certain degree of intelligence. It was currently creeping back into the darkness behind it carefully.

Are you kidding me? That was a Level Nine Colossal Dragon, even if it was one of the weaker White Dragons, it was still a Level Nine!

Wherever you went, a Level Nine would be a higher-up equivalent to an Elder, even in Snow City and the Grey Shadow Parliament, they would still be honored at the very top. It was this powerful, and a Dragon to boot! The only thing they could achieve by staying behind was suicide, nothing else.

“Trying to run, are we?!” Garen grinned.

Although this Undead Butcher did not have any special abilities, its Ice and Fire Reinforcement, as well as its powerful regeneration abilities, were already great assets, and it might work well as a subordinate. It just so happened that Garen also specialized in Necromancy spells. Even though no one knew it, he was already a Level Five Wizard.

With one flap of his wings, Garen pounced directly at the Undead Butcher.

This creature at the peak of Level Six, who had just fought against the Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon, was instantly spooked into turning tail and running away. But Garen pounced on it from behind like an eagle pouncing at a chick, and pressed it directly to the ground, standing on its back so that it could not move.

The so-called Ice and Fire Reinforcement was nothing more than a joke in the face of Garen’s pure strength and speed. It was true, he could not really do anything against advanced space spells, but he could deal with creatures like these, who were vulnerable to brute force, quite easily.

“Let me go…!! I’ll give you a huge treasure!!” roared the Undead Butcher loudly, struggling desperately. But the two dragon claws had it pinned tightly against the ground, and it could not move at all.

“Treasure?” Garen needed cash right now, so he was instantly tempted by that word.

“Hand over your Soul Core. I can choose to believe you.”

“No, you can’t do that…!” yelled the Undead Butcher loudly. “I can give you the treasure in exchange for my freedom.”

“No way! I don’t like having someone haggle with me.” Garen rejected it point-blank.

The Undead Butcher still tried to struggle, but Garen immediately crashed one claw into it lightly.

There was an enormous rumble, and the Young Dragons nearby who had rushed over immediately felt their eyelids twitch at the sight.

A deep and huge crater had formed on the impenetrable skin on the Undead Butcher’s back, like metal sinking down in the center. Add that to the unbelievably loud cracking sound, and they all knew its bones had been broken…

It was fine for the Undead Butcher to take that hit, but if that blow had landed on the body of any dragon, including Black Giantfang who had just crawled back onto his feet, they could not guarantee that they would be able to survive the one swipe of that claw.

“White Dragon… Do you know who I am? Lowly White Dragon!!” Suddenly, a rough voice reached their ears.

The Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon flapped his wings, flying over to them.

“You, a mere White Dragon, dare rob me of the item I have set my sights on? Looks like the White Dragon Mountain has been peaceful for too long, so long that you have forgotten under whose wing you are protected!!” roared the Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon in considerable frustration and anger as he flew over to them.

Garen was discussing conditions with the Undead Butcher and had yet to come to a decision when they heard the whining from behind him.

“A Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon?” He remembered now, the White Mountain Dragon was unlike the other dragons’, its base was in Hell, or the place the Wizards called Purgatory. It was all thanks to the Black Dragons that they could find their standing in Purgatory and obtain a large enough space to live.

Chapter 1308: Treasure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“White Dragon Mountain? What does that have to do with me?” Garen grinned. “Sadly, I don’t have any relation with White Dragon Mountain… so I won’t be troubled in any way. You, on the other hand, may be in big trouble very soon…” His gaze turned cold, staring straight at the Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon that was flying toward him.

His gaze made the latter shudder and stop in his tracks, afraid to continue further.

“Dare you kill me? My father is the leader of the Hell Dragons! If he finds out about this, he definitely won’t let you go!!” The other guy was feeling slightly nervous now.

“Let’s gang up on him! He’s just a Level Nine, if we all jump on him, we could even crush him to death!!” Not far away, Black Giantfang yelled out encouragements.

Right now, the Undead Butcher was being suppressed, and the large Undead Army was retreating slowly as well. It showed that the control of this army had a very direct correlation to the Undead Butcher.

Without the pressure from the Undead, everyone’s confidence and spirits had returned now.

Garen continued to apply pressure on the Undead Butcher, smiling coldly as he stared at the Young Dragons and Wizards who were slowly surrounding him. In the distance, a Purple Dragon was already preparing to unleash a powerful spell, at least Level Seven according to the forces. Evidently, it was using every ounce of power it had.

These little runts actually dare to defy him?

This was making Garen slightly impatient. Right.now, he was already completely immune to Level Nine direct damage spells, and the effects of any status ailments were also drastically weakened, such that they were practically useless. His own actual combat power was already equal to the strongest physical Warrior in the history of the White Dragon Clan.

Only Space-Time Spells that were Level Eight or above could prove some disruption to him. Other than that, the only way left was to fight him with brute physical strength.

IAs for fighting with brute strength… With his eighty-point peak-level stats, forget these Young Dragons who were merely at Levels Five or Six, even their Adult Dragon elders could only act as cannon fodder in front of Garen.

“Looks like I’ll have to kill everyone who knows about this, huh…” Garen’s malicious gaze made most of the dragons shudder in fear. Their instincts told them that if they continued to offend him, they and the other dragons would probably die before they even reached their summon time limit.

In the distance, Blue Void stood on the Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon’s back. The dark golden shortsword in his hand was still emitting a faint golden light, but he had clearly lost his confidence. This sword was a pinnacle Level Nine Enchanted Weapon, but unless it was wielded by a Level Nine fighter, to try and fight a Level Nine Colossal Dragon with it… would be equivalent to the difficulty faced by those mortals challenging the gods in the legends of old.

“Milord, perhaps we can borrow this Colossal Dragon’s power to investigate the entire Underground City thoroughly,” said an old Wizard softly, his voice transmitted into Blue Void’s ears. “We probably can’t get the Pearl of the Temple back, but if we want to cut our losses as much as possible and reduce the risks, we can just ask him to help us explore the Underground City. It’s the Underground City where we found the Pearl of the Temple, after all, so I believe that he would be more than willing to help us. After all, he’s also one of the dragon companions summoned by our Contractors.”

“We can threaten him with his Contractor companion,” said Blue Void softly, his voice cold. He was still sore about it, that was a Pearl of the Temple! If he could get his hands on it, he could definitely rise to Level Eight immediately, and his soul might also benefit greatly from it. It would be extremely helpful in his quest for Level Nine in the future. To just watch it fall into the hands of this White Dragon that randomly showed up from nowhere…

“Please, don’t!” the old Wizard advised him hurriedly. “If the Contractor does, this Colossal Dragon can just use the power of the Contract to return to where he came from, leaving this place. He can’t harm his Contractor himself, but if we were to get provoked and kill his Contractor, he’ll be free of all inhibitions, and will become even harder to deal with! To us, his Contactor is a positive asset!”

Blue Void lowered his head reluctantly. The truth was he understood all that in theory, but no matter what, he could not calm his heart down. His biggest target for this trip into the Underground City was that Pearl of the Temple, but to think this would be the final result!

On his side, after Garen used his Intimidation Aura to pressure all the dragons into staying quiet, he accepted the Soul Core that the Undead Butcher finally handed up. He left his Soul Energy Aura on it and instantly felt much better. He had made the right decision in coming here, because not only did he get a Pearl of the Temple, he even obtained a decent Undead lackey.

Glancing at the dragons and humans who had gathered together at the plaza nearby, Garen mused for a moment and then turned his gaze to Kevin and his daughter. After all, he was the dragon companion that Kevin summoned here, so as long as Kevin was here, at times like these he had no choice but to fulfill his Contractor’s requests and conditions.

“Can you make yourself smaller?” he asked, releasing the Undead Butcher.

“No… I’m naturally this size,” replied the Undead Butcher honestly. He was, by nature, bloodthirsty, fond of rotting meat, and honest.

Crawling up from the ground, he felt that the bones broken by the attack from Garen’s claw earlier had not heard yet, so his whole body felt lopsided, and it was not a very good feeling at all. Grumbling, he began to capture the Undead that had been killed, lying on the floor, and tossed them into his mouth, chewing them roughly. As he devoured more Undead materials, his injuries began to heal quickly as well.

“Then you just stay away and get me more valuable things, treasures or gems and the like. I want them, the more the better,” Garen instructed him. Now that he had a local leader under his command, it was only natural that he would try to make as much of it as he could.

“Oh… What counts as valuable? Edible things?” asked the Undead Butcher in a quiet voice.

“Didn’t you mention a huge treasure just now?” Garen was speechless.

“Yeah, there are all sorts of precious and delicious ingredients and food in there. They’re all very high in level, and I want to eat them all the time, but I’m too scared to get too close…” replied the Butcher honestly.

“Even you’re too scared to get too close?” Garen was slightly shocked. “What’s guarding it? Tell me with your soul.”

The Butcher hurriedly shut his mouth and used his soul to communicate instead. The Wizards and other dragons nearby sighed at the waste, since this was clearly the key information. To think that there was still information about a possible lode of wealth, it definitely was worth coming to this Underground City.

Garen and the Undead Butcher quickly exchanged some information.

Luckily, the two of them were communicating with their souls, so it was very fast. Instantly, a large amount of information regarding that treasure appeared in Garen’s brain.

“An Underground Thane? A Level Eight creature?” Garen found that slightly difficult to handle.

An Underground Thane is the title of a giant beetle-type creature. Legend had it that it migrated here from the Earth Element Plane, and it naturally had the ability to drill through the earth quickly, as well as to control the element of earth. Although its destructive power was only Level Eight, its ability to escape was much stronger than many Level Nine powerhouses, so it was known as the strongest survivalist.

If it could not win a battle, it would just drill into the ground. Be it granite or marble, nothing posed an obstacle to it. As long as it was something like stone or metal, the Underground Thane could instantly escape through it.

But at the same time, this creature was also the best and most precious scout when it came to searching for all sorts of mineral ores.

A treasure that would keep an Underground Thane there without leaving would surely be worth quite a bit.

Garen’s thoughts whirred in his head, and he instructed the Undead Butcher to leave this place, so the latter retreated into the darkness and vanished. As for Garen himself, he flew back to the rest of the crowd and blew away the Warriors standing in his path with one flap of his wings. Finally, he walked up to Kevin.

Gradually, his enormous body began to shrink rapidly. From its initial size, twice that of an elephant, his body quickly shrank until it was the size and length of a regular Young White Dragon. He did not return to his Dragon Whelp from, as this regular body size was his most stable and energy-efficient state.

As he walked up to Kevin, he saw that Kevin was keeping his expression calm, but there was an irrepressible glee in his eyes.

“Contractor, the compensation you gave isn’t even enough for me to clean my teeth with,” said Garen, annoyed. “The last time, you canceled the summon halfway and nearly caused me serious injury. If this ever happens again, I’ll eat you!”

Only then did Kevin understand why the White Dragon refused to fight in the beginning. If it were not for the appearance of the treasure, the Pearl of the Temple, this guy would probably still be acting dumb. All Kevin could do was smile wryly.

“That’s my fault… Please accept my sincerest apologies, O Powerful Garen. But haven’t you already obtained the biggest prize this time?”

“That’s why I have generously decided to forgive you this time,” said Garen with a cold harrumph. “But next time you’ll need at least a Level Six Demon Core to summon me!”

He had seen that Level Six Demon Core in Kevin’s hands.

He had reaped some great rewards this time, and that put him in a very good mood. With one Pearl of the Temple in hand, he would have earned a killing even if he did not continue on. By initial estimates, the Pearl of the Temple could give him at least a hundred potential points. If he absorbed it slowly, he could even obtain a new Soul Ring just for once! This was the product of a Demigod powerhouse condensing all their divinity at their deathbed, so naturally, it was not that simple an item. It would be even better if Garen could understand that wisp of divinity hidden within, it might rapidly speed up his path to the Demigod level.

“Alright, I need to rest. If I’m free, you can summon me.” Garen tossed Kevin those parting words and flew straight into the darkness.

In his wake, Blue Void and the others just exchanged glances wordlessly.

The Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon roared once in deep dissatisfaction.

“I wanna go back and tell Father!! That damned White Dragon!” he yelled out angrily through their contract’s spiritual connection.

Blue Void was extremely unwilling to give up too.

“Since that guy has the guts to do something like this, that must prove that he’s not afraid of the consequences! I bet your actions won’t have much of an effect.”

“Right now, I get frustrated just looking at a White Dragon!” The Double-Headed Hell Black Dragon’s gaze swept past the other dragons, and the few White Dragons among them trembled under his glare.

“Perhaps we can find out some information about that White Dragon from before through these White Dragons. I heard that Contractor mention his name just now, it’s Garen.” Blue Void’s eyes twinkled.

“Garen? I’ll go ask.”

This idea had occurred to the Hell Black Dragon and the other Dragons, so Black Giantfang and the Red Dragon Betty both dragged their bodies along the ground until they had surrounded the few White Dragons among their midst.

All of them stared at the White Dragons maliciously.

“Garen… I know him, we all do.” One of the White Dragons smiled bitterly. “He’s the strongest prodigy in our clan, and he’s already this strong even though he’s not even five years old yet. It’s practically unbelievable.”

“The strongest prodigy? Are you saying that he’s a Dragon Whelp who’s not even five years old?!!” Black Giantfang exclaimed in disbelief.

“That’s right…” said the stockiest of those White Dragons helplessly.

When they saw that scene, all of the dragons and humans took a sharp intake of breath.

What did that mean!? If he was already this strong and had already reached Level Nine at five years old, then wouldn’t he be a definite shoo-in for a Demigod powerhouse in the future??

“Could he be Tiamat’s God-Favored?!” said the old Great Wizard in disbelief.

“No… As far as I know, Garen is not God-Favored, he has never been baptized by the Dragon God,” explained a White Dragon.

“He will be soon,” sighed the old Wizard.

Instantly, everyone understood what he meant.

Just how impressive was the talent Garen just revealed? The moment someone from the race of their followers displayed such peak-level genius, no god would be stupid enough to let this go. They would all make sure to tighten their grip on such a powerhouse.

This was the best candidate for them to groom as a Subordinate God!! For all they knew, this would signal the rise of another Lower God in the future!

Some of the more open-minded Wizards could not help but think of that.

“We can’t offend him…” Blue Void’s voice was extremely dry… A future Demigod, and a definite God-Favored… If anything happened to such a being, Tiamat’s God-Favoreds would instantly and desperately rain hell on Dragon Mountain!

Chapter 1309: Gain 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the underground city, the battle in the square ended as the team had temporarily halted to treat wounded members while the wizards resumed their meditation.

But there was an odd, peculiar ambiance clouding the team.

All of this originated from the tent where Kevin and his daughter resided. Blue Void and a few Great Wizards would throw their glances to Kevin’s tent from time to time

The largest piece of treasure was grabbed by that evil, white dragon. The remaining people did not obtain even the least bit of share hence one could understand their sore disappointment, but they dared not breathe a word given Garen’s overly brutal abilities.

Inside the tent.

Garen sat in the middle with his legs crossed. Kevin and his daughter, Maria, sat on the side preparing his meal.

“So, you’re saying that after being here for a few years, apart from some undead materials, you only encountered the Pearl of the Temple as some sort of treasure?” Garen asked, feeling a loss of words.

“Indeed,” Kevin smiled bitterly.

“This underground city is simply too huge,” Maria muttered begrudgingly.

“It’s true that it’s huge…” Garen could also sense the underground city’s complexity that it even possessed a Pearl of the Temple of Demigods. Still waters do run deep…

He was actually considering to stop meddling now.

However, he thought of the wizard tower that was still not within reach due to limited finances. The Wizard Tower was needed to break through to level five Arcane Technique for isolated research, as well as using its powers to execute research on the dimensional leap. That would require a large number of expenses, perhaps the underground city before him was an opportunity.

“I want you to accompany me to a place,” Garen said suddenly.

The moment he spoke, Kevin and his daughter instantly knew which place he was referring to. They had overheard a little of the conversation between Garen and that Undead Butcher.

“Are we, a little weak?” Kevin was helpless.

“Yes, you’re too weak but with protection from this team, it wouldn’t pose much of a problem,” Garen dully replied. “I believe the team would be glad to venture into a place with great treasure.”

He needed to get to the bottom of the situation regarding the treasure, otherwise, he might be sent back once the summon time limit is up. It was unknown whether the team would summon him back again.

“That should not be a problem,” Kevin believed that nobody would reject at the mention of treasure.

As the decision has been made, Kevin on behalf of Garen stepped out to discuss the plan with Blue Void and the rest. Blue Void shared the same views and reached a mutual agreement with Kevin without wasting any words.

After resting for a while more, the team headed towards the direction pointed by Garen with the Undead Butcher in the lead. The Undead Butcher actually has a good ability in controlling a few advanced vampires. The advanced vampires, in turn, controlled a large number of mid to low-level undead creatures. These were the same creatures that attacked the campsite earlier but were now the team’s main forces to sweep off enemies.

With a large group of undead high on alert, any small-scale battle was settled without needing help from the campsite team. Any wounded and death could be replenished through summoning and this resulted in the campsite advancing at more than doubled the speed.

Without much hindrance, they hustled to the destination mentioned by the Undead Butcher.

It was the second day’s mid-noon, and not a ray of light shone in the underground city. The wizards themselves only had a pocket watch to tell the time.

Blue Void and the rest finally arrived before a large, black water lake. Reaching the lakeside, the Undead Butcher ceased his footsteps, hesitating to move forward.

“Master, it’s just up front,” he transmitted his voice to Garen through soul telepathy.

The dirt around the black lake was black and soft. There were a number of various sizes pit holes around similar to an ant’s nest as if some bugs dug the dirt out.

Garen flew out of the campsite and landed beside the Undead Butcher. He looked towards the lake.

“What a heavy scent of death…” His heart sank, and he could indistinctly feel the energy turbulence from deep within the lake.

His dragon eye looked far towards the distance, and at the furthest depth of the lake, a white light soared into the sky. That light source traveled in light years that even Garen could feel his skin scorching just standing by the lake.

“What a powerful energy!” He was solemn. This energy turbulence was definitely a level nine.

“You guys stay here. I’ll go take a look!” He said to the team. It should not be a problem for a dragon to temporarily leave the contractor for not more than a day.

He spread his wings and flew. His body expanded in size and swooshed in lightning speed towards the exploding light source.

Before Blue Void, Kevin and rest could respond, he disappeared out of sight.

The black lake was as vast as the ocean.

A flutter of Garen’s wings brought him several kilometers in front yet he was still unable to see the end of the lake. The lake water beneath him was smelly and as thick as mud,

As the distance grew closer, he could clearly see the source of the turbulence.

It was a large, four-tailed scorpion, wielding its sharp tails. A young man with dark hair and purple eyes was standing beside it.

The four-tailed scorpion was longer than a hundred meters. Its four tails swung overwhelmingly and made a deep pit wherever it hit.

The man was holding a large sword, and his other hand was burning a purple flame.

Both parties were not moving fast. The man looked tired, it was obvious that the battle had gone on for a while now.

The large sword could automatically expand and stab, while the purple flame could interchange between a large net, spear or javelin, disrupting the scorpion from far range.

Beside them laid a huge beetle the size of an elephant that had died long ago. This must be the thane mentioned by the Undead Butcher…

The sound of Garen’s fluttering winds attracted the attention of both parties.

The four-tailed scorpion swiftly retreated by a few steps and attempted to escape into the lake.

Wham!

Garen pounced over, one of his wings struck the four-tailed scorpion. The thunderous collision rumbled and fumbled the scorpion, making it rolled on the ground a few rounds before getting up in a daze as if it was knocked out of its senses.

“Where’s the treasure? My treasure!” Garen’s dragon eyes stared at the two fellows. They were obviously at level nine but as they were battling for a while now, it was the best time to reap the bargain.

“Treasure?” The man gazed back in bafflement. “White Dragon, you’re here in time. Help me to finish this thing off and I will reward you with a level eight demon core!”

His purple flame blazed, and a clear purple holy emblem emerged in the air.

Garen’s hair raised when he saw this holy emblem.

This guy was a God-Favored!

He dreaded anything God related.

God-Favored may not be very strong but they have a special ability which was called Clone of God… in other words, they could summon a God’s clone into their bodies. Their abilities would temporarily arch the peak of the mortal world.

Therefore, nobody would offend a God-Favored, no matter how low of a level they were. This person was at least a level nine God-Favored. No one would dare offend such a being.

Garen was left with no choice with the calling from the God-Favored. As he dared not offend him, he could only lend a hand. He was about to go after the four-tailed scorpion when a familiar sound wave came to ear.

“Help me! We are the same kind! You can’t leave me to die!!” The four-tailed scorpion’s screeching voice stabbed into his mind.

This fella!!

Garen was in for a headache.

The four-tailed scorpion was a Void being and a Void Demon Lord with high intelligence! He would have never thought that he would come across a battle between a void existence and a God-Favored in an underground city.

“How dare you kill an underground guard placed by my master, unforgivable!” The God-Favored man declared solemnly.

He was referring to the thane beetle that was dead on the ground. This thing had a master. Garen was fortunate that he was not the first to take care of this thing himself.

Now the problem was how to attend to the matters concerning these two.

The four-tailed scorpion was stronger than the God-Favored, but it must be wary of his final trump card which was Clone of God hence its only thought was to flee.

Garen thought quickly and made a call. Its large dragon body lunged towards the four-tailed scorpion.

“Die, blasphemer! Die!”

He dived over threateningly, his fangs and his claws spread open. His large, dragon tail whipped out heavily…

Wham!!

The God-Favored was caught by surprise, flying away as he was struck hard by the tail and was briefly knocked out of consciousness. Garen spun around swiftly and opened his mouth and bit the man on his waist. Crack!!

It was all over…

“You…!!” The God-Favored’s face of disbelief vanished in Garen’s white dragon breath. He did not think that Garen would attack him.

“Hahaha! He must have stayed below the surface for too long that he’s not even wary about his surroundings!!” The four-tailed scorpion burst out laughing in delight.

“If it were a God-Favored just a level below god then you’d be in big trouble. It’s a shame that this fellow was only a regular Holy Knight. He even dared to forge a holy emblem.”

Garen chewed the guy into pieces and spit him out. He did not want to eat him. He might have killed him, but the God behind him would not put this to rest. There sure would be trouble in the future, but this has nothing to do with him. Only a God-Favored could transmit the scene to God prior to his death, while a regular Holy Knight could only do so with a special technique. When that happened though, they would be after the four-tailed scorpion that killed the thane.

“What’s next? I saved you, so how should you repay this debt of gratitude?” Garden looked at the four-tailed scorpion.

As a level nine giant dragon, he could crush any beings at the same level. Garen was confident he could take down any non-dragon species of the same level. It was not him only, any giant dragons would have the same confidence.

“My name is Manfey, and I have been reproducing here for over a thousand years. I have a large group under me. What sort of repayment are you looking at?” The four-tailed scorpion started to bargain, “You and I are beings of the Mother Stream Void, hence you must have heard about the God-Lure Operations, right? I can recommend you to my monarch to have you participate in the operations.”

“God-Lure Operations?” Garen frowned.

“You didn’t know?” The four-tailed scorpion cried out loud in exaggeration. This person was so strong, yet he was not aware of such an important operation.

“Why don’t you tell me about it?” Garen swept his glance over the God-Favored’s corpse. He retained his composure after he confirmed that nothing was out of the ordinary.

He was bound to go against God sooner or later, so killing now or later would not make much of a difference. He was just a God-Favored after all.

“Our alliance has teamed up with this world’s Dragon of Disaster. Using the strongest existence in the mortal world as a threat, we lure the Clones of Gods to descend and kill them off to gradually weaken them,” the four-tailed scorpion explained briefly. “The divinity obtained from killing the clones will be made into a Bottle of Holy Blood. I’m here to create a special trap using the treasure here.”

“I have not been in contact with the Alliance for a long time now,” Garen explained. “So, you’re saying that you intentionally lure this fellow down?”

“No way!?” The four-tailed scorpion blurted with two of its clamps kicking about in high emotions, “I am a noncombatant!”

“Dragon of Disaster?” Garen paid attention to this phrase.

“Yes… a group led by the three Dragons of Disasters, Ann, Jessyca, and Lucy. Right, if you were to participate, you get a share of the Bottle of Holy Blood. Participate or not, that is still a Bottle of Holy Blood that could strengthen the soul!”

Chapter 1310: Gain 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Ann?…” Garen’s heart skipped a beat, “you’re saying that one of the leaders of the Dragons of Disaster group is called Ann?”

“Yes, is there a problem?” The four-tailed scorpion was puzzled, “You know this Dragon of Disaster?”

Garen did not reply.

“Can you talk about this situation related to Ann?”

“Situation? You should really exchange information with the alliance,” the four-scorpion said helplessly, “alright, alright, but I don’t know much.”

A pile of information then flowed into Garen’s mind. It was all about Ann’s situation and information as well as contents of the recent God-Lure Operations.

The operations were successful in some ways as many clones just a level beneath God were lured down and taken care of. This angered many of the churches, bringing the feud between the two parties to a next level.

Ann, a dragon that has engulfed over a hundred billion lives, Dragon of Disaster, Master of Time and Dark Shadow that died 4,600 years ago. There were rumors that she had not died but was hiding in an abyss. Ever since she lost the battle between God of Shadow and Time, she purposely lurked in the dark, concealing her existence from all beings. As the strongest existence amongst the Dark Shadow Dragons, she was once the most beneficiary contender for the divinity of time and shadow but she failed and transformed into a Dragon of Disaster, the energy source of destruction and massacre.

“Dark Shadow Dragon…” Garen suddenly understood why Ann helped him in the first place…

“You have an aura of Pearl of the Temple on you, you must have gotten it then? How lucky. I will not give you such a treasure then. I will instead, reward you with this.” The four-tailed scorpion tossed an item and something black rolled over to Garen.

Garen grabbed the item with his claw. It was a black metal bracelet the size of a human. He could only use it as a ring.

“This is?”

“A God-Favored Detector. It also has a dimensional communicating function. It could penetrate dimensions and communication with the alliance. There’s also some information on how to kill the beings of this world and absorb their energy. Killing beings between our two worlds enable us to obtain their energy. This is the most basic energy source. In simpler terms, the more you kill, the stronger you get!” The four-tailed scorpion concluded, “alright now, more is in there. Take your time to analyze it, I’ll make a move first!”

He quickly shrunk and snuck into the black lake before vanishing.

Garen kept the bracelet and searched around the corpse pieces on the ground, finding two rings with demonic attributes. He then looked around the surroundings and flew off when there was nothing more to be found.

“The more I kill, the stronger I will become?” Garen flipped through the contents in the bracelet while on flying on his way back. This thing was similar to a mini computer, there were all sorts of information in it.

The main thing was how to crystallize an Enneahedron crystal core.

An Enneahedron was the source for Mother Stream Void beings in obtaining this world’s energy.

The way to crystallizing was simple. Just killing a level two being and using its soul as material, could create an Enneahedron. It was naturally evolutional which it could continue to strengthen the main body’s ability as it grew.

He could not be bothered with questions by Blue Void and the rest and went into the tent directly to analyze it carefully, leaving the nitty-gritty to Kevin and his daughter to manage.

He happened to have a Soul Crystal which fulfilled the requirement of creating an Enneahedron.

Following instructions, he extracted the soul and compressed the Soul Power, laying down a simple yet profound course of dimensional formation.

It wasn’t long when an Enneahedron crystal core appeared in his hand.

Garen looked at the Enneahedron in his hand.

It looked similar to a normal Enneahedron crystal. It was colorless and transparent, looking insignificant.

He pressed the Enneahedron on his chest.

Hiss… the Enneahedron automatically mounted into the scales on his chest, becoming a natural ornament. Garen clicked his tongue in wonder.

He could not yet tell what this thing was used for.

Garen pondered for a while, and let the thing absorbed the remaining Soul Crystal. There were no changes.

The Enneahedron had a few stages. There would be a new change once it achieved qualitative changes. Garen was not in a hurry. He took out the Pearl of the Temple, which was the real highlight.

He did not plan to consume it as a single-use item, but rather absorb it gradually.

This gradual absorption was enough for him to add another Soul Ring. A Soul Ring was born through five Soul Seeds. Although it was not as solid as a Soul Ring from a foundation built step by step, this speed was faster than him realizing himself.

He was already at the red Soul Ring stage. Another Soul Ring could perhaps elevate him to the third stage of Heptachromic, at the level of yellow Soul Ring.

Storing the Pearl of the Temple, he swallowed it into his tummy to slowly absorb it in. Garen could feel his surroundings contorting. He was still in the tent moments ago and he suddenly appeared on a deserted, bleak grassland.

Two pure White Dragon Guards were crouching not far off for a rest. Hearing the noise, they got up.

“You’re back?” The Dragon Guard exclaimed with joy.

“Uh huh, how long has it been?” Garen nodded.

“It’s been three days. We are currently at the north grassland near to Snow City. Passing a few more villages and we’ll see Snow City’s territory,” Ken answered.

Adjusting his mood, Garen gazed in the direction of Snow City. It was afternoon.

“Let’s go and continue the journey. Perhaps we’d be able to spend the night at Snow City.”

“Yes,” Annie and Ken did not have any objections.

The three White Dragons soared high up in the sky and flew away.

******

Among the nestled hills and countless mountains, a grand city stood on the highest peak, overlooking the mountain range.

A sea of clouds drifted beneath the city.

The afternoon sunlight painted the pure white city in red. Various flying dragons hovered around the city. Ear piercing howls and roars rattled eardrums from time to time.

The sun resided on the left of the city and was descending slowly.

The three White Dragons including Garen flew to this city. Viewing down from above the sea of clouds, they felt a wonderous feeling looking at the glowing, majestic city. They felt as though as they were flying towards a legendary, ancient city.

On the right of the city, was a high tower carved with a huge golden dragon head. Countless workers were hanging over the dragon head by ropes tied to themselves while they were in labor.

A silver airship measuring over a few hundred meters long swept past beneath Garen and the two White Dragons, sneaking into the clouds and heading towards the city. The passengers on the airship looked up to observe the three White Dragons at close distance.

The side of the vessel was hung with air-dried, white furs. A sculpture of a seductive woman was at the front of the ship.

Whizz!!

Out of a sudden, the space on Garen’s left side began to contort. A large amount of air compressed into the core of a circular area, surging wildly into it before rumbling.

Puff!

Countless air currents spewed out.

As the spurting air current dispersed, a metallic huge ball in a dusty color emerged in the air. It rotated slowly like a terrestrial globe, structured on top of it were densely complicated mechanics. A white halo orbited it like a planetary ring.

The ball was a product of Alchemy, at over a thousand meter in diameter, heading straight to Snow City.

A few figures flew out from the Snow City to welcome and receive it.

“What a wondrous and grand city,” Annie who was beside Garen gasped in admiration.

“I’m seriously considering living here,” Ken smiled.

“It’s a shame that we’d probably not be welcomed,” Garen shook his head. “Let’s go, faster now.”

The three White Dragons hastened their flight to the city.

Without any examination process, they penetrated a thin layer of transparent film without any hindrance when entering the city within a thousand-meter range. Garen passed through the city’s towering walls and descended on a landing spot by the city.

Further up was the attacking range of the center towers. Regardless if it was courtesy or by warning, they were not permitted to fly in the city and could only travel on foot.

Snow City was famous for its crowd of Wizard Towers in the city center. Over a hundred Wizard Towers were built in the city center, concealed by five, six thousand-meter high city walls. Outsiders would not be able to peek in.

The only tower that the city walls could not conceal was the Silver Tower.

It was also the same tower with the sculpture of a dragon head in progress. The ten thousand meters-high tower peaked the clouds. It was eye-catching being the only, standing tower in the whole of Snow City.

It was empty all around when they descended. A few wizard apprentices at the landing spot came up to welcome them.

“This is the descending spot for the dragon races. We have received permission of your descending. Please rest at Dragon Urban Area number 187. Someone has already reserved a room for three of you.”

The apprentice that spoke was a beautiful and innocent-looking young girl. She looked to be cultured, catering to their taste. Apparently, it was not a rumor that giant dragons favor innocent princesses.

“Noted. How do we get to the Dragon Urban Area?”

Garen asked casually.

“This is a guide. Upon activating it, you need not worry about getting lost in the city,” the female apprentice handed over a small round button in pale gold. The button was magnetic as upon contact, it immediately attached to Garen’s scales.

A pale blue cursor appeared before his sight. The striking cursor was in a shape of a guiding arrow.

“How convenient,” Garen sighed in admiration.

“Who helped us to book a room?” Annie was curious, “since we’ve never been here before?”

Garen smiled without saying a word. Apart from Soaring Wing King, he could not think of anyone else who would reserve a room for them. He was sure that Soaring Wing King would be in contact with him very soon after they settled down.

He really needed to establish a Wizard Tower as soon as possible or else he would not dare to investigate the divinity. Once the divinity was dissected for research, it was possible that God would detect his location and punished him from above.

Without a screen to isolate the Divine Power, this high-level research could not be done.

Chapter 1311: Dragon Master 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dragon Urban Area Hotel.

Different from the Human Urban Area, the hotels and residences in the Dragon Zone varied in height and entrance level, some were high some were low. Some of them hung off a cliff, some of them were underground, while some had poisonous mist lingering around it, making it suitable for poisonous dragons to stay.

The magnitude of the building scale in this zone was huge and eye-catching, at least three to five times bigger than a regular human building. Dragons and Dragon Beasts of various sizes roamed the streets. The Dragon Beasts were horrifyingly powerful beings.

Walking from town area, one could observe that the surrounding buildings were pure white in color, while some shimmered in pale gold.

Garen and the two followed the guide’s direction and arrived at a frozen, snow-covered pyramid-shaped building.

“Welcome, three honorable White Dragons.” Two Dragon Lizards with seductive figures greeted them at the door. These lizards carried the dragon bloodline, and they were a mini version of the dragons. From a dragon aesthetic concept, their figures were considered sexy and suited their taste.

It was a shame that Garen did not respond to the winks thrown by these two Dragon Lizards.

“It’s here,” he lifted his head to look at the hotel’s name, Blood of Moon Gaze.

“You must be Lord Garen?” As the two Dragon Lizards were lost in sorrow, out came another Dragon Lizard smiling saying, “Welcome to Blood of Moon Gaze, a reservation has been made for the three of you. Feel free to ask us if you require anything. Please follow me and I will show you to your room.”

Garen nodded, and together with the other two, followed this slightly bigger Dragon Lizard into the pyramid. It was how he had imagined it to be, the place was compressed by space but the actual space was much more than it looked to be.

The hotel was specially designed for frozen Snow Dragons as cold, white air spurted out in funnels similar to air-conditioning, spraying down like wonderland.

There was a huge pond by the side, a few Snow Class Blue Dragons gathered closely with an old White Dragon, conversing softly.

Other than them, no other Dragon Clans could be seen.

Garen and the two entered and took a look around casually. Hive-like empty holes were everywhere.

Following the Dragon Lizard into a cave, the space within it changed and converted into a new, white frozen cave.

“This will be your room. You can knock on the door if you require anything and a waiter will come forth to serve you,” the big Dragon Lizard explained in a low voice.

“Thank you,” Garen looked around the cave. There were three independent caves divided in there. There were even special tools placed in the rooms, large-scale tools that provided dragons entertainment, such as… a huge hammock…

“If you want to play some interesting games, I can also provide some convenient services,” the Dragon Lizard chuckled.

Garen and the rest were speechless.

But seeing how Annie was implicated and stealing glances at him, she must be aroused…

Although dragons were lascivious, Garen still found it hard to comprehend their hardcore taste.

After gesturing for the Dragon Lizard to leave, the three retreated into their caves respectively. Garen had just entered his cave to rest when low moans and groans were heard coming from Annie’s cave on the right.

Needless to say, Annie and Ken must be doing each other.

A human scholar once researched that apart from spending half their lives on sleeping or resting, dragons used the remaining seventy percent of their time to mate.

“Looks like there is some truth to that…” Garen was speechless.

Sleeping in a coiled-up position on the ice bed, he grabbed a bunch of frozen grapes. Tossing it into his mouth, he chewed and swallowed the sweet and sour grapes.

He began to rest and entered dreamland.

He charged to the third level with familiarity.

It was the same sealed room in a villa with a giant crow flying around it.

Garen opened his eyes and found himself sitting in the middle of the sofa.

Black ashes drizzled down lightly from the air, disappearing as soon as it landed on him.

“I have been waiting for you for a long time,” Soaring Wing King’s voice was heard coming from his back.

“Soaring Wing King, it was you who arranged the room?” Garen turned and stood up. He saw Soaring Wing King standing by the window, holding a staff. His back was resting on the window lattice with his eyes closed.

“Yes, are you satisfied? That’s one of the popular hotels that most dragons want to visit. Blood of Moon Gaze has the blessing from the Reproduction God that could increase fertility to a certain stage,” Soaring Wing King opened his eyes and gave him a naughty wink.

“Yeah, right… I don’t have such a hardcore taste,” Garen was speechless. “Alright now, let’s talk about the plan you mentioned before.”

“And your answer?”

“Answer… I can agree to it but I need some time,” Garen frowned. “The time frame you confirmed is a little long.”

“That’s out of my hands. Other than you, I have another two candidates but they’re no better than you,” Soaring Wing King shook his head. “Getting in contact with that race is not just dangerous, it’s troublesome.”

“The God Damnator race is an enemy of God. It’s the doing of the Gods that they’re sealed in that dimension. Why is it your turn to suppress them now?” Garen asked.

“There’re many reasons to it which you can’t imagine. Moreover, this branch of God Damnators managed to escape the eyes of God using some special tactics. If it weren’t because we noticed something amiss, and took it as one of the weapons to retaliate against the Gods, they probably would have broken out from the seal. These God Damnators are quite valiant, the consequences would be severe if they were to escape,” Soaring Wing King explained in brief.

“So apart from guarding and reinforcing the seal, what else do I have to do?” Garen asked in detail.

“If you are able to obtain complete control at the crucial moment, and release them when we need them to be released, the Alliance would be happy. You have Enneahedron on you, you must have found a way to absorb Souls?” Soaring Wing King smiled.

“Yes.”

“I need to remind you that the Enneahedron is basically snatching the Souls of this world and is the same nature as those Gods, so it is easy to be discovered by them. Once they’re onto you, you will be taken care of the first minute so do not execute a massacre until necessary.”

“How long do I need to defend?”

“Fifty years. During the fifty years, if you’re willing, I will build a Wizard Tower in the Defending Zone. If you are alright to have the tower where the seal is, I will apply for an exemption for a majority of the materials. If you are not willing, then you would have to foot the bill yourself.”

“Fifty years…” It has only been a few years since Garen arrived in this world. A price of fifty years seemed quite hefty.

The God Damnator race was a powerful existence, possessing great resistance against the existence of God and going against it.

Normally, the birth of one God Damnator would trigger fear in a country or even a dimension so the release of an entire God Damnator race would be disastrous.

It was also one of the bargaining chips that allowed the Arcanists to be able to maintain independence amongst the Gods. They held in hand with them thirteen God Damnator sealing venues and guarded the security of these seals.

Soaring Wing King wanted Garen to secure one of the locations and his goal was to have Garen grasp control of it for fifty years to cooperate with the Alliance to destroy this dimension.

“You’re not the only one in this. The Alliance has sent forth another two powerful existences. It may be not successful, and the chances of success are low. We are trying our luck hence it would be best if we succeed but it’s also quite alright if we don’t.”

“Fifty years is too long. I would need some form of compensation,” Garen thought about it before continuing to bargain. Truth be told, he was already moved by it.

“If it’s compensation, what do you want then?” Soaring Wing King pondered for a while. He thought highly of Garen. Even as a high-ranking Demon Lord, a development speed such as Garen’s was still rare.

“I would need a large number of Demon Cores or Soul Crystals. The higher the level, the better,” said Garen solemnly.

“Demon Cores? Sure, what specific level do you need?” Soaring Wing King’s frown loosened up.

It might be difficult if he requested for other things, but Snow City had plenty of this Demon Cores.

“What’s the most you can offer?” Garen asked.

“One level nine Demon Core, ten level eights and a hundred level sevens. What do you think?”

“It might be better if I hunt it myself then!” Garen exclaimed in disdain. “Hunting a few level nine beings in the ocean of another dimension is a lot more than what you’re offering.”

“It seems you’re akin to things related to the Soul. Perhaps there’s a thing you may like,” Soaring Wing King smiled. “The Despair Head of Annas.”

He gestured an arch with his finger and a floating silhouette instantly appeared midair. It was a gleaming skull.

As soon as this thing appeared, Garen felt a vast potential aura surging over but disappeared almost immediately as though it was all in his head.

“This is an unprecedented, semi-divine weapon left behind by a powerful godly being upon passing. It used to be a part of a death staff divine weapon. It was then disassembled so it’s a semi-divine weapon,” Soaring Wing King noticed that Garen was visibly moved.

“This semi-divine weapon can falsify and steal the power of belief. In it harbor the torrenting will of a great god. It could restrain any existence lower than your own level and decrease their reaction by two levels.”

Garen gazed at this semi-divine weapon intensely, unable to turn his sight away. He was lacking a multitude of Potential Points in the original void and this semi-divine weapon harbored at least a few thousand Potential Points. It was the greatest reservoir he had ever seen.

After putting many thoughts to it, Garen lifted his head.

“It’s a deal then.”

“Great,” Soaring Wing King was satisfied. “And if you would like to join the Blood War, it will not be a problem. I can send you directly to Ten Thousand Abyss Plains. The condition is that you must return alive or else everything will be wasted.”

“Of course,” answered Garen.

******

Waking up from his dream, it was already the morning of the next day.

Garen recalled the matters he agreed with Soaring Wing King, about the semi-divine weapon and guarding the sealing venue. These were two important matters.

He touched his right leg. A huge tumor grew at the back of it. It was obvious in red and seemed to be growing bigger.

“I need more Potential Points, more Souls… I will need to go to Blood Wars. The real battle fifty years later will kill me if I’m not strong enough…”

“Master Garen, someone’s is here asking for you, saying that you’re an old acquaintance who came all the way to visit you,” Annie whispered from outside.

Chapter 1312: Dragon Master 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Old acquaintance?” Garden could not recall of anybody from Snow City who was an old acquaintance.

“Male or female?”

“A female. She seemed elegant and strong,” Annie answered honestly.

“I’ll go take a look,” Garen really could not think of anybody knowing him here. Soaring Wing King would definitely not contact him out of the blue, otherwise, communications with Void beings would be exposed and he would be dragged into it too.

Stepping out of his cave, Garen only saw Annie present. Ken was out of sight but he was not bothered. Dragon Guards too have their own personal time and space.

Approaching the frozen cave’s door and experiencing a dimensional distortion, Garen appeared at the pyramid hotel’s entrance.

A petite girl stood out among the large beasts which were bustling around the busy streets.

Standing outside the hotel waiting for him was a cute, little girl dressed in a white blouse and black-laced skirt. She had light brown, wavy bangs and two, long ponytails tied up which tailed all the way down to her waist. Her skin was fair and delicate, giving an impression of a next-door sweetheart.

In her hands were a bouquet of white roses. Standing at the entrance of the hotel circled by large beasts, she seemed fragile and timid, and others could not help feeling the want to protect her.

This was the Dragon Urban Area, the residence and activity zone of large beasts. It was incomprehensible for a human to come over.

Garen and Annie caught sight of the girl as soon as they came out. She was hard to miss.

She was just too cute. Her pouted tender pink lips and puffy cheeks indicated that she was a little unhappy from waiting long.

But the second she saw Garen walking out, the little girl beamed with joy.

“It’s Garen! I finally see you! My beloved Lord Garen!!” She darted forward towards Garen, opening her arms. Her voluptuous breasts were undisguisedly facing Garen’s direction.

The Dragons around cast envious looks. This was typical, throwing oneself into somebody’s arm gesture. If Dragons knew of the Ultimate Transformation Spell, they could enjoy a long sexual lifestyle. No Dragon would let go of such a cute worshiper that even if one could not transform, any form of sexual activity would be considered a fortunate event.

Garen had not even gathered what was happening when he saw the girl darting over.

Dragons have natural urges, and the little girl’s heavy aura could not help but instigated hot-blooded impulses.

Garen could not help but opened his arms wide, fearing that the little girl would stumble on to the ground. Very quickly though, he realized something was not right. How could there be such a circumstance when his willpower was normally strong.

It was then that the little girl’s expression in her eyes changed. With a swish, the bouquet of roses in her hands turned into an exceptionally large, heavy metal hammer. It was engraved with countless dark golden characters, and the aura flowing on it surpassed that of level nine. It was a semi-divine weapon!

“Hahaha!! Another genius dragon is mine!!! Hahaha!!!” The little girl laughed maniacally, an extreme contrast with the earlier, cute appearance.

“A Dragon Master!!” Garen’s heart skipped a beat, startled. The metal hammer in the seemingly cute little girl’s was a heavy, unavoidable threat to Garen.

Given the extremely close distance, he would not be able to dodge in time. He decisively charged forward in full force.

Wham!!!

The huge collision burst open a wave of faint ripples around him.

The little girl’s face changed. She knew it was not good. Even if she was able to restrain Garen during this impact, she would suffer fatal injuries. The loss outweighed the gain.

“Damn you! To be my personal slave is your luck, yet you dare retaliate!!?” She shouted out loud. She immediately retrieved the contracted glow on the hammer and turned her focus on defending her body.

Wham!!!

The entire street rumbled from the impactful collision. The street surface between Garen and the little girl cracked open a rift. Snow City’s automated repair machinery went to work immediately, and the rift was repaired at visible velocity.

Garen rammed mercilessly onto the little girl. Strangely enough, the little girl’s physique looked light but she was in fact as heavy as a mountain. He only managed to knock her over, flipping three to four rounds before she stabilized herself.

“Don’t you dare escape!!”

The little girl screamed, as she stood firmly and wielded her little arm in the air. Three Red Dragons instantly charged out from her back towards Garen.

The three Red Dragons were in adult form. As they charged towards Garen, the dynamic air current pressed on both sides, high heat radiation spread out causing the temperature to increase rapidly.

“Let me!” Annie dashed ahead towards a Red Dragon. Ken too seemed to charge out of nowhere towards another Red Dragon.

The remaining Red Dragon pounced at Garen ferociously. There was no killing intent, but a bitter smile flashed across its eyes.

“Don’t fight it, it will save everybody’s time.”

Garen did not even look at him as his body suddenly expanded. His tail whipped out, leaving behind a trail of shadow.

With a loud wham, the Red Dragon was struck away, tumbling into the opposite building, creating ripples on the building’s protective film surface.

Beep!!

The alarm sounded in the Urban Area. Sounds of giant dragons’ fluttering wings could be heard from a distance. The security was on their way.

“Rola!” The Dragon Master girl screeched in a sharp voice.

Swish!

A shackle glowing in light yellow burst out from her chest, trespassing space and appeared in front of Garen’s chest before binding itself tightly around Garen.

Garen was shocked. The chain was abnormally sturdy that even his eighty point strength could not break him free.

The Dragon Master laughed in delight. With a gesture of her little hand, space tore open. She jumped into it, and Garen disappeared together with her.

The Red Dragons turned into shadows and disappeared completely in a puff.

******

“Contract, I swear with my Soul that you will forever submit to me, never resisting. What’s yours is mine, what’s mine is mine, not yours. You and I are one body yet separated. I swear to love you wholeheartedly, and willing to be lifetime partners with you. Together we rise, together we fall. We’ll spend when we have money, drink when we have water…”

A mess of chants rung in Garen’s ear.

He woke up leisurely from his momentary unconsciousness from the space-time teleportation, finding that he was still tied up. The little girl in black skirt was in front of him, muttering some weird incantation.

Wham!

Instinctively, his tail lashed out. The little girl flew at the sound and knocked only something violently before crying out loud.

“Damn you, Garen, don’t you know I hate it the most when someone hits my face!! You’re dead! You’re so dead!! Ah!!! Let me go, I want to kill him!!!”

At a wall of the cave not far away, the little girl was screaming, flipped, as she was held back by a Black Dragon helplessly.

One side of the little girl’s face was swollen from the tail’s whip.

Garen then realized that he was inside some cave. It was dark everywhere, except for a few spots lit up by some candles.

Eight giant dragons gathered around. There were Black Dragons, Red Dragons, Purple Dragons and Blue Dragons. He was the only White Dragon.

“I say, young lady, this fellow is only a White Dragon. Do you really want us all to concentrate our powers to restrain him?”

“Duh!!” Dragon Master Asilia screeched. “He is the strongest White Dragon in history, how can you all idiots compare to him!!?”

“Young lady, it’s not nice to hear that,” a Black Dragon replied listlessly. “It’s just a slightly stronger White Dragon, he could not be stronger than any of us Black Dragons?”

“Even my powers weren’t able to restrain him! You guys wait till he terrorizes you all!” Asilia continued to cuss out loud.

“If you can’t restrain him, all you will be scrubbing the toilet! Scrub! Toilet! Ahhhhhh!!” Asilia seemed to lose her mind a lot, as she started to shriek again while pulling her hair.

Seeing the expressions on the surrounding giant dragons, it was obvious that they were quite used to it.

Garen stood up, flipping his huge dragon tail.

“Dragon Master Asilia? You look like a kid who hasn’t grown up.”

“What!? How dare you say I’m a kid!!?? You’re dead! You’re sooo dead! Wait till we are bounded by contract and I’ll have you scrub the toilet for three hundred days! Three hundred days!!!” Asilia obviously believed that scrubbing toilets were the ultimate punishment.

“Alright, let’s begin,” the Black Dragon listlessly said. “I want to continue enjoying my life after this, I don’t have time to waste here.”

“Alright, little Asilia, stand further away. We are gathering our powers, don’t let us hurt you,” a female Red Dragon smiled.

“I’m joining in too!!” Asilia jumped in.

“No, there’s no need. Although you share one-third of our powers, your body can’t fully use this tremendous power. It’s better for you to sit on the side and observe,” a Blue Dragon reminded gently.

Garen looked at the eight dragons encircling him. Dragon Master Asilia seemed to be on good terms with these contracted giant dragons. These giant dragons did not seem unwilling. What an odd contracted relationship.

“Four adult dragons, four young dragons. You’re willing to be this little girl’s contracted giant dragon? How strange,” Garen muttered.

If this was the only case, then it was fine but these dragons were not any regular dragons. They all had a special, rippling aura on them. Asilia must have her eye on their individual strengths.

“There’s nothing strange. Once you sign the contract, you’ll understand why,” a Blue Dragon said lightly. “Although I don’t know why Asilia took a fancy to you, a White Dragon, she must have her reasons with her decision.”

Once the master-slave contract was formalized, there would be no secret. Garen did not want his biggest secret exposed but these eight dragons had some special formation that could combine their powers together. He was now tied up by that light yellow shackles that weakened his body by a tad.

“On behalf of Snow city, if you let me go now, I can still forgive you,” Garen said solemnly. Asilia was the daughter of the Silver Tower Master in Snow City. Unless pushed to the extreme, he really did not want to offend this ability which peaked in the mortal world. As the President of Snow City, that monstrous old man held in hand a terrifying authority that was similar to King Gus. He was also at the range of the Silver Tower powers.

Chapter 1313: Blood Wars 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“How arrogant,” a Purple Dragon answered listlessly. “Let’s do it so this little one will learn to respect his stronger elders.”

“Hehehe…” The Black Dragon rubbed his claws and snickered.

This group of fellows seemed to be quite the oddballs.

Garen had already made his point so he was not going to waste any more breath and got up. A layer of white golden color started to spread out over his scales.

“This little guy is about to make a big one, restrain him!!” The Purple Dragon shouted out loud.

The group of giant dragons bolted over. With Garen in the middle, the surrounding eight giant dragons stuck themselves onto the transparent barrier beside Garen, unleashing rays in varying tones of color.

Their movements paused for a moment before a powerful, large force burst out.

“Dragon Force Formation! This is the Dragon Force Formation I devoted myself to creating, you can’t escape now, hahaha!!!” Asilia had her hands on her waist as she laughed hysterically.

“You little pipsqueak better be prepared to lick my ass! Ha! Ha! Ha!”

This fellow was getting out of hand.

It was at this moment when the large multitude of colors clicked, and a horrifying white golden glow broke out from the chained shackles. Garen’s body expanded rapidly into multiplying folds of his original size to twice the size of an adult giant dragon.

He gently swiped his massive tail.

Wham!!

The assembled Dragon Force Formation by the eight giant dragons crushed. The eight dragons flew out from the impact, whizzing in high-velocity wind.

“What!!??” Asilia was stunned and wham, she was knocked right in the face by one of the flying Red Dragons.

Wham!

She crashed violently onto the wall before tumbling down together with the Red Dragon. A human and a dragon laid on the ground whimpering, not being able to get up.

Bam, bam.

In just two steps, Garen came before her. He extended his large claw to dangle her up, as his tail made another sweep on a giant dragon which was trying to get up.

“Little girl, there’s a price to pay for being so arrogant,” he dangled Asilia by the collar like a pendulum.

“Let… me… go!!” Asilia shouted weakly. She was alright from that dreadful bang onto the wall. She must share much of the Dragon Force that her vitality was similar to a dragon’s.

Roar!!

A Black Dragon bit Garen’s wings from behind.

Garen swung his body casually, and the Black Dragon was tossed into the wall by Garen’s wings. Runes appeared on the wall, but the wall did not crumble. The Black Dragon instead was smashed to the point that he was incognizant, with blood bleeding out of his seven apertures.

Wham! Wham! Wham!!

With three consecutive knocks, the claw on Garen’s wing let go of the Black Dragon and left him to free fall. He had lost his strength to retaliate.

“You’re next,” Garen looked at Asilia. His malicious eyes gave this little girl the chills.

“No, you can’t do this to me!” She shrieked.

“You can ambush me, yet I can’t return the favor?” Garen curled his lips into a smile, “or maybe, you have another choice.”

“What… what other choices?”

“Let me eat you,” Garen made out an evil face.

“Ah!!!!” Asilia cried out loud. “You’re dead!! Dead!! How dare you bully me!! My father will not let you go!!”

Garen’s ears were ringing, his eardrums hurt from her sharp screeching.

“Stop crying!! Stop crying!!!” He roared.

But her voice got louder and louder, crispier and crispier, stabbing hard into his brain.

“Wa…! I’m going to die!!!” Asilia continued to wail.

Garen felt something sticky leaking out of his ears. He touched it. It was White Dragon blood!

He immediately tossed Asilia away.

But a terrifying force froze her in midair. Asilia’s cries continued but her eyes flashed a white silvery glow.

Garen felt his body weakened. He scanned his status. This voice depressed an average of ten attribute points.

He dared not stay on further and made a dash to the cave’s entrance. This Dragon Master was too weird. He glanced at the eight giant dragons on the ground. These fellows were conversing while lying on the ground, only the Black Dragon was wiping off blood from his body with a long face.

“I say, that fellow must not be able to withstand, right?” The purple dragon said while lying down.

“Once Asilia’s ultimate technique is out, it is without parallel! She is the direct bloodline of that lord after all.”

“There will be another companion joining us soon.”

“Isn’t that great? This time, this fellow is not just your regular valiant. We are easily shaken off.”

“You, a Purple Dragon, come talking to us about strength?”

“Let’s see how long he’ll last?”

“I’m betting ten seconds.”

“I bet one minute. He must be immune from level nine spellcraft. Tsk tsk, no wonder the young lady was so hung up on it. Already immune to level nine spellcraft at such a young age, you can just imagine how strong he will be in the future.”

“It can be a little troublesome. Such a young talent, if Tiamat were to get word of it…”

“It’s okay. It’s Snow City here, the territory of Ola. Tiamat can only rot in purgatory and abyss.”

The giant dragons were unharmed from the soundwave due to the contract, so they were in the mood to do small talks.

But Garen was not in the most pleasant mood. He felt the scales on his body loosening up. This sound wave of an energy seemed to be equivalent to a level nine Succubus’ Wail, perhaps even more powerful and could last forever. He might be immune to level nine spellcraft, but this sort of long-term damage would loiter.

Wham!

Garen hammered himself heavily onto the transparent barrier in the cave, creating clear ripples.

The massive force quaked the entire cave.

The eight giant dragons looked over with their jaws dropped. They didn’t think that Garen possessed such powerful strength.

Asilia was startled as well, and she stopped shrieking. The white silvery color in her eyes finally faded away.

Garen glanced at her in pain. He finally understood the reason why the three elders warned him to stay away from Dragon Masters. This little one… was just so strange.

The earlier powers… did not seem it could be wielded by just anybody. It was obvious Asilia harbored with her a deep secret. This secret must be related to the upper levels amongst Arcanists. He really did not want to be tied down to anything prestigious this early.

He gave another hard ram.

With a bang, the walls of the cave crumbled. The entire cave contorted and the scenery around changed. Garen suddenly found himself back in the streets of the hotel.

The guards and patrolling flying dragons had tightened their security around. His sudden appearance did not cause a panic but quickly, a lean elegant Blue Dragon walked up.

“You look fine?” The Blue Dragon was surprised. “Don’t worry, Asilia has been taken away by the Tower Master to be taught a lesson. This time, she was too irrational. The Tower Master will be giving all dragons a satisfactory answer and compensation.”

There were large groups of level two and three elites patrolling around here with a few veiled powerful auras that could be felt.

It looked as though that the attack had triggered a negative impact in Snow City.

The Blue Dragon blocked the mess on Garen. He was slightly surprised and felt pitiful. If Asilia and Garen had succeeded in binding a contract, things would be easier to take care of. The contract binding failed so Silver Tower would need to pacify the dragons with a satisfactory answer, otherwise, any dragon with the slightest talent would be forced to sign a contract and no Dragon Clan would ever want to cooperate with Snow City and that could be troublesome.

A few old dragons wielding white staffs flew over from a distance and landed gently by Garen.

“Thank Tiamat that Master Garen you’re all okay. We are already in serious negotiations with Silver Tower. Don’t you worry, this time we will definitely uphold justice for you!” They held with them a White Dragon Mountain emblem. They must be representatives of White Dragon Mountain. They reeked of heavy divine powers of Dragon God. They were Tiamat’s dragon pastors.

Rushing over at the very first moment, they were here to brown nose.

Garen responded with a smile and exchanged greetings in gesture of graciousness. Soon, the group of dragons sent Garen off to the hotel to rest. Of course, it was not the same hotel but another. Ken and Annie rushed over, with a strong adult Black Dragon following behind them. Another exchange of politeness, this Black Dragon was a level ten in charge of coordination between humans and dragons in Snow City. Ken and Annie had apparently gone off to seek help.

A few of the White Dragons with contracts with Snow City nobles came over to express support. Garen responded all with open arms. The representative of Silver Tower, a level eight old wizard came over, showing concern and apologized on behalf. He also offered plenty of options in compensation.

The situation caused by the Dragon Master was then laid to rest but Garen was now wary of Asilia.

That white silvery eyes really stunk of godliness.

******

A shop in Dragon Urban Area.

Garen and his two Dragon Guards were hanging around in a department store swamped with various large beasts. There was no sight of any human. They were all large beasts with huge body types. Dragons were the main customers while the rests were oddly shaped dragon beasts or highly intelligent large beasts.

The boss was a large octopus ten of meters in height. Each of its tentacles has eyes, a natural surveillance camera.

The store sold many unique sparkly items. Some were enchanted while others were natural treasure, jewels or crystals. There were even unknown mysterious items. The lowest price was set at over a million gold coins, definitely not your regular rip off.

Garen stood behind two large-headed monsters, looking at a transparent crystal ball on the counter.

“Boss, how much is this?”

He squeezed in and grabbed the crystal ball, asking.

The octopus monster reached out a tentacle and sized Garen up.

“Twenty million, non-negotiable.”

“Void Crystal. It can imprison a soul from another world level eight above but below level ten. A must-have to build a Wizard Tower.”

Chapter 1314: Blood Wars 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen nodded.

It was a must-have item to build an Advanced Wizard Tower and this item alone cost twenty million gold coins. Although its price was rather exaggerated, he would have already guessed that the materials required to build an Advanced Wizard Tower would be incredibly expensive.

He had obtained a batch of unique and shiny treasures that was adored by the Dragon Clan from the Silver Tower as compensation since his encounter with Asilia.

Then, he brought this wealth along with him and started to inquire about relevant materials required to building a Wizard Tower to estimate the total cost required.

He managed to estimate the total cost needed within a few days and the total expenditure was no lower than what Soaring Wing King had said.

He also gained a valuable piece of information in the past few days. He finally had a full understanding of Snow City and its circumstances.

This city was saturated with idle mercenaries and travelers ranging from Level Two to Level Five. The Battle Wizards, Mercenary Warriors, the Berserk Barbarians and the Dwarves formed the majority and next in line was the humans. Most of the pure humans here were high levels and the follow-ups were hybrids related to the humans such as Hybrid Half-Elf, Barbarians, and Human Hybrids. There were a lot of hybrids between humans and succubus such as the Wizard Disciple, who greeted Garen, had the rare Succubus blood flowing through his body.

The pure humans who had the courage to visit here were typically at least Great Wizard Level and above as this place was termed as the Wizard City. Great Wizards were often spotted in the streets as they were not considered valuable here.

Garen could sense one or two hidden presences that threatened him as he looked down the street.

“No wonder the Snow City is often said to be as strong as an empire.”

After having a clear overall picture of the items’ prices, Garen went straight to the bookstore to buy a complete set of Basic Arcane Spellcraft books. He spent at least a hundred thousand on the books and ordered Ken to purchase the basic ingredients for the types of Spellcraft for research purposes.

He himself brought Annie along to the Wizard Tower located in the inner city where the Soaring Wing King lived.

It was the Dwarf Urban Area the moment he got out of the Dragon Urban Area. As Garen was not allowed to stop moving, he went passed through the Dwarf Urban Area directly towards the entrance of the Transportation Formation so that he could head directly to the address which Soaring Wing King had given him.

The transportation was incredibly fast as Garen immediately arrived at the Soaring Wing King’s Wizard Tower – Black Crow Tower.

***********

“Please wait for a moment. The Tower Master is currently giving his honorable guest his daily treatment.”

The Wizard Apprentice was a young and busty girl. She explained to Garen softly as she served him hot, concentrated tea.

Garen’s body had shrunk to the size of a dragon whelp so it was not a problem for him to sit on a slightly larger chair. On the other hand, it was not possible for Annie so she could only lay on the ground, resting while observing the surroundings cautiously with her dragon eyes.

The Black Crow Tower was one of the tallest towers out of the few hundreds of Wizard Towers. This was related to the social standing of the Soaring Wing King as he was a member of the Snow City and Grey Shadow Society at the same time. He was one of the highest members that could decide the fate of the Snow City.

Afterall, one would not be able to spot a Level Twelve anywhere. Hence, it was only natural for him to reach such a social standing with his strength.

Garen waited for a while and the Soaring Wing King soon appeared in this floor with a crutch.

He looked rather tired and he seemed to have exhausted a lot of his strength.

Garen stood up.

“Good day, your honorable Soaring Wing King.”

“The powerful White Dragon genius. I’ve heard of your reputation the moment I reached the city. Hehe. How can I treat you?” He was one of the renowned, best therapists in the Snow City as well.

Both of them acted as if they do not know each other.

“Of course not. The reason I’m here is because of this.” Garen flicked his finger and shot out a pile of white mist which automatically formed into a clear image in mid-air, revealing his advanced technique in controlling the chilled air.

The image only appeared for a second. It was actually a pointless symbol and a signal of the promise between them.

It meant that Garen had finished his preparation and had come to fulfill the contract.

The Soaring Wing King smiled faintly.

“I understand. When do you plan to depart?” He was asking when he was going to participate in the Blood Wars at the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains located in the Abyss.

“I can go whenever I want since I can prepare myself at any given moment,” Garen replied confidently. He had to strengthen himself within fifty years and the Blood Wars was the fastest and best option for him to hunt for Souls. Naturally, this was the assumption that he could survive.

“You should go and get prepared. You’ll need all of the essentials, otherwise, you’ll only know how valuable they are when you need them most.” The Soaring Wing King reminded him in a friendly manner.

Garen nodded.

He wished to purchase some above average medicine from the Soaring Wing King as well since the Abyss’ Blood Wars was filled with terrifying wars ranging from low levels to high levels. Despite him being a Level Nine being, it was of his best interest to not underestimate the harsh environment there.

Garen did not wish to stay in Snow City any longer as he had a feeling that the Dragon Master Asilia would not give up that easily. Hence, he decided to participate in the Blood Wars as soon as possible.

Entering a room together, Soaring Wing King sprinkled a huge amount of Isolation Powder, enacting an absolute divine barrier which ensured that the environment was safe to talk freely.

“Okay, I’ve prepared all of the items you required. The High-Grade Transporation Scroll, Positioning Stone, High-Grade Recovery Ointment and the Emergency Guard. Since you’re immune to Level Nine Spells, most of the Gain Scrolls are ineffective against you as well.” The Soaring Wing King reminded again, “You have to be careful out there. It is the eternal battlefield between Demon Batz and Tanar’ri. Try not to reveal your full strength as much as possible. Regardless if it’s the Abyss or the Nine Layers of Hell, there exist beings comparable to the Demigods and even the Evil Gods live in one of the layers as well. I don’t wish for you to die there this early and your corpse turning into materials. That would mean that our contract is ruined for good. I’ll ask you one last time, are you sure you want to go into the Blood Wars?”

He asked him in all seriousness.

“I’m very sure,” Garen nodded. Although Garen knew of the dangers of the Blood Wars, it was the only place that he could grow quickly. In this material plane, he would require a huge amount of Demon Cores in order to achieve his desired strength.

Recently, he felt that his body is undergoing a strange evolution. Thorns started to grow on his back and it seemed that he would be entering a new evolution soon.

Furthermore, he wanted to see for himself the horrifying war between the legendary Demon Tanar’ri and Devil Batz.

Regardless if it was the Potential Points or Enneahedron, both of these would require a huge amount of stolen Souls. This was a huge taboo in the material plane and would be easily detected by the God. However, it was entirely different in the Abyss.

“It’s not an easy task to find a more suitable person than you. I wish you good luck.” The Soaring Wing King said regrettably. “However, I believe that we Demon Kings are beings who experienced and survived countless battles and we will not simply die in this world.”

“That’s but of course,” Garen smiled as he curled his lips.

“These are your items.” Soaring Wing King passed a small ring to Garen, he took it and glanced at the contents inside. The Semi-Divine Weapon that was promised was included in it as well. Food, drinks, medicine and so on were all well prepared.

“Do you need armor and weapon?”

“What kind of armor is tougher than my scales? Weapon? My claw is much more powerful than any weapon existed,” Garen said without a care in the world.

“That’s true.” Soaring Wing King nodded. “When do you plan to leave? I’ll make preparations as well.”

“Let’s do it today.” Although he had only stayed in a small corner of the Snow City for a few days, he had yet to immerse himself in the city’s atmosphere, but given his concerns from being targeted by the Dragon Master, he did not wish to stay any longer.

“You can tell two of my guards the truth when I leave. I don’t wish to be dragged by them both.”

“How pitiful to call two Level Eight beings a burden,” Soaring Wing King shook his head. “By the way, you have to be cautious when you’re using the Despair Head of Annas. Most of the demons and devils in the Abyss are very sensitive towards souls and beliefs and you’ll be easily spotted.”

“I understand.” Garen nodded. Other than having an enormous amount of Potential Aura, this item is very useful in gathering Soul Energy. He could collect the Souls that had died in the war on the battlefield. However, he had to be discreet about it as collecting Souls would be equivalent to snatching the goods away from the Abyss.

“Do you have the overall intel of the Abyss?”

“I only have the intel for Ten Thousand Abyss Plains. There are a lot of steel fortresses built by the Devils. Since their management is very strict, you can only participate in the war alongside with the demons,” Soaring Wing King explained.

“What about those Demon Kings that had departed before me?”

“We lost contact with them. The chaos in the Abyss would cut off all communication from the material plane. Hence we are unable to keep in touch with them at all times.”

Garen then compared the intel he had obtained from Ann as he inquired about the Abyss’s intel and information.

There were two lowest and most basic life forms in the Abyss. The first one was the Demonic Worms, which was also known as the Abyss Maggots. They were the initial form of all demons and would slowly evolve via the trial of survival of the fittest.

The second life form was the Prayer.

When the Soul had been corrupted by the Abyss, the Soul would become distorted. They were at the very bottom of the hierarchy and were the workers and slaves. Some of them were even turned into materials for battleships.

Next in line were the demons in varieties of shapes and sizes. Among all of the demons, the Tanar’ri’s clan was the strongest and was the main force that fought against the Devils in the Blood Wars.

After having a clearer understanding of the situation, Garen found a portion of the Abyss’ most recent map. Since the geography of the Abyss often changed, it was not necessary to keep them for the long term.

He had also obtained another information from the Soaring Wing King. The largest Spacetime Dimension Fissure had been opened somewhere in the south and there were a huge amount of Void Creatures of different types gushing out from it. The priests from the major Gods and even the Divine Officers and Bishops had already gone to the scene

The Void Lords and the True Souls had engaged in a large scale war as they tried to secure the lands as their base.

As all of the Gods were paying attention on this end, the Demon Lords who had hidden hoped that they could grow quickly so that they could be on the field in fifty years time.

After making everything clear, Garen sent the two Dragon Guards back as he stayed behind to learn a thing or two related to the requirement to increase his Arcane Techniques from the Soaring Wing King. Naturally, he had to pay for it. Finally, he went back to the hotel with the Despair Skull, Semi-Divine weapon, and the signed contract.

There was one thing that he had to do before he went to the Blood Wars. He had to absorb the huge amount of potential aura from the Despair Skull. He would be able to reach a new height before participating in the Blood Wars if he were successful.

Chapter 1315: Disturbance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Evening hours.

Inside the Black Crow Tower.

After Garen and his underling dragons left the area, a small human figure came rushing in noisily through the Black Crow Tower’s main entrance.

“Hahaha! I, the young miss, have returned! Garen! Get your ass out here! You’re so dead this time!!” The small Dragon Master placed her arms on her hips as she laughed maniacally. Behind her was a sincere and honest looking tall man in black armor holding a two-meter-long hammer in his hand.

“Where’s Garen?! Where’s Garen!! I’ve received intel that he came to this place!!” Asilia shouted.

The waiters serving on that floor of the Black Crow Tower stared at her calmly as the Wizard leader of a class came up and greeted her respectfully.

“Your honorable Miss Dragon Master, Master Garen left just a while ago.”

“Left?! What about Sir Black Crow?” Asilia’s eyes widened.

“He left as well. He headed out to look for some materials.” The female Wizard responded softly.

“That freaking immortal!” Asilia muttered softly. “He left? Fine. Considered myself unlucky! Did that brat Garen mention where he’s going when he left?”

“Uhm… no.” The female Wizard was shocked. How big of a hatred did one require to chase after a person in a residential area?

The female Wizard then stared curiously at the man behind Asilia. She unintentionally spotted the green black tattoo on the man’s body, chills went down her spine as she was stunned.

“Law Enforcer!?”

She was shocked as this Dragon Master had even called out a Law Enforcer, who was a main elite from the Silver Tower! They were the legendary elites who stood at the pinnacle of the Level Nine and they could face against a Level Ten for a long period of time with the top of the line equipment they had on them. Furthermore, the Law Enforcer was able to summon the shapeless and transparent Law Enforcers for assistance. These Law Enforcers were all Level Eight and all of them were the standard terrifyingly powerful killing machines.

“Whatever, he should consider himself very lucky!” Asilia was extremely unhappy since she was not able to obtain any intel on Garen. She then turned around and stomped her way out through the main entrance.

The stupid looking big guy followed her out as well.

Those who had visited the Black Crow Tower were high-level characters that were feared by many. Those people who were Level Seven and above had trained themselves for decades, so it would only be natural for them to have the basic experience and knowledge required. As a Wizard City, it was virtually impossible to encounter a powerful single unit Warrior. However, extremely smart Wizards could be seen all over the streets.

Although some Wizards acted on impulse, there was a common trait that all Wizards would have. It was that they were all not idiots.

The Law Enforcer was one of the violent individuals that should not be messed with the most in Snow City. This was something that could be clearly observed by the people who had visited the Snow City.

Hence there was not a single verbal conflict as Asilia walked out of the area with her man like a God of Plague.

After she had left for ten minutes or so.

Phew…

A sigh of relief could be heard at the very top of the Black Crow Tower.

***********

Spiral Hotel.

“The special envoys from the White Dragon Mountain had been waiting for you for many hours.” The Dragon Lizard from the hotel told Garen softly.

A Level One Sound Transmission Spell was enchanted on a button as the noise was sent directly into Garen’s ears.

He was bringing Annie and Ken along and the moment they reached the hotel, he heard of such news relating to the special envoys.

“Special envoys from the White Dragon Mountain?” Garen instantly knew the objective of the opposing party.

“How many dragons are there?”

“A total of two and they’re all in their human forms.” The Dragon Lizard hostess replied softly.

“In their human forms huh?” Garen was slightly startled as he knew that the big shots had arrived. Those who were able to freely use the Ultimate Transformation Spell were at least a Level Nine Arcane Technique Masters. Furthermore, all of the key members of the White Dragon Mountain were of this level. This meant that they valued Garen a lot in order for them to send two members to see him.

“Be careful Master Garen. The White Dragon Mountain has been unfriendly towards us from the very beginning,” Ken reminded him softly from the side.

“I know,” Garen gently nodded as he signaled Annie with his gaze.

The three of them walked towards the Teleportation Points in their own respective caves. Number plates were erected on dozens of the Teleportation Points and Garen stepped into it as he found his number.

Colorful lights flashed across his eyes for a few moments and everything instantly brightened up instantly after.

He then found himself appearing in the center of a wide beehive-like cave.

The cave was white as it was completely covered with snow. Blue and White Dragons could be seen flying in and out of it and a few human-looking dragons could be seen standing beside the wine cooler at one corner. They were unexpectedly dressed in simple, summer wear.

Garen knew that as long as they were powerhouses without any special physical characteristic, they would require to enhance their temperature energy field in order to sustain in this central cave, which was an environment that was negative ten degrees Celsius cold. These humans who were chatting freely in front of him had no apparent spells activated. It was obvious that they were not human since they were able to stay in this environment naturally.

“The White Dragon Mountain’s Emblem.” Annie’s eyes sharpened as she was able to immediately spot the White Dragon shaped emblem pinned onto the two male and female’s chest. It was a simple outline of the White Dragon’s body and it looked clean and vivid.

Garen took the first move and walked towards them.

The two special envoys from the White Dragon Mountain spotted Garen coming towards them and the people around them started to leave respectfully. These people were friendly allies of the White Dragon Mountain and all of them were powerhouses who could use the Ultimate Transformation Spell. The weakest one was a Level Nine and there was also a Level Ten female lady walking towards Garen with a friendly smile.

Garen smiled back politely in response as well.

Level Nine and Level Ten was a very crucial gap as it would be extremely difficult to go across this wall. There were at least dozens of Level Nine beings that were unable to advance further. However, those who were able to reach Level Ten were basically able to become a member of the Snow City.

Since this woman was not a member, it was obvious that she was a powerhouse from other places. Afterall, it would be normal to assume that the Level Ten members would have their own social circles.

However, the most important crux was not this but a Level Ten would definitely have a powerful force backing them.

After sending this powerhouse off with his gaze, Garen then turned his head around and greeted the two special envoys from the White Dragon Mountain politely.

“I heard that you, two special envoys, have come to seek for me the moment I return. If I recall correctly, our clan and the White Dragon Mountain doesn’t see eye to eye, right…?”

His words were very respectful and straightforward.

The male envoy from White Dragon Mountain frowned for a moment before loosening up.

“That is indeed true. However,” he glanced at the two White Dragons behind Garen.

“The demarcation line for a clan should not be this obvious for a true White Dragon genius. Regardless, we White Dragons are a clan, am I wrong?” He gave a smile to show his friendly gesture.

“Okay, there’s no doubt about it. So what brings the both of you to seek for me?” Garen asked without beating around the bush.

“Obviously, we want you to return to our main clan, the White Dragon Clan.” The female envoy smiled gently as she said happily.

“Return?” Garen was not surprised since his reputation obviously had spread from the Underground City and the Dragon Master’s incident here in Snow City. His reputation would eventually spread towards the White Dragon Mountain. Only an idiot would not recruit a genius White Dragon that appeared out of the blue.

“The main clan has the best Legendary Crystals. Furthermore, we also have a large amount of inheritance, Semi-Divine Weapon, and Divine Weapons left behind by the Ancient Dragons. You may even obtain a personal guidance from Tiamat’s embodiment. As long as you have enough talent, accumulating everything should not be a problem for you.”

“The most crucial thing is that you’ll be under the protection of the White Dragon Mountain as long as you hand over the Pearl of the Temple.” The male special envoy smiled gently as they finally state their visit’s main purpose.

“Do you know? The Dragon Master has already mobilized a Law Enforcer to capture you.” As long as you hand over the Pearl of the Temple, we can protect you under the name of the White Dragon Mountain since even the Silver Tower is not able to ignore the White Dragon Mountain’s social standing.” The female special envoy said rather arrogantly.

Garen and Annie thought that they had heard wrongly as their expressions suggested that they did not hear what they had said clearly.

Did the White Dragon Mountain come all the way here to crack a joke? That was the first thing Garen thought. Did they decide to get their hands on the Pearl of the Temple?

Rumors had it that the White Dragon Mountain had become more and more arrogant and domineering as of late. Garen thought that it was just a rumor but he felt that the rumor was real when he came in contact with them…

“The Pearl of the Temple is an extremely valuable treasure. Even the Demigod would be tempted if they know that a person of a caliber such as you are wielding it. You won’t have enough strength to protect it. It’s better for you to trade it in for the White Dragon Mountain’s friendship instead of leaving it as a seed of misfortunes. You can also be recruited into us along the way to obtain an even greater protection.” The female envoy said in a proud tone.

“Protection?” Garen was on the verge of laughter instead of being angry. “Do you think I, Garen, requires protection from anyone?”

“The Law Enforcer who stands at the pinnacle of Level Nine is able to fight toe to toe against a Level Ten with their equipment. Are you sure you can escape from them?” The male envoy seemed to be threatening him as he spoke.

“Protect me? You guys?” Garen smirked. What kind of joke was that? The Soaring Wing King was situated in the Snow City. Although he was not able to negate the Space-Time Spell that was Level Eight and above, he would definitely act. A Level Twelve Arcanist and the Black Crow Tower that monitored the entire city at every moment was nothing to be messed with.

“The White Dragon Mountain is a second to none sacred heaven to the White Dragons. Countless of White Dragon geniuses had attempted to join us. It seems like you have yet understood the situation.” The male envoy’s tone turned cold. “We’re not here to beg you to join us, we’re letting you in because of the Pearl of the Temple. It’s impossible for you to reach Level Ten without the top secret knowledge!”

“Whether I will be able to breakthrough is not for you to decide. I don’t believe that no White Dragon that did not join the White Dragon Mountain is not able to break through.” Garen said is a disdain tone.

“You’re right. None of them has broken through yet.” The female envoy started scoffing.

“Then I shall be the first one.” Garen was frightened but he still gave her a cold stare. “Let’s go.”

Annie and Ken followed along as they stared with hostile intent at the two envoys.

“How reckless!” Garen could hear the envoys behind him scolding loudly.

He had guessed that the opponent would most likely not spread the news regarding the Pearl of the Temple since this would mean that the amount of ill-intent people would increase if many people knew about it.

He was extremely unhappy with the White Dragon Mountain’s arrogant attitude in this conflict. They dared to treat their same kind with such an attitude since they were the only White Dragon Sacred Heaven who had a White Ancient Dragon among them. No wonder the clan did not see eye to eye with the White Dragon Mountain.

“Did the Dragon Master really summoned a Law Enforcer? If this is true, you might be in some serious trouble, Master Garen.” Annie spoke softly behind Garen.

“The Law Enforcer…” Garen’s gaze turned cold. That Dragon Master was truly a troublemaker since she was able to find a borderline Level Ten powerhouse for assistance. It had now become necessary for him to depart from Snow City as soon as possible.

He needed to return and absorb the Potential Points from the Semi-Divine Weapon as soon as possible.

Boom!

A loud bang reverberated the entire hotel at this moment as the explosion seemed to originate from the main entrance.

“Hahahaha!! Let’s see where you’ll run to this time! Garen, get your ass out of here!!” Asilia’s voice reverberated the entire hotel and the sound waves had even transmitted to the underground.

Chapter 1316: Disturbance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen froze in his tracks.

“It’s the Dragon Master!” Ken said angrily. “Master, what should we do?”

“Let’s run! We don’t stand a chance against them when they have the Law Enforcer on their side!” Annie was feeling scared.

“Don’t panic,” Garen said calmly. “Let’s head out together.”

*********

At the hotel’s entrance, Asilia was laughing like a maniac, her hands akimbo on her waist. She was dressed in a gothic black silk dress, two big black silk bows were tied on her head, which made her looked extremely cute.

“Get your ass out here! I want to take my revenge!” She shouted.

The entire hotel’s guest hall was filled with her buzzing and ear-deafening scream as it reverberated the entire hall. The Dragon Lizards which were responsible to greet the guests huddled in a corner hopelessly. The boss had even arrived at the scene. It was a sturdy big Black Dragon but he could not do anything against Asilia. The people from the Silver Tower would eventually come and make compensation for the losses but…

The surrounding was filled with dragons of different clans. There even was a series of half transparent Eyes of Clairvoyance, which were cast by the Wizards from far away to observe the situation.

The Dragon Urban Area had not been this bustling with noise and excitement for a long time.

The majority of the Wizards hated loud noises and it was the main reason why none of them would scream. However, Asilia was one of those exceptions.

“The Dragon Master is going all out again…” Someone started laughing discreetly. “Let’s see who’s the unlucky one.”

“I wonder if it’s Garen. I heard that there was a talented dragon called Garen who was called the future White Dragon King. I’ve heard that Garen and the Dragon Master had a quarrel on the street a few days ago and she must have come to take her revenge today.”

“I’ve just finished regulating the tranquilizer and I’m here to watch a free drama show.”

“You’re really into this.”

The crowd gradually grew as the hustling discussions became louder as well.

Three White Dragons ultimately appeared in the hotel as Asilia was on the verge of losing her patience.

It was Garen and the other two. Then, a group of dragons appeared as well and the two special envoys from the White Dragon Mountain was among them. They wanted to see, in a bantering manner, how Garen would handle the situation.

The Law Enforcer did not lack an equipment that could deal with the Dragon Clan on him. One could have guessed that he would have used an Advanced Enchanted Equipment as a grenade with the wealth of the Silver Tower at his disposal.

“I’m curious how this kid is going to go against the Law Enforcer,” the male envoy mocked.

“Make sure he doesn’t escape. Be prepared to make your move when he does so as well. We must obtain the Pearl of the Temple at all cost!” The female envoy stressed.

Both of them secretly took out a pair of black and white rings each and tapped on them with their fingers.

Garen and the other two dragons walked out of the Teleportation Point. Since Garen’s body size was still of a Dragon Whelp, he looked extremely miniature and very similar to a Dragon Whelp. This made the other two Adult Dragon Guards looked extremely threatening.

“Garen?” Asilia was confused and shocked at first seeing Garen in the form of a Dragon Whelp.

Garen ignored her and stared intently at the big, stupid looking man behind her.

He was also a being who stood at the pinnacle of the Level Nine that could threaten a Level Ten. This made Garen extremely wary of his unique aura on his body.

This aura could only be found in a person who often experienced battles.

“Capture him!” Asilia shouted.

The big doofus in black armor was activated as if he was a tank as his armors gave off a faint gold halo in an instant. It looked like the gold was glowing at the edge of the black armor. He leaped and went straight towards Garen.

“Critical Realm!” The Law Enforcer shouted as transparent and aqueous-looking Warriors with heavy shields appeared beside him. Their bodies were half transparent and they surrounded Garen from all directions. They stomped the ground with their powerful strength, emitting a thunder-like tremble.

Boom!!

The Law Enforcer used his hammer and slammed it into Garen’s head mercilessly. His murderous killing intent filled up the entire air as it materialized into a blood red aura, tangling around Garen.

Roar!!

Garen roared. His body instantly grew to become the size of two Adult Dragons as he pounced on his opponent.

His scales gave off a blinding, bright white gold luster.

Two powerful beings clashed against each other fiercely.

Boom! Kaboom!!!

A shockwave spread across the room and pushed the Dragon by-standers off their feet.

Garen roared up into the sky as he pushed the Law Enforcer back. He spread his wings and blocked off the Warriors with heavy shields with the sharp claws on his wings. However, there were still a few transparent Warrior hitting his body.

Huh!!…

An immensely powerful Draconic Aura had been dispersed. Similarly, the blood-red halo spread out from the Law Enforcer’s body as well. It was the Massacre Halo unique to them and it had nullified the Draconic Aura.

The hammer was swung to the top from the bottom, clashing directly against Garen’s claw. Gold sparks danced about as colorful energy dispersed. Dozens of negative effects on the heavy hammer that were automatically activated was mostly negated by Garen. There was only one black poison type effect which had stained Garen’s claw, knocking him to take two steps back. Although the opponent was not as strong as him, his attacked contained a powerful knock-back effect.

“Law Enforce Summoning!” The big doofus shouted angrily as he tossed his big hammer up in the air.

Crack!

A stream of white thunder which was as thick as a water bucket struck Garen’s head from above.

At the same time, Garen used his tails to attack the Law Enforcer who had just finished casting his spells by his waist.

Blood spattered as a loud thud could be heard. A huge amount of blood started to flow out from the Law Enforcer’s waist and the thunder had completely engulfed Garen.

“It’s useless.” Garen’s voice came from within the thunder.

“My body is able to negate the effects of even Level Nine Spells.”

The Law Enforcer stood up quietly without saying a word. He seemed to have suffered a grave injury. His waist seemed to have been broken by the tail attack as blood started to seep through the crevice of his armor.

“Although you’re stronger than me,” The Law Enforcer said calmly. “I’ve won.”

In that instant, a warhammer which was ten of meters wide came crashing down from above. It was the hammer that he had tossed up in the air moments ago! It had unexpectedly gigantified by at least ten times as it fell from above.

Garen raised his head up. Although the electricity around him was not able to hurt him, it brought upon a temporarily physical shackling effect. This caused him to not be able to move away from his current position.

His opponent was also a Warrior who had experienced hundreds of battle. Hence, the advantages he could gain from his flaw was very little. The best way to fight against a rough and straightforward fighting style was to clash head-on with them. The opponent would gain the higher ground and oppress him further on if he did not choose to do so.

He looked up at the incoming warhammer and gave off a deep roar as he tried to capture it with one of his claws.

He realized that something was amiss the moment he came in contact with it. The strength coming from the warhammer above him had far surpassed his limits. It was not something a living being was able to pull off. He must have used a special method and spell to increase the power and speed of the warhammer!

The horrifying strength within the warhammer had erupted out from it.

This strength was able to annihilate a small mountain in the External World. However, it was materialized into only a blinding white light here.

As Garen was covered within the blinding light, he rushed in front of Asilia as he tried to grab her with his claw.

Asilia mouth was wide open, preparing to scream as she stared hatefully at Garen.

As she was about to scream at the top of her lungs.

“Enough!!” An authoritative tone came from the sky above.

A spell effect similar to of a commanding spell was cast onto all living beings at the scene. This included Garen and Asilia who was about to scream. All of them were restricted.

Garen gave a sigh of relief. He originally planned to agitate Asilia to unleash her powerful scream to break the deadlock. Since there were many bystanders, the casualties would greatly increase if she were to scream.

This would force the powerhouses who were watching from the sideline to step in.

Garen stood still as he looked at this broken claws. It was the price he paid going against the warhammer. He broke his nails so that he could divert the impact and convert it into vibration, sending it to his feet and finally to the ground. He, who stood at the pinnacle of martial arts, would naturally know of such technique.

Although his opponent had experienced hundreds of battle, he was dwarfed compared to Garen the Demon Lord.

The tremble started to dissipate.

Asilia stared at Garen frustratingly even when she was shackled to the point where her cheeks were as big as a small bun.

Pew! A stream of white light flashed across her body as she and the Law Enforcer was sent away, disappearing from the scene without a trace.

It was only then the shackling effect was slowly deactivated.

Garen tried moving his body and whipped his huge tail around. He was obviously much more intimidating compared to the Dragons around him as he was much bigger in size.

“Finally, that little pesky plague is gone!” He gave off a sigh of relief. The fight was tiring and he was not able to kill them off as well. He could not hide away from them and yet it was in his best interest to not anger them as well. It felt like going to the Blood Wars immediately was the best option for him.

Turning around, he felt a slight pain in his tail. He instantly felt something was off since it was not possible for him to feel any pain with his high defense.

Ah!

A painful cry could be heard from behind him. He turned his head around to see the two envoys from the White Dragon Mountain were holding off a black spike with their hands as their physical movement was restrained by a black aura.

Garen then only realized that the black necklace around his neck had appeared. It was the key to enter the labyrinth given to him by Ann.

As he was stunned.

“It’s the Dragon of Disaster!!!” A sharp voice filled the entire area. It was filled with fear, anger, hatred and killing intent!

A huge thundercloud started to gather up in the sky. The countless purple thundercloud gathered together, forming a huge face as it stared at Garen.

The shackling power appeared once more as it restrained him in all directions.

The sky roared as it shot out an incredible sharp dragon spear. The strength which surpassed even the Level Ten automatically gathered the surrounding air and elements around the spear, forming circles of mysterious patterns on the dragon spear.

“It’s the Snow City’s automated attacking formation!!” A Wizard shouted in shock.

“Run!!”

Garen was dazed. He could only stand absentmindedly on the ground as he was not able to react at all as he was affected by a mysterious Mental Energy Field.

Chapter 1317: Enter 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I object!” Inside a colorful space that was encircled by numerous yellowish-brown spheres at the top of Silver Tower, Soaring Wing King and the other members were gathered in the center here.

If Garen looked over from here, he would discover that the yellowish-brown spheres were actually exactly the same as the various forms of large planes of existences that he saw when he shuttled here initially.

“I object.”

After Soaring Wing King had spoken, another member who was in agreement with him all along now opened his mouth slowly instead.

A different member said, “I retain my opinion.”

A white-robed Elder who wore a monocle with golden threads on one side was standing on the highest point as he held on to an extremely short, white oak staff. It looked like a little hammer when he held it in his hand, and he was using it to hit the palm of his other hand continuously.

“The Automatic Defense Mechanism has been activated. The matters regarding the White Dragon Garen’s location, or should I say, whether or not we’ll hand Garen over to White Dragon Mountain, depends on the respective attitudes of White Dragon Mountain and the White Dragon Clan that are seeking refuge with the other clans in the Deladia Empire. Although your honorable selves may feel that voting appears overly severe or formal, these choices are actually sufficient for us to proceed with casting our votes,” said the old man in a sluggish tone.

“A mere little White Dragon may seem insignificant but the key points are the attitudes of both major forces. Although White Dragon Mountain is stronger than the clan by a large extent, it’s uncertain whether they can become a part of our strength. Hence, I’m in favor of supporting the clan,” said a female member in a red robe softly.

The fifth and final member wore a round hat that was embedded with diamonds. It seemed as though his squinted, smiling face was completely stiff.

“I, however, feel that it’ll be considered as a great reward if White Dragon Mountain will be inclined towards us because of this. Although our Deladia has obtained the support of many of the dragon races, this is merely on the surface. In reality, everyone is well aware that the various colored dragon races are simply using our empire as a place to train their new soldiers. Even though the White Dragon Clan is seeking refuge with us, their forces are way too weak. Their strongest elder is a pseudo-Level Ten individual while White Dragon Mountain is a place where Ancient Dragons exist.”

“However, the arrangements will affect the attitudes of the various major dragon races towards us this time, especially because the present trouble was caused by Little Asilia,” said Soaring Wing King while furrowing his eyebrows. “I maintain my doubts towards Diamond King’s opinion. White Dragon Mountain has been arrogant towards everyone else all this while. It would be an issue if they did not look highly upon our Deladia as well.”

“It seems like Soaring Wing King is in great support of the clan, huh…” Diamond King narrowed his eyes at him. “So, are you brave enough to make a bet with me for once?”

“What are we betting on?” Soaring Wind King was unwilling to display any sign of weakness.

“We’ll use the Blade of Kanbera that you won from me to bet on whether Garen can become the pivotal point that influences the standpoint between White Dragon Mountain and the clan. If White Dragon Mountain agrees to side with us because of this, you’ll give me that Kanbera Divine Weapon; if they don’t, I’ll help you enchant an item instead.”

Soaring Wing King immersed himself in deep thoughts. He was hesitating whether he should persevere and continue his support for Garen.

Diamond King continued, “I’m in favor of handing Garen over to White Dragon Mountain in exchange for their inclination towards us.”

“But what if this angers the clan and they break away from us because of that?” said an opposing member softly.

“Alright, alright. This issue ends here.” Since they had already voted, they would reach a resolution through the number of votes.

The Central President raised his short staff and shook it lightly before the image of Garen in the urban area appeared in the middle of the five people.

“Three votes against handing Garen over to White Dragon Mountain, one neutral vote, and one vote in favor.”

“But how will we deal with the Dragons of Disaster’s Imprint on Garen’s body?” Diamond King continued speaking.

“Dragons of Disaster…” The President shut his eyes and pondered momentarily.

Suddenly, new changes appeared throughout Garen’s image in the center.

**************

The Thunderbolt Spear was suspended above the top of Garen’s head before it descended rapidly. It missed piercing into Garen’s head violently by a hair. However, it seemed as though Garen did not move or resist at all.

A black chain-like necklace appeared around his neck indistinctly. It was the Teleportation Necklace that Ann had given him.

Garen’s entire body was numb while countless hallucinations were filling the space before his eyes simultaneously. These effects were caused by the hypertoxic poison that was spreading throughout his whole body rapidly after his tail was stabbed.

These toxins were extremely potent. His terrifying Vitality was completely paralyzed now.

However, he was unaware that the two White Dragon Mountain Emissaries behind him were gasping in shock because of these obstructions.

“This is a poison that can even cause Semi-Divine Colossal Dragons to fall into a coma while their tongues become numb after being briefly injected! This fellow… actually didn’t faint at all! This is simply unbelievable!!”

“Aside from that, what is this black string necklace-like thing? I can’t find a way to undo it!”

Both the emissaries struggled with all their might. However, it was still impossible for them to break free from the rope on their bodies despite their various peak Level Nine spells and abilities that burst forth continuously.

The black rope extended out from the necklace on Garen’s neck.

“After the Shadow Dragon, where is Ann, one of the three main monarchs of the Dragons of Disaster?!” roared the Matrix Spirit throughout the entire Snow City. A face that was made of thunderbolts appeared indistinctly throughout the storm clouds in the sky. It contained an incomparable amount of fury.

Garen recovered from the poison slowly. His overpowered Vitality that had reached its limits was already immune to the toxins. The poison was so terrifying that it could paralyze him for some time but that was the extent of its abilities.

The strength that was brimming on the top of his head made his whole body trembled slightly. This Matrix Spirit was a terrifying being that had existed for an unknown number of years. Unleashing its powers now, it was almost equivalent to half of Silver Tower Master’s strength.

Silver Tower Master’s strength was the pinnacle of the mortal world. Half of his strength would already be ranked at Level Thirteen at least. Pressure like this made Garen’s breathing somewhat sluggish as well because he was terribly constricted.

The Draconic Aura throughout his entire body was firmly compressed into a ball that pressed up against his skin closely and could not escape at all. His physical fitness was also repressed until it deteriorated to twenty points on average, leaving him with an average of sixty points which weakened him to a huge extent.

“I don’t know what you’re talking about?!” Obviously, he could not reveal Ann’s existence, regardless of whether he was doing it out of kindness or for his own safety. Once he had exposed Ann’s whereabouts, not only would he lose the assurance of his safety, he would be rightfully charged with collaborating with the Dragons of Disaster. There was a possibility that he would be killed as a means of venting pent-up anger.

“Since you have the aura of that monster on your body, I won’t admit that I’m mistaken!” the Matrix Spirit roared angrily.

“Alright, Matrix Spirit. We’ll take care of this matter from here onwards so you can go back and rest,” The President’s voice rang out again.

A tremendous bout of intimidating strength forcibly suppressed the Matrix Spirit before the storm clouds vanished and the Thunderbolt Spear dispersed.

“Since you’re not one of the Dragons of Disaster and may have merely been unaware that Ann was one of the three monarchs of the Dragons of Disaster when you came into contact with her, this is excusable. Nonetheless, you need to be punished for the Dragons of Disaster regardless.” The President’s voice projected downwards from the sky as he said, “Soaring Wing King will have the sovereign rights to handle your punishment.”

There was a whooshing noise and Soaring Wing King appeared before Garen in the sky immediately. He was floating in mid-air, while he looked squarely at Garen.

Garen’s mind stirred frantically. “I humbly apologize for my ignorance and rashness. Perhaps I was completely unaware that she was one of the Dragons of Disaster indeed.” He lowered his head.

“So, are you willing to accept your punishment?” Soaring Wing King cast another glance at him instantly. The sovereign rights to handle this matter were something that he had struggled painstakingly to obtain.

“Yes, I’m willing,” Garen said hurriedly.

It seemed like Ken and Annie who were behind him could not interrupt at all. They were anxious and felt helpless because they were imprisoned by the Energy Field. As Garen was the greatest hope of their clan, they would be completely unable to return and explain to Third Elder if there were any severe tragedies.

“That’s good. Since the Dragons of Disaster had previously swallowed countless living beings, I will send you away to the Abyss to serve your sentence and accept the Blood Wars in order to exempt you from the responsibility of your offenses. If you survive, all of your offenses will be written off.” Not waiting for the other members to speak, Soaring Wing King waved his staff. A red crack that resembled an eye opened up before Garen instantly.

Sent off to the Abyss to serve his sentence?!

When they heard about this punishment, the President was slightly dazed as well. This was not just a form of punishment anymore but a way to covertly send Garen to his death instead!

The Abyssal Blood Wars was not merely a place. He would be forced to battle endlessly there until he died of exhaustion because it was completely impossible for him to escape at all. Those without specialized regenerative abilities would only linger in the Abyss eternally until they assimilated and were contaminated into becoming a part of it.

This punishment was too severe!

Even Diamond King felt the same. At this moment, he felt that it was merciful for him supporting to hand Garen over to White Dragon Mountain. When he looked at the depiction of Soaring Wing King before him, he felt that he needed to reevaluate this person’s character now.

Garen cooperated and plastered an astonished expression on his face as if he could not believe what he had just heard.

Without waiting for him to respond, Soaring Wing King pointed his staff before his Level Twelve Arcanist strength released a massive Energy Field that seized Garen immediately, flinging him into the crack.

Shh!

The scene before his eyes turned into a sea of red instantly as he felt his entire body spinning.

“He’s a member of my White Dragon Mountain! You actually dared to deal with him arbitrarily?!!” The voice of the emissary of White Dragon Mountain could be heard indistinctly behind him. It trailed off further before Garen was soon unable to hear any more.

The blood-red tunnel flew before his eyes. It seemed as though he was in a long portal that resembled a winding, intestinal tract.

After an unknown period of time, a ray of light gradually appeared in front of him.

Boom!

He felt like a fish that had leaped out of the water’s surface. The first things that he saw were the grey sky and the blood-red sun.

There were boundless black plains in his surroundings. The ground of these plains was completely empty except for large, exposed white rocks. He could not see any other creatures.

“The most important thing to do once you’ve arrived in the Abyss is to conceal yourself first,” Garen recalled Soaring Wing King’s advice.

He scanned his surroundings hurriedly and was fortunate not to discover any unusual creatures. He dug his tail into the ground below him quickly and excavated a hole rapidly in a back and forth motion before digging an extremely large pit quickly. Placing himself into the hole before releasing a circle of temporary guards to investigate the area and prevent any creatures from possibly approaching him, only then did Garen let his guard down slightly.

“I’m quite fortunate that no battles occurred to attract the attention of the demons and devils. I can set my mind at ease and absorb the Despair Head first before going any further.”

Without saying another word, he began to set up a protective screen to isolate auras. He had no issues with low-level negative energy protective screens but it was impossible for the auras of Semi-Divine Weapons not to dissipate at all. Therefore, he needed to absorb all of the auras cleanly before they were vaporized.

Inside the pitch-black hole, Garen allowed the Semi-Divine Weapon called the Despair Skull to float in front of him. This skull did not look very different from an average human skull except for the golden flames that were burning in both of its eye sockets, the faint golden symbols in the space between its eyebrows, and the large mouthfuls of purple mist that were surging out of its mouth and nostrils before they were absorbed by Garen in similarly large gulps.

He could clearly see that his Potential Points were rapidly rising at a speed visible to the naked eye.

“According to this speed, I can absorb all of these auras completely within five days.” Garen estimated the duration. If he had not been unexpectedly forced here at an earlier time, he would not have to be so afraid at all.

However, since the incident had already occurred, it would be useless for him to act any more grudgingly. The most important thing was to face reality.

He calmed his heart down before concealing himself inside the cave slowly and absorbing the potential aura.

***************

A colossal creature was crawling leisurely towards Garen from a certain place in the black plains that was several kilometers away from him.

This enormous beast had the upper body of a Colossal Dragon and the lower half of a spider’s body. Yellow flames would burn across its back incessantly. It also had a pair of perpendicular gold-yellow pupils in its eyes that were incomparably fierce.

Numerous yellow insects that resembled ground beetles encircled the surroundings of this enormous beast. Several large colonies of these insects crawled up and down the body of the enormous beast as if they were cleaning its body.

“There’s a strange aura… near me…” (Abyssal)

The enormous beast opened its mouth to speak suddenly.

“It’s a dragon’s aura…” It used its nose to sniff. It moved the lower half of its gigantic body. Its body was over ten meters long and more than eight meters tall at least. Aside from its back, everywhere else was covered in a soil armor that resembled thick layers of scales.

“Should we take a look?” The numerous beetles converged beside it and condensed into a humanoid state that resembled a woman.

“No, there’s no need. Even if it’s a Colossal Dragon, it can’t escape the Ice Ant Tide that will engulf it in the evening.” The enormous beast was crawling again.

“If it can endure the Ice Ant Tide, only then it qualifies for me to go and look at it personally.”

It had established the rules.

Chapter 1318: Enter 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The sun dimmed gradually before it descended below the horizon.

Icy auras gradually filled the air as well.

On the black plains, a long stretch of white “tides” surged out from the furthest point, sweeping across while charging toward the area at which Garen and the enormous beast were located.

Strangely, it spread open and uncoiled automatically in the area where the enormous beast was located. It continued moving forward as if it did not see the beast at all before it approached Garen’s position quickly.

Inside the cave, Garen could faintly detect the sound of certain movements. However, when the defenses that had been set up to stand guard outside did not have any responses, he suppressed the anxiety in his mind and continued absorbing the auras.

Hiss…

Suddenly, the faint sound of an insect that was tearing and biting something echoed into the cave from the outside.

Beep…

The invisible temporary defenses let out a sharp alert immediately.

Garen’s heart trembled before he paused his absorption frantically and kept his Semi-Divine Weapon back into his Space Ring.

He turned around and looked at the entrance of the cave where seemingly countless, tiny, densely-packed white ants had surged inside there at an unknown time.

The ant colony that poured in was accompanied by a terrifyingly-low temperature that was as cold as negative seventy to eighty degrees, rushing inside frantically.

“An Ice Ant Tide?” Garen was obviously aware of this natural disaster. Although every single one of these Ice Ants looked tiny and were only the size of a human palm, they were genuine Level Two creatures. Their bodies were feeble, but their teeth were invincible and even dragon scales for no match for the tough bones that they could gnaw.

When he saw that so many of these Ice Ants were charging towards him, he sighed in relief instead. He would have been slightly worried if they were Fire Ants. However, since they were Ice Ants, and since he was, fortunately, an ice-type Colossal Dragon, it would be easier to handle them in this aspect.

He sprayed out a mouthful of Dragon Breath. Garen’s current Dragon Breath already possessed the power and momentum of an Adult Colossal Dragon. His Frost Aura instantly made the Ice Ants livelier. Aside from their hard teeth, their most threatening ability was actually their naturally intense low temperature. Low temperatures of negative seventy to eighty degrees would accompany them as they moved and advance endlessly. Other than actual ice-type creatures, most other creatures could not handle these effects at all. Moreover, these low temperatures also harbored certain types of ice-type toxins. However, Garen’s Vitality was immune to it. Nonetheless, if another Peak Level Nine Wizard of the same level was here instead of him, the situation would probably be very troublesome, because when their magic spells would inevitably be exhausted; they would truly only be at the creatures’ mercy when the ice-type toxins entered their body. Fortunately, Garen’s physique was stronger and unlike theirs.

The movements of these large colonies of Ice Ants were slowed down when they were blown by Garen’s Dragon Breath. When they increased their icy auras simultaneously, this made Garen feel as if the creatures on the other side were of a slightly similar species to himself.

The main characteristic of this Ice Ant Tide was that they would only gnaw at creatures that did not have low temperatures. Since the blood of White Dragons was at temperatures of zero degrees and below, they were naturally a typical example of low-temperature creatures.

Therefore, the seas of Ice Ants that poured in were pushed out easily.

It was merely a false alarm.

Garen exhaled but the feeling of unremovable chills that kept springing up remained in his mind. He scanned his surroundings, yet he was still unable to find any abnormalities.

He sighed in relief and was about to continue his absorption before a black shadow of a human-shaped smoke passed through directly in front of him suddenly.

Garen was about to hide but was unable to do it in time. However, he noticed immediately that the other party merely passed through his body directly. It seemed as though it was not substantial at all.

He felt his body weakening slightly at the same time.

Shh…

The humanoid creature condensed behind him and floated in the darkness of the cave. It was basically a shroud of black smoke that had formed into a human silhouette. He could not see its face at all, only its blurry limbs.

“Void Shadow?” Garen was slightly shocked before he said, “Isn’t this a creature from the Undead World?”

Creatures like Void Shadows were very troublesome. It was disastrous every time they appeared on the surface of the Main Substance World.

They were immune to the innate laws of things and even had a fifty percent dodging rate towards enchantments and spell attacks. Moreover, they would weaken the powers of the other party every time they touched other creatures.

The debilitation of their abilities was everlasting and extremely despicable. Unless you could kill the Void Shadow that had absorbed your powers, you would eternally lose the part of your strength that they had absorbed.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows faintly while looking at the Void Shadow before him. The most troublesome aspect of Void Shadows was not this, but the fact that most of them usually appeared in groups.

Every time they killed a creature, they would develop it as a part of themselves to form the next Void Shadow. Thus, these Void Shadows would appear in groups under normal circumstances. As a peak powerhouse in the aspect of physical attacks, Garen was the most annoyed at creatures like these that were immune to these types of physical attacks.

His Spellcrafting strength was only at Level Five, and he did not have any Enchanted Equipment either.

Garen had just thought of this before more than ten densely-packed Void Shadows appeared inside the cave. His scalp tingled immediately.

“This is troublesome…”

The previous Void Shadow had taken away half of his strength when it pounced on him once. If so many Void Shadows were to set on him together, wouldn’t his strength which exceeded eighty points vanish completely within a few moments?

He felt as if his Vitality was strong while he was still standing on the Main Substance Plane previously. Aside from being immune to spells, he was also not very concerned with Spellcrafting and Arcane Techniques as he felt that there were no forces besides Level Eight Space-Time Spells that could challenge him. However, after he had experienced using spells in Snow City to strengthen his physical attacks such as Warhammer, and witnessed the supernatural powers that were brought on by the Void Shadows now, did he understand that purely walking on the path of physics was not the true path of this world.

“No wonder peak level Warriors also require the assistance of Enchanted Equipment and Divine Weapons.”

While he was surrounded by a group of Void Shadows, Garen’s mind stirred rapidly as he thought of a way to escape.

These were the effects of being restrained. A Level Eight Great Wizard here would have an easier time handling this than him. Thus, Garen was having a hard time now.

Whoosh!

More than ten Void Shadows pounced on him suddenly. Garen could not dodge them in this narrow space in time. Moreover, despite his great speed, the Void Shadows possessed pretty good speed as well. The distance between them was closed in a moment. These Void Shadows were clearly high-level characters.

The leading Void Shadow appeared first. It released a loud and sharp chirping noise that instructed the others to pounce over.

Garen opened his mouth and spat out a large mouthful of Dragon Breath that struck two Void Shadows precisely. Although his Dragon Breath was not a harmful spell, it was still considered harmful towards supernatural powers; it had certain effects towards Void Shadows.

The effects of the deceleration that was caused by the cold suddenly appeared throughout the bodies of both of the Void Shadows that were sprayed, but none of them were harmed. Since they were Undead Creatures, the cold could only decrease their speeds, not kill them.

Garen moved toward the right side suddenly. While he was surrounded by more than ten Void Shadows, his body shrunk suddenly. His physique decreased into the size of an extremely tiny Dragon Whelp before he barely rushed out of a crack in the encirclement.

It was pointless to strictly view these types of Advanced Undead according to their levels and divisions. They could only be destroyed using focused tactics. Thus, if the tactics were not focused, even first-rate Warriors would only be worn down to death by them while they were still alive.

Garen dodged inside the cave from left to right. Every time, he was only able to evade the Void Shadows’ attacks by a hair’s breadth. This made the leading Void Shadow abnormally irritated.

Chirp chirp chirp chirp!

It began yelling again.

The movements of all the other Void Shadows became more speedy immediately.

Garen timed this opportunity properly and rushed out of the cave at once before reaching the ground.

He remembered that his Semi-Divine Weapon, Despair Head, probably possessed supplementary soul attributes. Perhaps it would be effective towards the Undead.

When he thought of this, he took the Despair Head out of his Space Ring suddenly and grasped it in his claw before he targeted a Void Shadow and approached it.

The Despair Head looked like a normal white human skull that seemed unassuming.

Moreover, when Garen extended his arms and legs after exiting, his 80-point speed was instantly given full control as well. Hence, when he extended his claws, he instantly struck the Void Shadow that pounced towards him at the same time.

Chirp!

A pained cry rang out. This Void Shadow released a miserable howl before it retreated and returned frantically as if it was burned.

“Was that effective?!” Garen’s heart was delighted.

He continued to follow the same pattern. His speed had peaked at 80-points while his body had naturally become agiler once it shrunk. The Void Shadows were thrown and spun around by him. He had only encountered them a few times before five Void Shadows were struck by his Despair Head. By looking at their physiques, it was obvious that they had lost a lot of the black smoke that made up their bodies.

The leading Void Shadow was slightly fearful now. It began to make chirping noises as if it wanted to retreat.

However, Garen made a surprising discovery; he noticed that the potential aura of his Despair Head had actually increased slightly again.

Although they were merely traces of increments, his subtle responses were extremely accurate in this aspect. Moreover, since he was holding it in his own hands all this while, he could feel the differences throughout his Semi-Divine Weapon in the first instance.

“Was I strengthened by absorbing the soul auras of these Undead creatures?” An assumption formed in Garen’s mind.

He tried doing it a few more times while pursuing the Void Shadow that had already started to flee while continuing to press down against it and strike it.

He continued to hit another Void Shadow five times before this fellow finally collapsed with a thud. It actually exploded into pieces immediately, turning into a puff of black smoke that dispersed slowly before it died completely.

Garen could clearly feel that the potential aura of the Despair Head had strengthened once again. His heart was extremely delighted. If this method was feasible, he could simply use the Despair Head to hunt souls and would not have to follow the rules of the Blood Wars that would only grant him souls according to the battles that he had won. Instead, he could freely hunt souls and turn them into potential aura!

Bang!

Another Void Shadow exploded and scattered when it was violently smashed by Garen. After that, Garen instantly felt that his strength which was previously sucked away had not returned. Meanwhile, the potential aura of the Despair Skull had increased slightly. It had probably undergone an increment of five or six points in comparison to the time when he had just brought it out earlier. This was not a minor increment. He had smashed two Void Shadows into pieces while the remaining ones dispersed and fled. The rewards that he had gained this time were already enough to satisfy Garen greatly.

“This is equivalent to more than half a month’s worth of my natural earnings, haha!” Garen turned around and returned to his cave happily. He noticed that the sharp points had become longer and were more pointy. Hence, their growth speed had obviously started to increase. He believed that he could evolve into another state soon and continue increasing his attributes.

“I’ve heard that evolved states can randomly obtain a type of natural ability from the Original Energy Sea. Some obtain elemental abilities while others get supernatural abilities. They weren’t all beneficial, and there were detrimental ones as well. However, great advantages could also be obtained from the bad ones as long as they’re used properly.”

Garen was very hopeful toward the natural abilities that he would gain through his evolved state.

Legitimate White Dragons would naturally gain natural abilities such as spells like Ice Mirror Art, Frost Swallowing, and Spewing (in a large area) during adulthood. However, he was different as he had already accomplished certain stages during his childhood that none of the other White Dragons had achieved since the beginning.

Chapter 1319: Cooperate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Time flew as the days passed…

A week had passed in the blink of an eye while Garen was hiding in the cave.

He had never imagined that the potential aura of the Despair Head would actually require a longer absorption time than anticipated. Nonetheless, he managed to fully absorb more than two thousand points of its potential aura as he had expected.

This was an extremely large number.

Moreover, the evolution of his body had reached a crucial moment. The forces of his body’s aura became unusually unstable.

He curled his body up inside the cave. His entire dragon’s body was wrapped in a thick Ice Armor which made him resemble a perfect, snowy-white ice sculpture that did not move at all.

Pfoo…

A gust of white mist sprayed out of his nostrils slowly after a long time.

Bang…

Bang… Bang… Bang…

A series of heavy footsteps echoed from afar gradually.

The walls inside the cave started to tremble slightly, as the faint, powdery soil fell from the cave walls.

The sound of the footsteps moving toward the entrance outside the cave slowed down before stopping after that.

“Outsider…” A deep Abyssal voice echoed from the outside. “Are you not planning to come out and meet me?”

Garen opened his eyes slowly. Hints of grey-black membranes were already covering his eyes now, as though an additional layer of something was stuck to the surface of his eyeballs.

An unknown powerful being had come to visit him during this important evolution period now. It was extremely obvious that the other party had purposely chosen this time to arrive, right when he was in a vulnerable state. He was clearly harboring evil intentions.

“Who?” he opened his mouth and asked calmly.

“I was merely teleported here randomly. Please forgive me if I’ve offended you. I’ll leave this place quickly…”

The outside of the cave was silent for some time as if he was determining and considering whether to make a move or not.

Garen waited for a confirmation from the other side as well. Whether he was a friend or a foe depended on the other party’s intentions. His own attitude was revealed in its entirety already.

After some time had passed, more noises echoed into the cave from the outside again.

“I’m Kratos, the master of this domain. Ignorant dragon, it would be best if you left my territory immediately.”

“Forgive me, but I’m currently undergoing an important period,” Garen answered indifferently.

“That’s truly regrettable…” The outside of the cave turned silent instantly.

Boom!!

There was a thunderous noise before a gigantic dragon head that was burning with flames entered forcefully, trying to use its mouth to bite Garen’s body.

The size of this dragon’s head was almost similar to Garen’s entire physical state when he was enlarged. It was also extraordinarily ferocious. Intense flames poured into the cave and melted the frost that was covering it before large amounts of white mist rose.

Garen’s entire body turned sideways while his tail whipped over violently.

His tail coincidentally collided against the tip of the nose of the other dragon’s head.

Bang!!

After a dull noise rang out, the dragon’s head and Garen were apparently fine. Both of them merely fell backward because of the reacting force. They continued charging toward each other again.

“Level Nine!” Garen’s heart trembled. For some reason, he would always encounter such powerful opponents wherever he went.

When he collided against the enormous beast the second time, he took the opportunity to push himself upward. He sprang his entire body out of the cave and broke through the surface of the ground before flying into mid-air.

The sky was currently blood-red while it seemed like the surroundings of the sun were tied with a black chain; the earth was completely grey-black.

Garen could only see a full view of the entire enormous beast clearly when he flew up.

This was truly a colossal monster with the upper body of a dragon and a lower half of a spider. Intense red flames were even burning on the back of this enormous beast, resembling an abnormally-magnificent mane.

The enormous beast raised his head before a ball of orange light lit up in his mouth when he saw Garen flying.

Shh!

An intense ray of red light rushed toward Garen immediately.

A popping noise could be heard when the red light beam struck his scales, yet only a faint white dot was left behind. Level Nine immunity against spells was not a joke.

Garen was completely unconcerned because his body had expanded back into its full state and he had instantly become a few times more muscular. Next, he flew up high before rushing downward ferociously.

Whizz.

His intense dive created ear-piercing, whistling noises while his tail whipped up dense white blasts.

On the ground below, numerous imposing Rock Giants stood up on the ground. They followed the enormous beast’s will and charged toward Garen to seize him.

The enormous beast moved speedily on its eight limbs while an abundance of intense, fiery whips shot out from its back. More than ten red whips covered the sky and earth while moving toward Garen to bind him.

Garen dodged from left to right. He went as far as to pass through the crack before colliding brutally against the enormous beast again.

A layer of multicolored light exploded in front of the enormous beast’s body suddenly, blinding Garen’s vision. This was a high-level, multicolored spurt. Aside from causing blindness, it also had vertigo-like effects. However, Garen was naturally immune to these effects that caused dizziness because they were considered as Spellcrafting effects.

He charged forward directly without the slightest worry.

Boom!

It seemed as though he had crashed against the enormous beast’s head through the rainbow light.

Both of these gigantic creatures rolled around on the ground before flying far away. They left a deep scratch in the ground.

Garen’s strength was apparently much stronger than that of this enormous beast. He did not release it in the cave previously. However, now that they were clashing together fully outside, the difference between the both of them could be seen clearly.

The enormous beast was clearly a monster that was inclined toward its own familial laws. It had not adapted t to facing a monster like Garen that purely conformed to the innate laws of things.

“Stop! Stop this!” He roared. “We don’t have to engage in this meaningless killing!”

Garen stopped in a timely manner after whipping his tail brutally against the waist of the enormous beast one last time. The enormous beast fell on the ground and rolled there a few times, causing earth-shattering, crashing noises and sending dust flying.

“What else did you want to say?” He looked at the other party in an engrossed manner.

“You… You have such powerful strength. You’ll definitely achieve great successes in the Blood Wars! As long as I create a Sawtooth Shield for you, you’ll surely become a slaughterhouse on the battlefield!” The enormous beast named Kratos explained loudly. “I’m a master of Alchemy and weaponsmithing so I can help you forge these items! What would you say about helping me in return?!”

This enormous beast had currently broken one of its spider legs. Its body was filled with injuries and it faintly looked like it was in a sorry state. However, it came prepared with healing spells that were speedily treating its wounds now.

“Help me forge a weapon and shield?” This thought had entered Garen’s mind long ago, but he had never anticipated to actually encounter a monstrous beast here that knew how to forge weapons and equipment. He glanced at the intense flames on his opponent’s back while his mind could not help but be slightly hesitant.

When he noticed faintly that Garen was slightly suspicious, Kratos spoke hurriedly.

“I have a pretty good relationship with one of the Vice Chiefs of the Wanku Fortress’ army because I’ve always been their head ironsmith. You may not be confident in my combat abilities but I’m definitely a specialist in the equipment-forging aspect! I’d also recommend you to go to the Wanku Fortress to participate in the Blood Wars.”

“The Wanku Fortress?”

“Yes, it’s a great fortress nearby. You don’t have to worry about this because their Chief of Army is the Level Thirteen elder demon named Eyeless Nada. This place will be organizing a major decisive battle during this period of time. You can take a look around and ask the other creatures if you don’t believe me,” said Kratos loudly.

Garen felt that his back was becoming itchier and harder to endure. His mood was also affected, and that made him very uncomfortable.

“I’ll take a look around before we go any further.” Once he had finished speaking, he flapped his wings immediately and flew into the distance before the enormous beast could answer.

After coming to the Abyss, he had spent the last few days withdrawing himself in the cave all along. He had yet to really tour the sights here.

While flying at high-speed, Garen quickly left the cave area in which he was initially located and entered a dark green forest and swamp.

He could vaguely see several old women with long, cascading green hair and long robes who were floating around above the swamp. These were Demon-Hags who went around scamming tourists, mercenaries, and even demons. Obviously, if your strength was great enough, they would simultaneously be the most cunning businesspeople who mainly specialized in selling information, intelligence, and souls.

When the Demon-Hags appeared, several little demons that were dragging black scorpion tails could be vaguely seen haunting the surroundings as well. Signs of living creatures had increased.

Garen continued flying towards the depths of the swamp forest. He could slowly see some gigantic, light green, sludge-type monsters. These monsters that were in a liquid state had bodies that were entirely green and sticky. They hid in the swamp and would suddenly appear to grab the tourists, dragging them into their bellies while they were still alive before digesting them.

However, the sludge monsters here did not seem to show any indication of hiding at all. Web-like blood vessels glistened throughout their green bodies. These blood vessels appeared to be giving off white light faintly, making them extremely eye-catching.

He saw a gigantic hundred-meter wide sludge monster talking to several Centaur Warriors now.

“This is the trader Gusca’s domain. Dragon race outsider, you are not permitted to fly here.” Suddenly, a voice echoed from below. Immediately, Garen could feel an intense strength suppressing him toward the swamp below, forcing him to descend there.

He did not resist but landed there instead. He stood on a part of the swamp that seemed steadier before freezing ice into a flat area below his feet immediately so that he could stand there.

“White Dragon? …Is he from White Dragon Mountain?”

“Probably not. He doesn’t have the badge of White Dragon Mountain on his body.”

“This is a valuable moving treasure chest… If we could kill one Colossal Dragon…” the voice trailed off.

Garen’s terrorizing eyes scanned the area.

That noise rang out again.

“Using force and fighting at close quarters are prohibited here. Only fair trading is allowed.”

“Traders?” Garen sneered several times. There were a few scattered tourists in his surroundings who were currently standing around and making deals with the Demon-Hags. Among them were humans, Orcs, and a rarely seen Earth Elemental.

There were so many traders in such a small area. One could well imagine that this domain seemed to be very famous here.

Garen walked around in the swamp while his heavy footsteps made banging noises wherever he stomped. He felt somewhat eye-catching and quickly shrunk his body into the size of a Dragon Whelp before flying around slowly.

These actions seemed very effective because a Demon-Hag, who was holding a walking stick, floated in front of him quickly.

“Outsider, is there any way that I can be of service to you?” Her shrill voice made people’s scalps tingle and was enough to scare little children and make them cry on their own.

“I want to purchase a sufficient number of souls. Do you have them?” Garen grinned but managed to smile warmly.

“Souls?” cackled the Demon-Hag sharply. “This will depend on the grade of the souls you desire… If they’re low-grade souls, I can give you more than ten thousand of them. However, if you’re looking for the high-grade souls that are Level Five and above, I only have a few in my hands…”

“I can really buy them?” Garen was slightly shocked. “What if I want the souls of Level Ten powerhouses?”

The Demon-Hag’s shrill laughter stopped abruptly.

“This… If you can give me a reasonable price that arouses the desire of the honorable Chief of Army, otherwise it would be impossible… You’re also aware that we Demon-Hags work for the Fortress Master in reality…”

Garen pondered for a while and responded with some other rare materials that he needed for his Wizard Tower. He had never expected that all four of them would actually be available here.

“What do you use as the trading currency here?”

“Currency? No, no, no… We don’t have such things here. We merely use soul-cocoons as the standard to measure values occasionally,” explained the Demon-Hag.

“How about it? I have the best enslaved souls, architects, craftsmen, and alchemists over here to help you establish a domain. I also have beautiful and cute elf slaves, and even little princesses with the bloodline of the Elf King, hee hee hee…”

Chapter 1320: Cooperate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I won’t be needing them for now,” Garen declined.

Garen got rid of these Demon-Hags who babbled on endlessly before flying toward the deeper parts of the swamp.

The ground of the swamp soon turned red gradually before a lofty black palace appeared in the distance. Numerous black War Puppets that were more than ten meters tall were patrolling the enclosing walls around the palace. These humanoid puppets with ox horns possessed extremely powerful shock forces. Since they were sturdy and durable, they were one of the best items that could be refined for guarding. One normal soul was all that was required to drive it for numerous years, making them extremely worthwhile.

Garen was obstructed by the War Puppets who refused to let him proceed any further. The level of the master here was unknown, and it was possible for various types of monsters to appear in the Abyss. There were no living creatures who dared to clash with an enemy for no reason. Hence, Garen did not force his way forward but withdrew and left instead.

He walked along another side before leaving this green swamp quickly.

However, he soon felt as if someone was watching him. After he had left the swamp, several little human silhouettes trailed him faintly.

Garen remained in his Dragon Whelp form. This physique looked extremely delicate and weak. Since it seemed like he was only at Level Four, it was not surprising that close-minded people were staring at him.

He found a hillock and flew there before descending in the shadows behind it. He turned around and waited for the pursuers behind him.

Shuffle shuffle…

Several faint noises could be heard before three translucent human silhouettes that were slightly distorted appeared at the top of the hillock. They were looking downward.

“Have we actually been discovered?” One of the people asked in a surprised tone.

Since they were already discovered, they did not bother to continue hiding. The Translucent Spell on their bodies vanished immediately. Three figures who were dressed in a silver armor were revealed. They were actually three knights.

A faint red Spirit Light was twinkling below their bodies. This faint red light was constantly centered around them. They radiated circles of blinding rays outward, representing their statuses as Blasphemy Knights.

The Blasphemy Knights were sentenced to be knights of the blasphemers by the Church of the Gods for various reasons. Most of them had entered the Abyss through special channels. This was the only way to prevent their lives and souls from being captured by the Gods and tortured forever.

After all, the Gods would punish the blasphemers extremely severely. Nonetheless, although the Abyss was a cruel place, it was still an opportunity for them to live.

Two of these three Blasphemy Knights were women while one of them was a man. They were not old and the armors that they wore on their bodies seemed to be of the same style.

“I want the skin and eyes of this Dragon Whelp, but you can divide the rest among yourselves,” said one of the female knights directly.

“I could tell that its eyes seemed strange with one look. It may be some type of treasure. It wouldn’t be good for us to divide everything up so early on, right?” said the other female knight unhappily.

“The way I see it, it wouldn’t be too late to discuss this again after getting rid of our opponent…” It seemed like the sole male knight had already detected that Garen was aware that something was amiss. His gaze was glaring closely at Garen.

“Were you three the only ones that followed?” Garen glanced behind himself unhappily. He focused carefully and realized that these three idiots had really trailed him. It looked like most of the other traders were much smarter in comparison…

He considered these three knights carefully. By looking at the forces of their Spirit Light, he could tell that they were at Level Four. Were these three Level Four individuals actually daring enough to hunt a Level Four Dragon Whelp in the Abyss? Perhaps they had special hidden moves. Was it possible that they were unaware that the creatures in the Abyss that looked weak were the one you should provoke the least?

In a place like the Abyss, everyone was afraid that their strength was not powerful enough to be displayed fully. Nonetheless, they had to exhibit their strength to prevent themselves from being bullied or oppressed. Only the most powerful beings would intentionally show signs of weakness to purposely entice the hunters and prey on them instead… Meanwhile, it was possible that true weaklings did exist among the local demonic creatures. However, none of the outsiders were abnormally weak.

“Go!”

The male knight drew his Greatsword first. The blade was dyed with a faint red Spirit Light, while his Level Four forces increased to Level Five immediately. By looking at the taut muscles throughout his entire body that was now enlarged, it appeared that he had used certain temporary means of strengthening his powers.

Ahh!

He charged towards Garen fiercely and swung his sword!

Bang!

His Level Five Greatsword struck Garen’s head violently. Garen remained on his initial spot and did not move at all. There was not even a hint of white that remained on his scales.

However, a large crack had burst throughout the Greatsword.

The male knight’s face turned pale instantly. Garen had initially assumed that he would discard his Greatsword before turning around and running away. However, an unwavering look appeared on his face instead as he roared and said, “Rena, Irene! Run quickly!”

However, he did not retreat. Instead, he moved forward, continuing to charge toward Garen without surrendering.

The two female knights behind him reacted immediately when they were aware of the situation that had occurred. One of them ran off at once while the other was momentarily dazed. Next, she actually drew her sword and charged towards Garen. She clearly wanted to save her companion.

“Interesting.” Garen extended his claws and gently blocked the cleaving motion of the Greatsword. He exerted a small amount of strength before the force throughout the male knight’s entire body was instantly exhausted when he was shaken by an intense vibration. He fell on the side after being paralyzed.

“I’ll fight you to the end!” The eyes of the female knight that charged forward were red now. She assumed that her companion had died and proceeded to use full force to explode a ray of red light towards Garen. She had apparently managed to leap to a Level Six force instantly!

As expected, those who were able to teleport themselves here from other planes were not weaklings… Garen sighed mentally. It was not a big deal for the dragon race to randomly encounter Level Five or Level Six powerhouses. However, among the humans, these powerhouses were a level that could only appear once in several thousand people.

He extended his claws and gently blocked the Greatsword that the female knight was slicing toward him. However, Garen instantly felt that something was amiss because the Spirit Light of the female knight’s Greatsword had actually transformed into countless tiny red vines that tangled themselves around his claws firmly. Although the binding strength was negligible to him, this twining would be sufficient to cause most Level Five and Level Six powerhouses to tremble slightly. If their reactions were one beat slower, it was likely that this delay would mean the difference between life and death.

“How loyal. I was planning to devour you initially, but when I look at it now, perhaps you may be slightly useful.” Garen released a tremor in passing and transmitted it to settle the trouble with this female knight by numbing her and causing her to collapse on the ground limply.

The Secret Technique called Quake that he had transferred to himself was simply always successful in countering the close-combat and material-type Warriors here. Extremely fine skills like these could almost be considered as godly techniques to the people here.

Thus, although the effects of Garen’s other Secret Techniques could not be used anymore, he was still able to peak among the material Warriors because of this skill and his own powerful characteristics.

“Kill me, then!” The female knight was still strong-willed.

“Who said you could come over, Irene?!” said the male knight furiously. “Even Rena knew how to escape, yet you returned to save me despite having the chance to flee! Why didn’t you escape?”

“If you’re going to die, we’ll die together!” the female knight answered stubbornly.

The male knight was angered to the point where he was speechless.

Garen flapped his wings and flew in the direction of the female knight who had escaped earlier. Less than a moment had passed before he saw that woman’s fleeing shadow.

She had covered her entire body in disgustingly smelly swamp sludge. It was almost impossible to distinguish the style of the armor that she wore on her body. Her actions and movements were also slightly hurried. When she blended in with the scattered humanoid creatures in her surroundings, it was truly difficult to find her.

However, Garen had never judged people based on their appearances, but by detecting their soul’s aura instead.

When he pinpointed this woman, he dived downward and transmitted a tremor. He eliminated all of her resistances immediately before carrying her back easily.

Since his strength was already at 80 points, as long as his opponent’s vitality was not resilient enough and had yet to achieve 50 points or more, his Quake skill would always be successful and could cause them to fall with a single touch.

When he flew back to his original position, Garen was shocked to discover that there were two Demon-Hags who were actually sneakily collecting the two captive prisoner’s souls that had fallen weak on the ground. The souls of those two Blasphemy Knights were being extracted from their bodies quickly as half of them were already drawn out.

“You dare touch my spoils of war? You’re really asking to die!” Garen’s mind was upset. He discarded the female knight in his claws and rushed directly towards the Demon-Hags instead.

“Block him!” screamed one of the Demon-Hags.

A black, gigantic beetle that was seven to eight meters tall with sharp pincers moved towards Garen, attempting to pinch him.

Garen moved his claws from left to right in a ripping motion before an enormous force that was accompanied by vibrations transferred directly into the beetle’s body. This bastard turned weak immediately, making it obvious that his vitality was lower than fifty points.

Its head was instantly smashed by Garen’s claw. Its red and green brain matter oozed out at once after the collision, and it lay on the floor, unmoving.

Neither of the two Demon-Hags had expected that the battle would end so soon. They were instantly scared to the point where their souls had almost left their bodies. They turned on their heels and ran while abandoning the souls they were collecting earlier.

However, Garen’s 80-point speed allowed him to catch up to them instantly. He caught each of them in one claw as if he was grabbing balloons that punctured immediately. Both of the Demon-Hags flattened out with a whoosh and turned into two pieces of green human skin that fell on the ground. They were collected by Garen before he turned around and went back.

The green poison that leaked out tried to attach itself to Garen’s body. However, it was completely ineffective as it could only hold on for two seconds before Garen’s powerful vitality became immune to it.

The three Blasphemy Knights were thrown together by Garen. He used a few random vines that he had found on the ground to bind the trio together before grabbing them with one claw. Garen was planning to look for some subordinates to help him gather information because working on his own was truly too slow-paced. As he did not have an Ultimate Transformation Spell yet, his movements in his dragon race physique were too conspicuous. Frankly, it was better for him to find some substitutes.

While clutching these three Blasphemy Knights, Garen flew and briefly asked along the way in passing if the situation that the Fiery Beast was talking about was true. Indeed, he was not lying.

Garen returned to the location of his original cave quickly. If everything that the beast said was true, the matters regarding the forging of his weapons and equipment really rested on his shoulders.

He would probably need to add more than two thousand potential points into his Void Original Opus.

While flying along the way, he began adding his potential points there. It had only increased to 14% after he had added over 140 points previously. This time, he added 500 points in one go before seeing that his Void Original Opus had suddenly surged to a large extent.

It leaped directly to 64% from 14%. He could clearly feel that changes had occurred throughout his body. They were several subtle but extremely thorough changes. However, he did not have the chance to investigate it for now.

He threw the three Blasphemy Knights into his own cave first before Garen went to look for the Fiery Beast whose aura was not far from there. He released a small-scale barrier from Negative Energy Spells. These three fellows were already fully exhausted by him while their muscles and bones were injured from the quakes. Since they were too tired to move, he did not have to worry about them escaping.

“What do you say?”

The enormous beast raised its head and looked at Garen who was flying over while lying on its own building ruins.

“Have you decided to let me help you forge your weapons and equipment?”

“What are your conditions?” Garen knew that nothing ever came for free.

“I want you to provide me with High-quality Souls. Don’t reject me frantically because I can sense the special Soul Divine Weapon that you have. I’ve recently been researching a Matrix that allows me to attempt to condense High-quality Souls. However, I’m lacking a Soul Divine Weapon. If the both of us cooperate, perhaps we can obtain even greater benefits!”

The enormous beast spoke sincerely. He was initially planning to snatch it forcefully, but it was unfortunate that he could not defeat his opponent…

“High-quality Soul…” Garen was aroused. If the quality of a soul was too low, it would be ineffective for him to absorb it as potential points anyway. This was similar to his current situation whereby if he absorbed the soul of a normal person to be used as his potential point aura, it would probably be ineffective. It would be useless even if he tried to absorb it anymore. Only the souls that were Level Three or above and had a certain density to produce qualitative changes were the ones that could provide him with some potential points to be absorbed.

Chapter 1321: Evolution 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

If he had a High-quality Soul, perhaps he could gather a large amount of low leveled souls to obtain potential points. Moreover, he could gain the greatest benefits on a battlefield like this.

Once his train of thought had cleared up, Garen discussed everything in detail with the enormous beast Kratos, such as the exact particulars and theories of the Matrix. Both of them were fellows who did not adhere to the principles of good and evil. Finally, Garen became clearly aware of the origins of the enormous beast’s Matrix, although he was secretive about it. He relied on absorbing the souls and Prayers who had died in battle during the Blood Wars. Although there were not many, he did not dare to snatch souls from the Abyss. However, a mere 0.01% of that amount was enough for those two fellows to sneakily eat until they were full.

After discussing this matter for some time, Garen naturally did not dare to simply believe the other party. However, when Kratos vowed solemnly to find an Underworld River Oath for them to sign this contract, Garen then waited for this Underworld River Oath.

Meanwhile, he continued spending time in his cave instead while interrogating the three new captives that he had acquired.

******************

After watching Garen’s silhouette left, Kratos arranged a Flame Isolation Boundary in a circle carefully.

Next, numerous beetles burrowed out of the ground behind him and formed themselves into a seductive female body.

“How did it go? How did it go with Maffey and Bakiloa that you contacted?” Kratos’ expression appeared solemn now after he had changed from his previously cautious attitude.

“I’ve informed them already. Bakiloa is extremely impatient. He was testing out a large-scale Blood Formation before I interrupted him. You will need to bear the cost,” answered the beetle-woman softly.

Kratos’ face was slightly contorted while a pained look appeared there faintly.

“Is Bakiloa willing to come?”

“Yes, but he’s extremely furious. He said that if you can’t give him a satisfactory reply, even the Wanku Fortress will not be able to stop him from devouring you.” The beetle-woman shivered. “I lost one-third of my torso just to meet him once.”

“He’s a Level Thirteen being indeed. He plays a part in the Soul Matrix this time as well. Anyways, our success rate will increase greatly as long as we obtain a Soul Divine Weapon.” Kratos’ gaze turned gloomy. “I really don’t believe that a mere little White Dragon can pass through three of our encirclements.”

“What if he really succeeds?” The beetle-woman asked anxiously.

“Then it won’t make any difference if we give him a share or not. I’m the only one who can activate the Soul Matrix. There’s nothing to be afraid of because I won’t be harmed no matter what happens,” said Kratos with a darkened expression. “There’s me, Level Eleven Maffey, and Level Thirteen Bakiloa, unless the Thane of Wanku… Hahaha.”

*******************

When Garen returned to his cave, the three Blasphemy Knights still remained unmoving there even though they were already awake and aware. Their pupils and face were the only parts that could move while the rest of their bodies were still numb.

The trio’s faces turned pale from fright when they saw Garen walking into the cave. Their gazes stared at Garen’s large mouth closely. They clearly thought that Garen was probably going to eat them.

Garen’s pure white body passed through the black Negative Energy Barrier. The inside of the cave was completely empty. There was nothing inside because Garen’s food and water were stored inside the Space Ring that Soaring Wing King had given him.

He walked toward one of the female knights and approached her one step at a time. Next, Garen grinned and exposed his mouth full of pure white and straight teeth.

Shh!

He bit the female knight’s head in one go.

Ahh!

A sharp pained cry rang out before Garen loosened his mouth. He looked at the female knight who had fainted and shook his head wordlessly.

“What are you afraid of? I was just scaring you for fun.” He was only joking around like this because he was extremely bored.

“Irene has always been cowardly,” said the male knight roughly. “If you want to kill someone, kill me first!”

“Still so strong-willed.” Garen shifted his gaze to look at this fellow instead.

He walked over and kicked this bastard away with one foot. Now was not the time to control these few people yet. He would wait until his Void Original Opus had finished simulating its original abilities. It would be perfect if he could condense an Aberrated Soul Seed like the one that he had in the Vampire World or perhaps the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s Distorted Seed.

Garen twisted his body once he had walked to the center of the cave. He had recently increased his Void Original Opus to 64%. Thus, he could already feel that numerous changes were occurring throughout his body.

The Void Original Opus was originally a key factor in gathering every single trace of his strength to advance his True Soul.

This 64% value had already consecutively activated several Secret Techniques that he had practiced previously.

The Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, which was one of the more crucial ones, was already activated perfectly. The following one was the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point that he had practiced previously. These two sets of skills that were worth being called as terrifying Demonic Techniques were finally refined and launched.

This instantly made up for more than half of Garen’s martial power system within his entire body. It also replenished his supernatural powers greatly. If he encountered another Void Shadow, at least it would not be so troublesome anymore, since he could use his Semi-Divine Weapon to torture it slowly to death.

He looked at his remainder of more than 1600 Potential Points. Once he had removed 500 points, these were his only leftovers.

“I’ll try again and see if I can use these leftover percentages to rush upward.” Garen could vaguely sense that the Void Original Opus would require more Potential Points towards the back.

When he had added five hundred points previously, he could already faintly tell that the percentage would increase very quickly when he had first started but had become more strenuous towards the end.

“I’ll try again.”

He continued focusing his gaze on the Void Original Opus. His Potential Points continued to decrease greatly while the increments of the Void Original Opus rose once again.

Garen did not seem to notice that seven blood-red black stars had already started to gleam faintly on the wings on his back. These black stars were completely pitch-black, save for the faint red light that was dispersing around it. A still, strange and deathly aura permeated slowly and dispersed throughout the surroundings of the cave.

64%… 65%… 67%… 70%… After that, it got stuck.

After reaching 70%, the Void Original Opus got stuck immediately while his Potential Points continued decreasing wildly.

Garen had spent more than 60% of his Potential Value to increase it by 6%. However, even though it had stopped suddenly towards the end, his Potential Value continued to decrease while his Void Original Opus remained static.

His Potential Points that previously stood at over 1600 points quickly decreased to only 1400 points. After that, since his Void Original Opus was indeed unable to absorb the Potential Value anymore, his Potential Points stopped decreasing.

Garen could clearly feel that his body was somewhat bloated. It seemed like a large amount of gas had surged into his body as if he was a balloon.

“I can’t increase it anymore, huh?” He moved his body. “My current physical fitness has probably restricted my increments. The few powers towards the back of the Void Original Opus are too strong. It has fully revealed that this body is incapable of loading it completely.”

After all, the Hellfrost Peacock Queen Secret Technique that he had gained during the later period was already considered an extremely powerful and terrifying Demonic Technique. The Void Original Opus would simulate and fully restore and repair it to its original state.

In other words, all of the Secret Techniques and Demonic Techniques that he had practiced previously would fully reappear and converge in this body.

When he opened his eyes, Garen could clearly feel that his right foot was slightly swollen. He lowered his head to looked at it before noticing that a strange, dark blue sphere that resembled an ice ball had apparently grown on his right hind claw.

His heart trembled slightly when this blue sphere separated itself from his body suddenly while his right hind leg disappeared at the same time as well.

This blue sphere fell on the ground and cracked on its own before an imposing, faceless man arched out from the middle, holding a halberd.

The muscles throughout the man’s entire body were extremely taut, and his height was over two meters. His skin was pale while his long, dark blue hair flew in the wind. A silent evil energy permeated around this man’s entire body.

Aside from the halberd that he was holding in his hand, there were numerous translucent halberds behind him that were naturally slowly frozen by the frost.

“You’re my right foot?” Garen’s mind stirred faintly suddenly before he opened his mouth and asked this question.

The three knights inside the cave were currently staring dumbfoundedly after they had witnessed this scene. Intense chills that were tinged with evil energy poured into their bodies silently. They did not seem to notice that strange faint shades of blue had appeared throughout their bodies while their temperatures had started to decrease automatically.

The man with long blue hair nodded faintly. His body was naturally covered in a layer of magnificent and exquisite light blue Ice Armor.

“I obey you, my master.”

He seemed to have his own intelligence, but his awareness was interlinked with Garen’s own, making it seem as though Garen was conversing with himself or perhaps if he was talking to his reflection in a mirror.

Garen felt as if both his wings had shown signs of breaking away from his body at the same time. He complied with the stirring in his heart and allowed both of his wings to separate themselves from his body naturally.

Both wings fell on the ground and naturally transformed into an imposing muscular man with a black colored body. Both of his arms were spread open as if they were two gigantic wings.

Seven black-red, closely-packed cavities appeared on his back slowly. This man did not have a face as well, but his stern, short black hair and exaggeratedly burly muscles gave off an extremely terrifying sense of forcefulness.

This was Garen when he was the Overlords of the Blood Breed World and the pinnacle of the world’s martial arts.

He relied on the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point to dominate the entire world at that time. He was peerless and if it was not for Nadia’s appearance in the end, perhaps he could have ruled over the martial arts of that world for more than hundreds of years.

“You’re my pair of wings.” Garen looked at the other person calmly.

“Of course,” answered the man in a similar low tone.

Garen looked at these two body parts that had separated themselves from his body naturally. These were clearly the works of the Void Original Opus. Originally, they were neither fully unified nor had they converged in one specific body. On the contrary, they were separated into different individuals to match each other and combine together. When these individuals finally gathered, it was time for the strongest body to appear.

“The final one.” Garen could feel his long tail disappearing, before an elegant man, whose entire body was wholly black, reappeared while holding a violin.

The most unique part of him was his eyes. He had no other features on his face other than two eyes. His left eye was red while his right eye was golden.

“In my heart, everything is possible,” said the man calmly. “My master, I’m very glad to meet you.”

Garen noticed that a golden lotus was engraved on his violin.

This was the manifestation of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, or perhaps the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book.

“Is this the path to domination?” This impression appeared in his heart faintly when Garen looked attentively at these individuals.

Achieving seventy percent of his Void Original Opus had revealed three of his previous states. The only ones that were missing were the Crystal King of the previous Mech World and the Hellfrost Peacock Queen.

Regarding these three individuals, Garen named them Evil Soldier, Demonic Book, and Seven Lives respectively.

When he looked at his dragon body that was already incomplete and imperfect, Garen’s will stirred before these three individuals returned to his body and transformed back into his right leg, two wings, and tail.

Two of the three knights had already fainted when Seven Lives appeared. When Seven Lives had just manifested, they were already contaminated by Evil Soldier’s ominous Spirit Energy that froze their bodies stiffly. Their entire consciousness and even their souls were inflicted with a temporary shock.

When he saw that his body was complete now, Garen faintly sighed in relief.

His right leg, both wings, and tail were the three parts that were flowing with powers. They were completely different from the strength within his own body.

Chapter 1322: Evolution 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With the tail being the most powerful part, the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book had a strong, overbearing power. When the long tail swayed gently, Garen could sense the horrifying urge to destroy everything locking its path. This sort of motive, or perhaps willpower, caused the Demonic Book energy which flowed in the long tail to rotate according to a mysterious track, which then produced a stronger power.

“It’s like… It’s still cultivating!” Garen suddenly understood the principle, a sense of absurdity arose within his mind.

A part of his body was actually cultivating a constantly powerful force according to his independent Willpower.

He tried maneuvering this kind of power, and it could actually be used regardless of each other.

“If so, with the tail added, there are still two other places. Together with myself, isn’t that equivalent to having four individuals practicing and strengthening one body at the same time?!” He was surprised and happy.

At this moment, he still did not know the extent to which his powers had reached. The variable was too big, and until then, it was still unknown how powerful a role the Void Original Opus played.

“What I need to do now is to test my true strength.” Garen glanced at the three knights on the ground as he stood up and walked out of the cave.

*********************

On the plains far away from Garen’s cave, a gigantic black Hound was slowly moving toward the ruins of the Fiery Beast.

This huge Hound was black in color. It might seem just like an ordinary hound from a distance. However, upon closer inspection, its body was actually composed of countless corpses and human bones.

This was an enormous Corpse-Hound. He was at least ten meters tall or so, and his massive body was twenty meters long. His eyes were made of two dark hollows, and blood-red mucus trickled down at the corner of its mouth occasionally. Its sharp teeth slightly exposed at the edge of its mouth.

Far away, all creatures around could already sense the deadly aura emitted from him, they would flee just from far away.

The Corpse-Hound was generally one of the favorite Undead Guards of Necromancers and Great Liches, but this Corpse-Hound was evidently out of control.

It had a clear row of black spikes on its back, which was a sign of that it had no ruler.

“Maffey, oh! My dear Maffey, you’re finally back!!” Kratos the Fiery Beast quickly rushed out of his ruins as the Corpse-Hound rushed in his direction from far away.

His eight legs were spider-like, moving steadily. However, with the dragon’s head above his body, it looked a bit strange.

“Hiss… His… Just nice, I haven’t eaten. You promised me a thousand high-quality corpses. That’s really generous, Kratos. Hiss…” the Corpse-Hound said loudly as he exhaled.

Kratos squeezed out a smile as he resisted the stench of the Corpse-Hound. “Come to my site first, and we’ll see. I’m sure you must be clear about my request, then?”

“Of course… Hiss…” Corpse-Hound grinned. “Bakiloa is already nearby, and his Teleportation spells are the best.”

“Bakiloa… So fast…” There was clearly a stunned look on the Fiery Beast’s face as a trace of fear flashed in his eyes.

“If you’re unable to satisfy him, hiss… You’ll really be in trouble this time,” Maffey snickered.

A loud bang sounded suddenly, and the two gigantic creatures looked up into the distant sky.

An evident expression of sneer and anticipation appeared on the Hound Maffey’s face, while Bakiloa’s face remained serious and cautious.

Soon, blood-red clouds floated across the sky from a distance.

These clouds were like living creatures, squirming at the edges. Their cores constantly twisted and converged as a huge human face emerged. It was the face of a man with a beard and hair.

It was almost the same as the Matrix Spirit Garen had seen in Snow City. However, those were Thunder Clouds, and these were Blood Clouds. Furthermore, the size of them this time was almost twice as large.

The Blood Clouds turned over and almost covered the plains. The sun in the sky was also blocked as well as it turned reddish and grayish.

“Kratos, if you even dare to deceive me, this time I’m really going to swallow you up!” The huge Blood Cloud rumbled furiously. It was an Abyssal that sounded like the screams of squally winds and the screams of humans.

“Bakiloa, have I ever not fulfilled something that I’ve promised you?” Kratos gave a slight apple-polish smile. “Even if you don’t believe me, do you not believe in the Wanku Fortress behind me? After all, I am the Blacksmith’s First Seat.”

Bakiloa was a mass of cloud that had no fixed form, and this had become his trait as the climate life. He was born in the intersection between the Abyss Underworld River and the Heavens. The Void Universe there would intertwine with the immense evil powers of the Abyss and the pure spirit energy, gradually forming large clumps of clouds. One of them produced the weird but special life of Bakiloa.

He had two extreme personalities, and his personality changed every Abyss Month. This personality was a mixture of the pure and devout spirit energy of the Heavens, and the evil selfish powers of the Abyss. His personality was generated by random according to different proportions, even he was unable to determine his own character for the next Abyss Month.

Once when he met up with his old friend Kratos, he just turned into an indifferent, hopeless character that was ignorant toward all matters. The extremity of this personality was self-destructive as he was just about to devour every life that was in his sight before blowing himself up.

The result was that Kratos was almost swallowed alive. If it was not for the Chief of Army of the Wanku Fortress, which was also the thane, who pulled him out, he would have probably turned into nutrients for Bakiloa already.

“My most respected Bakiloa, I hope you are in a good mood during our meeting this time,” Kratos said cautiously.

Maffey, however, was not really afraid of Bakiloa. He had escaped under the mouth of this fellow once and he was best at escaping. His confidence for this area was extremely strong.

“I’m in a bad mood, really. Your Emissary interrupted one of my important experiments at the most critical time, If you can’t pay a price that satisfies me, then I’ll consider killing you right now.” Bakiloa was in a furious mood. He continued howling and the storms whistled. The airstream was increasing rapidly and the surrounding temperature was rising tremendously. The temperature at the plains had risen by more than ten degrees and it was still heating up.

“Please rest assured, this time I’m letting you make a move just for a Soul Semi-Divine Weapon!” Kratos made sure he emphasized the term when he said the word ‘soul’.

“Soul Divine Weapon?” As expected, Bakiloa had slightly calmed down.

“There’s also another heterogeneous White Dragon with a very good talent. He has a powerful body and the energy contained in his flesh can definitely satisfy you.” Kratos grinned. His heart was slightly relaxed now as Bakiloa’s mood seemed to be traceable. This was the best time to negotiate with him.

“Where is this thing?! Bring me there immediately!!” Bakiloa was getting irritable.

“Hold your horses, I shall bring the both of you there right now…” Kratos replied softly, pleased.

********************

“An abnormal Force Field?” Garen felt a bit fretful.

“Could it be that there’s a problem over at Kratos’?” The Abyss was full of frauds and scams, so he had every reason to be worried about Kratos’ ulterior motives. That fellow seemed to be a scoundrel, so it was natural to meet some helpers to get some help.

“Seems like I still have to be more careful.” Garen thought about it and felt that the Force Fields that came from the distance suddenly was unusual. Just as a precaution, he grabbed the three Knights and left the cave.

Somehow, sometime, a big clump of red clouds had appeared in the distance, slowly moving towards his side.

“It seems that the abnormal Force Fields are caused by these red clouds? Perhaps it’s related to the strange messy weather at the Abyss.” Garen frowned. He thought about it and decided not to care, then returned to his cave and soon disappeared within.

The red clouds in the distance moved in quickly the moment he returned to the cave.

Below the red clouds, Kratos and Corpse-Hound were running swiftly as they followed the pace of the red clouds.

Kratos kept pulling out pieces of metal elliptical rune paper. The yellow rolls of paper were constantly burned into black ashes that disappeared into the wind. The black ashes were all scattered everywhere and was then naturally swept up by the strong winds of the red clouds blowing toward the open space around Garen’s cave.

Rows of black ash were automatically arranged into a series of complex yet detailed symbols and words, forming a huge circle of Abyssal and Rune powers.

The entire circle surrounded Garen’s cave, placing him right in the center. It was at least kilometers in diameter when the last speck of ash completed the circle.

Buzz!

The entire circle suddenly began buzzing and shaking. Black threads floated from the ashes and were interwoven into a net spreading toward the sky. It grew longer and bigger as if they were black vines.

“Devour everything!” A human face emerged among the red clouds and watched Garen’s cave below greedily.

His massive body made of clouds was pressing down entirely.

Boom!

The cave collapsed immediately, but there was nothing in it.

Kratos’ face froze while delight shone in Maffey’s eyes.

As for Bakiloa, he was stunned. The stare he had at Kratos was so cold it could possibly freeze everything.

“This is what you call a heterogeneous White Dragon and Soul Divine Weapon!? If you want to die, you can just say it. I’ll gladly grant that wish of yours!”

“No, no, no! Bakiloa, please listen to me, the situation is certainly not like this!” Kratos shook his head frantically, a trace of fear flashed through his eyes. “The White Dragon has been living here all along! It’s true, and I swear under the oath of Soul and Underworld River!”

“You still want to lie to me!?” Bakiloa was completely furious. He swooped down as immense red clouds shrouded Kratos. An oppression of such a colossal Soul naturally had a certain Decree Spell effect. Moreover, it was the power of the Decree Spell of a Level-Nine peak, it would be a steady flow of power unlike those released only once by the average creature. Bakiloa seemed to be releasing this terrifying, endless surge of oppression, immobilizing Kratos.

“No! Master Bakiloa! You must listen to me! It’s not what you think it is!” Kratos shouted. Watching the red clouds that were almost reaching his head, he finally sensed the true shadow of death. It was not that he did not want to fight back, he did resist it, but nothing happened; it would only irritate the other person.

The gap between Level Thirteen and Level Nine was that different from the gap between Level Five and Level Nine.

Chapter 1323: Blood Wars 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Wait!” the Corpse-Hound Maffey yelled by the side, “Kratos is right. Technically, there’s still a White Dragon out there and three humans. There seems to be the scent of Blasphemy Knights.”

He sniffed with his sensitive nose and revealed a look of greed. “Such perfectly strong flesh, if I’m able to eat it, perhaps I can safely pass the next Bottleneck.”

The movements of the red clouds that were swooping downward immediately stopped.

Bakiloa turned and looked at Maffey.

“Are you sure?”

“Of course!” Maffey glanced at him with dissatisfaction. “Are you doubting my sense of smell?”

Bakiloa did not respond, instead, he set his steely gaze on Kratos, withdrawing the big clumps of clouds that retracted back to the sky.

“From what you’ve said, he probably hasn’t gotten far, maybe nearby here that we can catch up. Can you confirm which direction he headed off to?”

Maffey continued sniffling.

“Should be that direction…” He raised his head and suddenly began running in a direction.

Bakiloa and Kratos then followed behind hurriedly.

*******************

Garen continued flying, the frequency of his wings flapping had reached an astonishing speed.

A large area of the Abyss’ ground swept under him. A steel fortress at his right side shot out a large number of black smoke pillars that were surrounded by large blood-red runes. It was clearly a sort of spell.

Garen could vaguely recognize the style of this fortress. The Devil and Demon’s Fortress were different. The Devil’s Fortress was extremely orderly and beautiful with a hint of grimness.

As for the Demon’s, it was just messy. Moreover, they were too lazy to even bother with all the repairs to the insignificant places. Because of the brutal fights and battles that often damaged the internal structures of the building and the surrounding walls of the fortress, they never bothered maintaining it anymore.

“It’s the Demon’s Fortress.” Garen simply identified the soldiers below.

Somewhere beneath the fortress and the big gate on the ground, a ruthless battle was happening right at that moment. Devil Soldiers that had horns on their heads were battling against chaotic strong Demons. Green, blue, and red blood scattered everywhere.

Several tall Balor Demons were entangled among the troops, fighting the giant beasts and giant squids.

Garen swept across the sky and attracted the attention of some of the creatures below. However, the war was getting heated up, nobody could turn their attention away.

As for Garen, he sensed a strong aura that was closing in on him.

“He actually caught up.” It bothered him that after drilling a hole underground and escaping from another place, not long after he was away, he could see the place in where he originally lived being surrounded by a large array of spells. He could also sense Kratos’ indistinct aura.

He instantly knew that Kratos had definitely brought trouble upon him.

Fortunately, he escaped right on time.

“This is Kaqiu Plains, we can’t fly anymore. There are flight restrictions here, time can’t stop over two Magic Points on the battlefield. Otherwise, the Thane of Fortress will kill us!”

The male Knight that was clutched in Garen’s claws started shouting.

“Thane of Fortress? What level of a powerhouse is the general Thane of Fortress?” Garen asked casually.

“Generally it’s the peak level, Level Fourteen,” the Knight answered honestly, “We can’t fight against the Thane of Fortress’ prestige. They still have many men of below Level Nine. If they work together on a spell, they can easily imprison or even kill a being of Level Ten and above,” Irene, the female Knight, continued.

“Level Fourteen…” Garen shivered. He once witnessed the power of a Level Fourteen, the speaker back in Snow City, who was also the father of Dragon Master. By just casting a spell far away, he was already able to suppress all the Wizards that were present in the area. If he was to cast a spell close-ranged, perhaps the power would be more than doubled. He was not an existence he could fight against at the moment.

“Let’s go down first and we’ll see.” He then flew lower toward the battlefield.

Behind him, he could vaguely see the large clumps of red clouds almost chasing up.

Kratos’ aura was getting closer and closer already, there was also a mixture of two inexplicable, unfamiliar force fields.

“He indeed found people to help.” Garen sneered and looked back at the red clouds behind him.

“We can’t actually help you with anything, so can you let us go?” Irene was the most naive one among the three Knights. After noticing the people chasing behind them, her face paled and she began pleading Garen.

“Let all of you go?” Garen smiled and glanced at the trio. “You guys were the ones who wanted to kill me in the first place, it’s not going to be that easy for me to just let all of you off the hook. Come on, let’s join this Blood War. We can avoid those three fellows behind too.

The bloody atmosphere and extremely broad battlefield was just the right place for him to hide his trail.

Garen rushed straight toward the battlefield, where a mess of massacre was all over the place.

A Gnoll in black armor swung a hammer toward Garen’s back.

With a swipe of Garen’s tail, he immediately smashed the spell barrier that was emitted from the Gnoll with a bang. The Gnoll flew on impact and was broken into half by the waist mid-air, both halves of its corpse fell onto the two Devils who were battling.

The Fiery Devils lingered in the flames and smoke. They wore blood-red robes and held long barbed whips. One of them slashed the whip toward Garen’s head.

“Die!”

With a smack, Garen caught the whip in his claws and pulled hard, pulling the Fiery Devil over and exhaled a breath of Dragon Breath.

The icy Dragon Breath was mixed with a cold toxin, and the Fiery Devil instantly froze into a block of ice.

There were all just creatures that were no higher than Level Six, they stood no chance against Garen at all. He could simply wipe out the entire space with just a mere swipe of his tail, or just a simple stretch of his claws.

He was basically a war machine in this sort of low-level battlefield.

His claws were already covered with flesh and armor fragments after just a few minutes.

Roar!

All of a sudden, a green fat Bullhorn Devil stared at him.

This fellow was carrying an enormous mace that was at least five meters wide. It had a long tail much like that of a Tyrannosaurus Rex’s. The tail resembled his third leg, supporting his bulky body as he walked towards Garen shakily.

The monster was almost two heads taller than Garen, looking down at Garen from his height.

The monster suddenly opened its mouth and spat, spewing out large black worms that flew toward Garen’s body. At the same time, the mace on his shoulder slammed down like a phantom.

Bang!

As Garen’s wings blocked before him, seven black-red stars flashed on his wings. It was hard, and the strength was unusually terrifying. The seven stars suddenly grew brighter. Garen immediately felt a steady stream of strength surged through his wings, increasing his strength by more than half.

With this strength, he gently moved his wings and firmly blocked the monster’s wings.

He was originally as powerful as this guy already. However, after this enhancement, he surpassed the other person. The fat devil had a great fall and soon, fearless Demons swarmed forward and started biting crazily.

Garen did not care much but just went forward and lashed his tail ferociously.

With a loud rumble, the fat Devil exploded straight away and turned into black bugs that flew around.

The surrounding Demons cheered.

“You’ve crossed the border! Dragon Race Mercenaries!” A Devil leader shrieked.

“So what if I’ve crossed the border?” Garen was too lazy to even bother. He was surrounded by Demons and Devils. Most of the Demons here were Gnolls, Fiery Devils and fat Devils like the one just now.

The Devil Leader screamed as he drove the large crowd of Fiery Devils toward Garen. As for he himself, he retreated back. The Devils that were being driven away had reddish eyes, they were clearly under some sort of stimulation.

The atmosphere everywhere was hectic.

Demons screamed in an insane manner as they darted out from Garen’s side, heading toward the Devils.

They then exploded to death, row by row, by the group of Warlocks’ spells. Yet, there was no sign of retreat.

Flames, strong acid, huge rolling stones, and magma bombs fell from the sky one by one onto the groups of Demons and Devils. Blood and the shattering sounds of Souls could be heard among the screams.

Garen stood on the battlefield with three of the Blasphemy Knights. In this battlefield, Garen could just open his wings and he was able to block and flames, rolling stones, and even strong acid. If he simply exerted a little bit more strength, he would be able to smash the crowded Devils into death.

His body scent was perfectly hidden in the bloodshed of this battlefield.

Gnolls were constantly torn into pieces by him and at the same time, he vaguely felt that a surge of evil yet distorted strength slowly seeping into his body in the process of killing.

This strength then proceeded in nourishing his body, accelerating the evolution of his body.

“So this is the Power of Abyss huh?” Garen immediately understood. The creatures that were involved in the Blood Wars would cause the increase of creatures killed, which would then gain the reward of the Abyss’ Will, thus gaining more powerful strength. This strength consisted a natural effect of creating chaos in one’s mind and if it was not stably digested, if this chaotic essence was not suppressed, one would eventually become extremely chaotic, turning into a war machine that could only kill. One could ultimately die on the battlefield.

Hiss!

With just one claw, Garen beat the Fiery Devil into ashes and he instantly felt his back loosen up. It was as if his back finally broke through something that was bound around him, piercing through his scales and releasing them all out.

He heard the exclamation of the three Knights behind him and turned around to look at his back.

Only then did he realize, at right that moment, his back was covered with rows of black venomous snakes.

His back that was originally like a Stegosaurus, full of spikes, was now full of soft venomous snakes. These venomous snakes looked ferocious with black spikes all over their heads. They looked just like sharp whips.

“Is the evolution finally over?”

Garen quickly glanced at his Status Pane. (TL Note: The author’s original script wrote something along the lines of “his IDE Status Pane”, this is probably a typo.)

As expected, there had been new changes in his status. Just right below his Attribute Pane, there was a new row of status.

‘Status: White Dragon Level 2 Evolutionary Body — Snakeback White Dragon. Spellcraft talent, Poisonous Eye.’

Garen then only discovered that his eyes seemed to be filled with a new kind of power. This power was like the liquid compressed within the eyelids; it was flowing around, yet it did not affect his vision. He felt that he could just use this strength and unleash it out at any time.

So he found a Devil that rushed before him, a slightly icy Devil, a white-skinned man that was wrapped in a white chilly fog.

With two subtle slurps, two rays of white-blue Light Beams shot out from Garen’s eyes and hit the icy Devil as quickly as a sudden clap of thunder.

Ah!

The Devil suddenly let out a scream and melted like a candle, turning into a gooey solution in less than two seconds flat.

Chapter 1324: Blood Wars 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen instantly felt that both his eyes were starting to accumulate the power again. Yet, from the looks of it, it was going to take some time.

He had a look at his status.

‘Poisonous Eye — Consists of the Natural Ability to use three gazes a day to poison the enemy. Vision +5, the eyeball will not be eroded by most toxins.’

“The recovery time should be within five minutes,” Garen calculated.

Soon enough, some high-leveled Devils finally fixed their gaze on Garen after charging about on the battlefield.

Two Level-Nine Chained Demons approached Garen. Their chains were entwined with black flames. It was the unique Sin Flames of Barto’s Hell. If a creature was ignited by it, the remorse and regrets from the deepest part of their heart would grow rapidly and from there, resulting in a hopeless tendency to self-destruct. They would seize the opportunity to kill the creature swiftly.

The two Level-Nine Chained Demons looked like tall and strong men with sharp, gray iron helmets.

They were bare-chested, they had green-grayish skin and solid muscles. They had a black belt that was gray by the edges with a skull around their waist, but their legs were just bizarre black goat hooves that looked furry.

“Surround him!” The two Chained-Demons had long noticed Garen. This White Dragon’s physique was unusually strong so they could capture him as their slave. If he was seriously injured, they could still get a good price by selling him off.

They flung their chains, and a huge amount of black words and symbols came flying out of the chains, surrounding Garen wholly.

“Hell Trial!” One of the Chained-Demon roared in Devil Language.

Numerous black words surrounded Garen and instantly formed a gigantic black funnel, positioning Garen right at the bottom of the funnel.

There was an extremely disgusting sticky substance hidden in the immense Attractive Force. It was blocking all of Garen’s nose, mouth, and other parts that could be used to breathe.

The severe suffocation was making Garen physically uncomfortable.

He bellowed, and his entire body began to shake in a high frequency, attempting to get rid of the sticky substance on his body. However, it was useless. The sticky substance was neither a spell effect nor a supernatural force, but a special physical attack created by spells. It was not fighting toughness with toughness. Instead, it was disguised in a different form, directly causing the creature to suffocate and lose consciousness.

Garen used up several ways, but he was still unable to get rid of the sticky substance completely. Suddenly, the contempt he had when he killed the small Devil earlier on completely disappeared. In such a short moment, two Level-Nine peak Devils had surrounded him. He could imagine the most important key here was not the sufficient power, but to be able to learn a powerful life-saving way.

You could be strong, but there were those stronger than you here.

Garen used every trick, the Dragon Breath as well as all other physical means, yet they were all useless. The suffocation kept up with him. If it was not for him being able to hold his breath for a long time, he would have probably lost consciousness due to the lack of air.

“Try it one last time.”

“Garen focused his gaze and stared into the black funnel right in front of him.

Swoosh swoosh! Two rays of white-blue Light Beams shot out. They were not eye-catching, looking just like normal ice rays.

However, the power it generated left everyone staring dumbfoundedly.

Two Level Nine Peak merged together and released a spell that was close to Level Ten, but it just melted. Within less than half a minute, they turned into a puddle of pale blue viscous liquid on the ground.

The suffocation that Garen’s body felt instantly faded.

The body after evolution was indeed extremely different.

The power of this Innate Spell had actually reached the standards of a Level Ten, making Garen particularly happy.

Level Nine to Level Ten was a key threshold. Clearly, the biggest indication of his evolution was that he managed to break through this threshold.

With 50 years worth of preparation for the great war, he could once again make great use of his Potential Points to improve his attributes.

“Soul! A lot of Souls…” An evil soft voice suddenly swooped across the top of Garen’s head.

It was a massive, white Entropy Ship that was made up of a myriad of naked human bodies that were still squirming. This was the gigantic Warship that the Demons used to weave through planes. Making an appearance here clearly meant that there was a special task here. This sort of Entropy Ship had a Soul Will itself. It was not a dead ship, but a gigantic monster.

The huge skull in front of the Entropy Ship howled loudly, as two bottom planks opened up and scattered a huge amount of Demon Seeds.

These Demon Seeds were like black Dandelion seeds, but once they get into contact with a Devil’s body, they would grow and parasitize on its body. Soon, it would take over the Devil’s body and turn it into a complete new demon.

“Parasitic Demons,” Garen recognize this type of Demons. He cautiously dodged the seeds that were sprinkled all over. Once contact was made, this sort of thing would not joke around regardless of who you were.

They had a crazy desire for flesh and blood, friend or foe alike.

Therefore, although the Entropy Ship mainly scattered the seeds in the direction of the Devil’s camp, Demons that were unable to dodge in time were also sucked to death by the Parasitic Demons.

“The counterattack of the Demons is finally about to begin.”

Garen saw a large group of tall gigantic Demons rushing out behind him from the Fortress gate all the way to the depths of the Devil’s army. Each of these Demons was at almost the same state as Garen, some even much taller than him. They had all sorts of strange forms, even Garen’s Snakeback White Dragon appearance was seemingly insignificant among them.

He mixed himself in the crowd as they rushed toward the Devil’s army. Among the giant Demons, most of them were Level Eight, whereas the stronger Gods were at least Level Ten or Eleven. It was extremely terrifying.

Only Demons would hire external mercenaries to participate in battles, whereas Devils were more dependent on their own troops to kill.

Cthulhu’s Hell and Thanes had something like a Reincarnation Pool. Dead Devils only needed to consume just a little energy and they would be reborn again, it was just that they would not have their original memory. That was why they were not worried about the number of Devils decreasing.

While Garen followed the troop rushing forward, he began to try increasing his Potential Points sneakily.

He still had more than a thousand four hundred potential points untouched. Now that he had finished his evolution, it was the right time to use them.

As soon as his gaze strayed for a while, his Potential Points immediately dropped whereas his Attribute Points increased rapidly.

The first thing that Garen improved on was his physique. With a strong enough physique, he could then be immune to higher leveled spells and negative states. Also, his self-healing ability would be even better. In the Blood War of the Abyss, strength was not a priority, survival was.

So physique was his first choice.

His physique was initially 80 points, which was already the maximum limit. However, now it was still rising quickly.

81… 82… 83…

Soon, Garen realized that something was wrong.

Despite his Potential Points being consumed a little bit too quickly, his attributes were increasing slowly.

He paused for a while and began calculating.

“It’s actually changed to ten points to raise one point of an attribute?!” He was shocked, but it was understandable. Now that he had reached eighty points, which was basically an unprecedented degree, it was normal to have a higher requirement of potential points.

“Thankfully, this is the Abyss Blood War, it’s still pretty easy to collect Souls and replenish my Potential Points.”

As he went along with the crowd of rowdy Demons, Garen continued improving his physique.

This time around, there seemed to be no limits.

One thousand four hundred potential points were soon consumed until there was not much left.

As for his physique, it actually reached an unprecedented level. 180 points!

He only had a mere four hundred-ish potential points remaining.

Garen’s body did not seem to have changed much. However, the color of the scales all over his body darkened, and there was a faint shimmer of a natural white-gold. There were some special textures that could make people feel dizzy without even using the Divine Statue Technique. Those were the powerful natural symbols.

180 points, this was Garen’s current Soul Limit’s peak. Even though he had absorbed Soul Rings later, his Soul Limit was increasing slower and slower. The Soul Seed condensed after absorbing the Soul Energy later was completely different from the quality of his original inspiration. Therefore, the improvement of his Soul Limit was still extremely limited. Even after absorbing so much, he only managed to increase ten points of his limits from 170 to 180.

However, Garen was still very satisfied nevertheless.

180 points of physique, even Garen himself was not very clear about this concept. He looked around, and Cliffon Demons with gigantic horns surrounded him. These Demons had a huge head, a furless gray-black body, and four extremely thick elephant legs. A sort of green mucus constantly dripped from their abdomen. Hence, when they passed by, they naturally left a trail of venom. That was why they were also known as Ecological Destroyers, the most hated Demons of Elves and living creatures of nature.

“What are you looking at!?” Garen’s arrogance and ignorance caused a dissatisfaction among the group of Cliffon Demons. These demons that were also known as Demonic Behemoths were much bigger in size than Garen. At ten meters high, they turned around and bellowed impatiently.

Garen was just about anxious over not finding an opportunity, and this Demonic Behemoth’s powers seemed to be around Level Ten. This was exactly the kind of opponent he could provoke at the moment.

He confirmed that his Poisonous Eye had finished accumulating, and he looked at this Demonic Behemoth in an even more impatient manner.

“What are you yelling for! Yell more and I’ll kill you!”

“What!?” The Demonic Behemoth’s eyes were wide open, as though it could not imagine a Level-Nine creature would actually dare to challenge it. After acquiring the Power of Abyss in the Blood War, there was the possibility of mental confusion and impulsiveness. The originally bloodthirsty and impulsive Demonic Behemoths were now even more barbarous; they could not stand being provoked.

With a bang, they rushed toward Garen.

A small hill over ten meters in size was coming right at Garen, and the immense Attractive Force had naturally locked onto Garen, making it impossible for him to dodge.

“You dare to challenge me!” Garen was furious, he looked as if his dignity was just insulted. He then directly charged toward the fellow without a care.

By this time, he had already used up the remaining four hundred potential points and piled them up on his strength.

Four hundred points were equivalent to forty points of strength. His original eighty points of strength straight away rose to 120 points, which had far exceeded the limits of the general biological body. Even an Ancient Dragon could never reach Garen’s current level. Purely physical wise, he had reached a peak.

Bang!

The two giants crashed into each other, sending out a clear shockwave.

Chapter 1325: A Chance Encounter 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Demonic Behemoth stumbled four steps backward, fell with a thump onto the ground and could not get up anymore.

Garen also felt a tremendous force crashing into him, as if he had slammed against a wall.

“It truly is the Demonic Behemoth. Its strength comes from the dark vortex in the depths of the Abyss. With the support of the dark vortex that swirls all the time, it doesn’t just merely aid the outburst of the body’s strength.”

Garen had an epiphany. His 120-points of Strength was already on par with the Demonic Behemoth’s. Even exceeded it.

After all, the Demonic Behemoths were one of the demons with the highest strength in the Abyss, not to mention the Dragon Clan; even the slightly weaker demigods would not choose to wrestle with them when encountering them.

The Demonic Behemoth that fell collided with two elder demons that were moving forward. These elder demons with sharp blades in their hands and long horns on their heads were about to rage, but they quickly fell silent and dared not speak a word when they saw that it was a Demonic Behemoth. They hurried away immediately.

A Level Ten-Demonic Behemoth was one of the top strengths ranked in this team. The one who could knock out this fellow would naturally not be a simple existence.

The Demonic Behemoth shook its head and got up. It was not injured at all. “That’s rather strong?” It could not believe that it was knocked down by someone from the Dragon Clan. The Dragon Clan, this kind of reptile, had always been skinny and weak, and only the higher-level Dragon Clan could scare him. A little Level Nine-White Dragon that could actually knock it over was absolutely unthinkable!

“I must have seen wrongly as my head feels a little dizzy.” He shook his head and charged at Garen again.

Boom!!

There was another thundering sound. The Demonic Behemoth fell back at the same spot and stared vacantly at Garen.

There was not even a mark on Garen at the spot where he had caught him with his claws.

“Get lost!” Garen roared impatiently.

The Demonic Behemoth seemed to have finally recognized the reality. Panting heavily, he silently lumbered away from Garen.

Garen rampaged among the gigantic demons. Wherever he passed, no one dared to cross him.

A few Level Ten-demons were knocked over to the ground by him.

Charging through all the way, the team very quickly reached the Devil’s Army.

Both parties fought and killed at close quarters, and nothing could be distinguished.

****************

“He has joined the Blood War!” Maffey said, displeased. “I hate the Blood War the most. There’re so many delicious corpses swaying about in front, and yet I don’t dare to go devour them. This is simply the cruelest torment in the world.”

Corpse-Hound brought Bakiloa and Kratos along and stood by the edge of the Blood War battlefield to watch from afar. They did not dare to go any closer as they could be forcefully dragged into the battlefield by the Will of the Abyss.

Bakiloa had completely retracted the cloud on his entire body and landed on the ground. He had transformed into an elemental life form that was formed completely through the condensation of red clouds. He was not clothed at all; even the skin and muscles were just masses of slowly drifting bloody clouds. On his head were two curved horns, while his face was that of an old man’s.

“Can we still catch up?” He asked impatiently.

“I don’t think so.” Maffey shook his head. “The smell inside is too mixed up. Even I have no way.”

Kratos had a stiff expression on one side. If he could not find Garen, he would be in deep trouble.

“I know the vanguard of this fortress. Maybe we can go inside to search. A White Dragon is also rather eye-catching here. After all, this is not the Dragon Clan’s battlefield.”

“I hope it turns out as what you have said…” Bakiloa said coldly.

Kratos did not dare to answer back. He quickly led the two behemoths toward the Blood War.

************

Garen was killing wantonly. One after another, the devils were smashed into pieces under his claws. As he spewed out a Dragon Stream with his mouth, a vast number of devils would be frozen into ice sculptures, dying completely.

Little demons flew up from behind and pounced onto the back of his wings, trying to pierce his wings with their steel forks, but to no avail. They were directly thrown off with the spreading of both his wings. His wings could now use the exertion of force as the basis. With the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point as the foundation, he could break out an even stronger force. Because his own basic strength was too great, and the enhancement of the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point was not developed for the Dragon Clan, so the increase was limited. However, it could also bring about a 150% enhancement to its original strength, which was a one-half improvement, reaching a terrific 180 points!!

Garen was a horrifying meat grinder on the battlefield. The surrounding devils and demons were slaughtered wantonly by him. With a swing of his tail, and wherever the platinum trail swept across, all the creatures would be cleared off. Some even directly exploded and turned into blood mist.

The Will of the Abyss continued to strengthen his body. The more creatures one killed, the greater the reward the Will of the Abyss would grant that being. It did not care whether you were the existence of other worlds.

Garen felt that he was growing non-stop, and every creature that died under his claws brought him a huge influx of soul power.

After filtering this strength through the Semi-Divine Weapon, the Despair Skull, and removing the messy memories and all kinds of chaotic emotions in it, it transformed into the purest soul power, which was absorbed by Garen and turned into Potential Points.

He watched his Potential Points begin to rise again.

A Level Five-little demon could benefit him, while a Level Seven and Eight-monster could grant him with more than ten points.

And now he had killed at least dozens of little demons and more than ten Level Seven and Eight-monsters. The potential aura rushed madly into his body like a waterfall.

Garen could not be bothered to look at the others and directly added the Potential Points to the attribute points. He watched his attributes climb continually.

A huge black scorpion darted at him, raising its stinger to strike Garen’s head.

The black scorpion was almost as tall as Garen, and it was also considered a big guy on the battlefield.

The tip of the poison sting shone with a faint white light.

Whish!

Garen’s claws caught the poisonous sting in an instant, and he wrestled with the scorpion.

He suddenly jerked hard. Roar!!!

With an angry bellow, Garen actually lifted the entire scorpion straight up and hurled it sideways. Boom, boom, boom, boom! All the devils and demons around were swept away.

“Tyrant! Kill him!!” A thunderous voice sounded in the devil’s language from the opposite side.

Boom!!

A bloody red foot similar to Garen’s size descended from the sky and stepped onto the demons in front of Garen. Even a Demonic Behemoth was directly squashed, fleeing awkwardly with half of the body left.

The owner of the foot was a huge humanoid devil with bright red skin. It had three eyes, but they were not on the face. They were at the crotch instead… The place that should have been the head and the face was just a shroud of huge mass of dark clouds. The rest of its parts were almost the same as a normal human being.

“It’s the Devil Warlord!!” Some demons were fleeing in horror toward all directions.

The Warlord of the Devil’s Army – a powerful existence that could command millions of demons, and their power was often incomparably savage. They were not necessarily the most powerful race, and they could have also grown from a variety of weak races.

Just like the humongous Warlord in front, he revealed the power that was not lower than that of Level Eleven or Twelve the moment it appeared. It was unknown how long his gigantic body had been evolving.

“Nagolas!” The Devil Warlord leaned down and grabbed at Garen with its huge hand.

Garen looked up at the bloody red palm that was almost of his own size. He did not avoid it but wanted to test his current strength. He stomped his hind leg, and the earth behind him collapsed directly, causing dust and smoke to diffuse into the sky.

Leveraging the tremendous strength, Garen rushed directly toward the huge hand.

Apart from him, there was no other demon around who dared to face the Warlord. All of them had shunned away.

Garen’s wings illuminated seven black stars, and the entire dragon’s torso muscles constricted, like an arrow released from the string.

Boom!!

Garen’s body collided fiercely with the huge hand and directly penetrated it, forming a blood-hole. One could see the view at the back through the center of the palm.

“Nagolas!!” The Warlord once again roared, this time with great anger. The blood-hole in his huge hand healed quickly, as if he had never been hurt.

Two giant hands grabbed at Garen with lightning speed. He bent over his height of a hundred meters, and his three eyes shot out rope-like black lights, attempting to capture Garen.

In theory, this Warlord was at Level Twelve!

This was the comprehensive calculated fitness according to Strength, Agility and et cetera. But the battle was not just a matter of numbers. The most important things were strategy, tactics, and practical skills.

Although Garen was only at Level Ten at the moment, his combat experience was not ordinary, and he was not inferior to the top warriors in the Blood War. Furthermore, the crucial point was that his physical fitness was also extremely scary, almost the same as the Warlord’s, except that the height of his body was far less cumbersome than the other party.

The two engaged each other, and Garen did not expect that the Devil Warlord’s skill was actually not inferior to his!

After fighting for a few moments, although the Warlord was cumbersome, its battle techniques were very skilled. It could be said that there were no flaws, and they did not seem to be inflexible.

Moreover, every attack the Warlord made was accompanied by a huge explosion, which exploded as soon as it came into contact with anything. This was the part that annoyed Garen greatly.

His attack, on the other hand, would cause penetration damage once it made contact, which was to destroy the opponent through vibration.

However, the Warlord’s skin was too thick, and the penetration strength showed no response at all.

The two monsters were entangled and created a battlefield by themselves. No devils nor demons wanted to be involved, and they all fled away.

Looking from afar, one could only see a red giant surrounded by a flying white dragon. Both went on the offensive and the defensive, and from time to time, one would get hurt or the other would be knocked over.

This was the first time Garen had encountered a high-level opponent who was on par with him in terms of skill, and this astounded him.

This Warlord was already the equivalent of the upper Demon Lord level, and his battle techniques were very skillful. Being a veteran in battles, Garen had repeatedly used various ways to try to lure him into advancing, but they were all seen through, and he himself was nearly deceived instead. The other party’s abundant battle experience exceeded that of any individual he had come across. Even Slayer from back then was a far cry from the other party.

“Nagolas!!” The Warlord once again yelled.

Garen did not know what he meant by this, but both sides had been fighting for a long time and had the notion of retreating. He looked at the Warlord’s three small eyes and quickly drew back, pouncing toward other low-level devils.

The Warlord had long been irritated and directly shifted his target, lunging at other demons.

Blood Wars; the biggest meaning of it was not battle, nor the elimination of grudges and hatred.

Instead, it was to deplete the ever-growing huge fecundity of the Abyss and Hell… So slaughter was the basis of the Blood Wars.

For the Abyss’s and Hell’s Monarchs, this was actually a circulation process of the internal energy. Because there were too many devils and low-level demons in the Abyss, so every once in a while they would set a time to lessen the population together…

Garen charged into the group of low-level devils, and the red Devil’s Army was like having a drop of white milk dripping into a bloody sea, which erupted in an instant.

The platinum shadow flitted around, and Garen’s claws, wings, and Dragon Breath all became a terrific weapon that would kill with just a touch.

There were devils all around. Garen did not know how long he had been slaughtering. He was tirelessly killing, and the continuous supply of energy was expended after being besieged by several dozens of Level Nine-existences. Even with his 180-points of Vitality, he was struggling a little. Feeling slightly depleted, he then slowly pulled back.

Chapter 1326: A Chance Encounter 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When Garen came to, there was a mixture of countless skeletons, flesh and blood everywhere. Crackling sounds were heard as they were ignited by the corrosive air, releasing a green smoke.

There were demons constantly rushing past him to the frontline. They were Tanar’ri’s little demons and elder demons. They were had long pointed tails, black bat wings on their backs, and horns on their heads. Their form was extremely distinct, which was the standard demonic form that humans had in mind.

Others were some oddly-shaped war machines; huge black turtles with sharp teeth, and giant cyclops with black scales all over their face.

There were also devil rays floating in midair, their whole body covered with huge stingers. Each one looked like a balloon, and they could burst out numerous stingers like arrows raining down.

In addition to the various kinds of demons, there were the mercenaries from each major Planes.

Humans and Humanoids had the most in numbers. Garen saw that most of those who rushed past him were Dog-Headed Humans. They were shouting an inflected Draconic Language and waving a chain or a hammer, while some of them had gleams of spells in their hands as the Will of the Abyss fanatically drove them to charge on.

The Blood War was about to come to an end, and the devil’s offense was further repelled. But overall, they still maintained their advantage. If it were not for the Demon Fortress releasing the last batch of huge demons into the battlefield, they probably would have directly stormed through the fortress gate.

“Respected Powerhouse, take out your military merit token. It’s time to reward you according to your accomplishments.” A Demon-Hag floated before Garen and spoke in a sharp voice.

“Lead the way.” Garen smugly glanced at her. Each different Demon Fortress was an independent kingdom. Any powerhouse could become the Thane of Fortress, regardless of race or standpoint. The general Fortress Master was the top powerhouse, at least Level Fourteen.

Level Fourteen and Fifteen were already the culmination of the mortal world, but they could only be the Thane of a small fortress here. This was the Abyss – a bloody land where the sun that was chained up shone upon.

There were even a few hidden demigods here, and there were some Evil Gods and Thanes of Abyss who lived in certain layers of the Abyss. These were the true Gods, not something the mortal existence could compete against.

One must be careful here.

Garen generally knew his own limitations. In the battle with the Devil Warlord, he had already understood that his overall strength should be at about Level Twelve. With the Soul Divine Weapon, Poisonous Eye and et cetera as his trump card, and as long as he was not caught off guard by the Space-Time Spell, he could rely on the fluctuation of spells to forcibly distort and interfere. In this way, he could still manage to reach an unbeaten level.

“Even if I raise both Agility and Intelligence to 180, it probably would be at about Level Thirteen. There’s a massive difference in strength for every level after Level Ten. It would be best to advance myself here and hunt for more devils as Potential Points.” Thoughts were running through Garen’s head.

He had shown his strength, and presumably the Thane of the Demon Fortress here would attach great importance to him.

Led by the Demon-Hag, Garen stepped out of the battlefield and stalked in from the fortress gate that was surrounded by spikes of white bones. Teams of crawling Abyss monsters were transporting the corpses from the battlefield into the fortress to fill up the damaged walls and the gaps in the building.

These giant demons’ form were like the enlarged version of the Skeleton Warriors, except that their bones were much thicker and their body was also five or six meters high. They were full of might.

The corpses were transported by black rays. They fanned their wide wings and dumped the piles of corpses, whether they were devil or demon.

Some black rays began to greedily chew on the corpses before they had finished dumping them.

Teams of well-equipped warriors with two sharp spurs on their backs patrolled inside the fortress. The spurs on their back formed a perfect ring behind their heads, and they looked well-disciplined.

The Demon-Hag took Garen all the way to the highest point of the Fortress.

They passed through an equipment production zone, and in it was full of dwarves, human blacksmiths. There were also many slaves who were cursed and forced to labor there.

They passed through a trade zone and a battle zone.

Very soon, they came to an enormous palace made up of white bones.

The guards were two white-silver statues of more than ten meters high. Leaning over, they studied Garen carefully. After that, they silently moved and let open the entrance.

A little demon with purple skin flew out and took over the task of leading the way for Garen.

“Please come with me, respected Powerhouse.” The Little Demon was a female with a beautiful face. Except for the wings on her back and a long spur-tail, all the other parts had grown into a human woman form.

As soon as he entered the palace, his heart panicked a little.

The Fortress Master at the highest place in the palace was a Skeleton Lich in a red robe. Her eyes flashed red and her hand held her chin to reveal a thoughtful look.

A few guests were seated below, and Kratos was actually among them!

“Welcome, our powerful White Dragon warrior.” Clap, clap, clap…

The Skeleton Lich clapped lightly and had the voice of a dignified and graceful lady.

“As a mercenary who joined the battle out of the blue, Master White Dragon, what kind of reward do you want to compensate your military merits this time?”

Garen glanced at Kratos, who glared at him fiercely from the left, and the two other weird creatures.

One was a black Dog-Headed Human who was discharging black gas all over, while the other had the skin of red clouds and looked like an elemental life form composed of red magma.

Both of these fellows showed a lot of hostility, greed, and bloodthirstiness.

Garen now had some faint understanding on what those above Level Ten centered on.

“Reward?” He withdrew his gaze and looked at the Fortress Master. Before the presence of a powerful Level Fourteen, these fellows should not dare to mess around.

“I want enough souls! High quality souls!”

Kratos’ pupils constricted from the side. The human form he had turned into was a miniature version of a giant beast, and the outer appearance was basically unchanged.

“This fellow is taking advantage of the fact that he has a Soul Divine Weapon that can purify the soul of its impurities. But he can’t directly absorb the soul, so what’s the use of wanting those souls?”

“In any case, capture this fellow first!” Bakiloa transmitted his voice coldly.

“High-quality soul?” The Fortress Master gently locked her white bone-hands together and gave it a thought.

“With your battle achievements, I can give you ten Level Ten-souls, mmm, complete Level-Ten souls, without any damage. In addition, your Level Ten-core was just formed right… It seems to be based on poisons. I will give you a White Bone Giant Pit, which can produce two White Bone Giant Demons every week. If you are willing to join me, I can endow you with your very own personal territory. How’s that? Slaves, wealth, treasure… Whatever is that that you want, you can have it all! I can also supply you with a vast army and let you return to the Primary Plane to take revenge against those enemies who once drove you into the Abyss!”

Garen instantly understood that the other party was recruiting himself.

Glancing at Bakiloa the trio’s surprised expression, his mind suddenly became clear. Obviously, the Fortress Master was using them as a threat and adding on other benefits to tempt him to join her.

He came here to kill and to upgrade himself anyway. It did not matter to him whether he joined the Blood Wars or not.

“Okay, I’m in.”

The Fortress Master giggled.

“How pleasant!” She rubbed her bony hands and began to look at the three fellows on the side with a malicious intent. Kratos’ face immediately turned white. Maffey was slightly nervous, and only Bakiloa was not bothered at all. He was confident that even if his Level-Thirteen strength could not resist the Fortress Master upfront, at most, he would only be seriously injured and could still escape.

But presumably, the Fortress Master would not kill them off just because of that.

It rolled its eyes and hit upon an idea, and it began to snigger too.

“Lady Vengeance, what if we join your Fortress together? Can you meet our conditions?”

“You guys?” Skeleton Lich seemed to feel funny and laughed out loud.

“Bakiloa, I have heard of your reputation long before. You’re capricious. Contract and terms are inherently meaningless to you. Even the Underworld River Contract couldn’t restrain you. Your character changes every Abyss month, who would dare to use you?

“And you, Maffey. Just your enemies alone are enough to give me a headache. Your strength is ordinary, but your fleeing skills are exceptional. Still, you just love to create trouble everywhere.”

She looked at Kratos.

“There’s still you, Kratos, The Thane of Wanku Fortress has already contacted me to send you back quickly. Having you stay here is impossible.”

She spread out her two hands.

“You see, in this way, what good do you guys still have for me? Master Garen, on the other hand, has actually killed numerous devils for me and has played a big role on the battlefield.

“In addition, not to mention the other relationship between him and me…”

Skeleton Lich remarked with some other implication.

“If that’s the case, then we won’t bother anymore.” Bakiloa saw that things could not work out and did not want to speak any nonsense. He was not strong enough to beat the other party, so he could only leave. His body exploded with a boom and disappeared from the same spot.

Maffey snickered and disappeared next. It was just their projection that was present. Which individual in the Abyss was not cunning and cautious?

Kratos gave a hateful look at Garen as he knew that there was no other way now. Having also feuded and made an enemy for no reason, he was feeling unusually frustrated and chose to leave as well.

Only the Skeleton Lich and Garen were left in the White Bone Grand Hall.

“Garen, is Ann doing well?” The Skeleton Lich suddenly opened her mouth and mentioned a name that somewhat stunned Garen.

“You! …?” He cautiously narrowed his eyes. “How do you know that I am associated with Ann?”

The Skeleton Lich suddenly laughed.

“How do I know? When I was studying the Arcane Technique with Ann, I’m afraid even your mother wasn’t born yet!”

This fellow’s aura suddenly changed and the entire body actually emitted a horrific aura as profound as that of a black hole.

This force enveloped the entire grand hall. It was even vaster than the ocean and more magnificent than the sky, and there were countless black smoky human-faces flying in it, which were exactly the same black smoky human-faces as those in Ann’s Abyss.

Seeing this, Garen believed immediately. This kind of black smoky human faces could only have come from Ann.

“Dragon of Disaster…” he murmured.

“Yes… This is just one of my incarnations.” The Skeleton Lich answered with a smile. “My real body is hidden in a certain dark layer of the Abyss, while I usually just use this identity to move around on the outside.”

Chapter 1327: Anti-Summons 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dragons of Disaster was a code name for a group.

Most of them were at least demigods, because demigods could take advantage of people’s fears and draw strength from them to strengthen themselves.

Dragons of Disaster, as the name suggested, was to create disasters so that all lives would fear them, enabling them to gain more Fear-Power.

Ann was one of the three Monarchs, and now it seemed that this Fortress Master Lady Vengeance should be one of Ann’s students.

Garen slightly tested the other party’s understanding of Ann, and soon he began to relax. She was even clear about the place where Ann was now at.

Since it was completely confirmed, Garen felt at home with the other party. He told of the reason he was banished as there was nothing to hide about it.

“You’re really unlucky.” Lady Vengeance shook her head, and the red light in her eyes showed a trace of sympathy.

“I think so too,” Garen said helplessly. “Had it not been the necklace of the Dragons of Disaster trying to protect me, it wouldn’t have been exposed. If it were exposed anywhere else outside the city, it will not stimulate the Matrix Spirit of Snow City. That is to say, this series of chain reactions led me to this state that I’m currently in.”

“So what plans do you have? Is it just to stay here and be a general at my place, or…?” Lady Vengeance said, “To be honest, I personally hope that you’ll stay. I have just recently seized this fortress and haven’t gained a firm foothold yet. So as you’ve seen, even the Devil’s Army almost broke through to my door.”

“Sure. Anyway, I was just thinking of participating in the Blood Wars for a longer period of time and obtaining more souls.” Garen nodded.

“Alright then. I’ll just appoint you as the Deputy Fortress Master. You can form an army by yourself. Whether it’s made up of mercenaries or demons, it’s all up to you. You can freely obtain the materials from the warehouse.” Lady Vengeance was very trusting of Garen.

“Aren’t you afraid that I will take the things and leave?” Garen felt slightly strange.

“There’s nothing to be afraid of. The necklace on your body will enable Ann and us to find you at any time.” Lady Vengeance revealed a cunning smile.

Even though Garen did not know how he read this kind of emotion off a skeleton’s face.

“Ok…”

Garen had not expected things to have taken a new turn.

However, his current strength that was comparable to Level Twelve and was not considered too low to be a Deputy Fortress Master.

“It’s just that we’re now like generals without an army, so you have to go recruit more manpower.” Lady Vengeance scattered a vast amount of white luminous powder with a whoosh. The powder fell on the ground, turned into a round arch door, and a tall red skin demon with horns walked out of it.

This fellow was like a tall blacksmith, and his muscles were all bulky, like a magnified version of a male human. Its chest muscles were inlaid with a black round gemstone, and a faint roar like that of a bear could be heard coming out of it.

“Miss. What have you summoned me for?” The bullhorn-demon asked presumptuously.

“Bilu, this is Lord Garen, the deputy commander who has just joined us. Since you are also a deputy commander, you should get acquainted with him in the future.” Lady Vengeance pointed to Garen.

The demon named Bilu glanced at Garen his eyes and studied him seriously.

The strength that emanated from Garen’s muscles immediately caught his senses.

“Welcome aboard.” He stepped forward, walked over to Garen and extended out his hands.

Garen stretched out his claw and held his hand.

Sizz!!

The two thick arms exerted a great force, and Bilu’s entire body’s strength was activated. The blood vessels on his whole body was bulging. Looking up, he saw that there was no change in Garen’s complexion, who was still carrying the same faint smile.

“Terrific!” He took the initiative to let go of his strength.

Garen also followed suit.

“There’s still much to learn from you. Please teach and guide me in the future,” he said modestly.

“Rest assured!”

“Alright. Now that you two have met each other, our Vengeance Fortress will have to rely on your support. I normally will only come out to assume personal command when it’s the crucial Great Blood Wars period. The usual times will have to rely on you all.”

Garen understood the Great Blood Wars she mentioned. It was not all large-scale investment in the Blood War every time but usually just small-scale killing. After a while, a great company would be dispatched for the decisive battle. At this time, there would even be the presence of those above Level Ten.

Generally, there were only Level Eight or Nine at most.

After that, Garen stayed in the Vengeance Fortress. With his relationship with Ann, Lady Vengeance seemed to trust him very much, and almost all the affairs were handed over to him and Bilu.

Bilu was a Level Thirteen forged elder demon, which was a branch of the Balor Demons. There was a large number of Tanar’ri little demons and Demonic Behemoths under his command, and they were also his assault elites. There were also some mercenaries who had just recently joined him.

After Garen came aboard, he acquired the control of a group of miscellaneous army and the control of three Dimensional Random Teleportation Portals.

The purpose of the Dimensional Random Teleportation Portal was to randomly recruit mercenaries who could potentially appear on the Outer Plane.

Sometimes, it was some hapless fellow who accidentally entered the Abyss when the teleportation failed; while some other times, it was some idiot who was framed by others and was teleported here.

Most of those in the army were practitioners who took the initiative to participate in the Blood Wars. Their strength level was uneven, but the lowest was Level Four. Nonetheless, Level Four in the Abyss was equivalent to a little demon, which belonged to the vulnerable group and was only slightly stronger than the Demon Maggots.

The Dimensional Random Teleportation Portal was the first source of conscription.

The second was that the demons would gather at each layers to help out and participate in the Blood Wars. This was the strategy decided by the masters of each abyssal layers. The Abyssal Layer Masters were the famous Thanes of Abyss from all of the Planes, and they were not someone the Thanes of Fortress could not compare with. Most of them were the lower Divine Power Level, and the stronger ones could even compare with the powerful Gods. The span was enormous. Moreover, their status and authority had been acknowledged by the Will of the Abyss, and they had a lot of mysterious and unknown abilities.

This part was not managed by the Fortress Masters, but they could fight for these armies’ battlefields to join with their Fortress.

Garen’s second source of conscription was to fight for the cantonment of these armies.

The third was the edge of the Underworld River.

That was where the famous Demon Larvae were. During the seasons, both sides of the Underworld River would have a vast number of foolish creatures and souls that died from pursuing evil.

Under the development of the Underworld River and the Power of Abyss, these souls would gradually turn into cocoons and then break out from it, becoming the demons’ favorite food – larvae.

Larvae were usually born not even reaching Level One. Apart from their sharp teeth and tone, even an ordinary human soldier could kill them.

However, as they devoured and killed each other to evolve, their level of strength would gradually increase. At the same time, they would evolve into different kinds of demons according to geographical factors and other conditions.

This was the largest and most important source of conscription. Vengeance Fortress occupied thousands of square kilometers of the Underworld River Plain, and half the area was also divided to Garen.

These were the basis of the three major sources of troops, and one could recruit high-level generals and cannon fodder. After learning about the situation, Garen roamed about the Vengeance Fortress.

The Forging Department was managed by an old gray dwarf man, who was a slave to Lady Vengeance. In addition to working hard to survive, he could not escape due to the power of the contract.

For the Logistics Department, a Six-Armed Snake-Demon was in charge of it. This fellow was greedy and lascivious. He was also responsible for the distribution of the slaves captured from the war. Before Garen had made any moves, this fellow was sensible enough to take the initiative to curry favor with him.

The rest of the little generals on patrol were a mess, often killing each other and switching. Garen could not be bothered to pay any attention to them at all, but familiarized himself with the main characters.

After that, he went directly to the Cultivation Room assigned to him. It was a large floating building, just behind the right side of the Fortress. On the edge was the Fortress’ Pillar of Fire that was never out.

The Pillar of Fire rose to the sky, like a plume penetrating the clouds, and it was surrounded by a large number of protective runes. There were also many wizard slaves working hard to repair and maintain the Rune Matrix.

Garen’s house was a white, cold villa that looked like a birthday cake.

He shrunk his body size and flew in from the main door. There were already two Succubus with a long tails kneeling on the ground to pay their respects.

“Welcome back, Master!” Except for the tail, the two Succubus looked almost similar to the pretty ladies of a human beings. Their skin was tanned, their figures were smoking hot, their long hair were loose, and their hips were slightly raised, giving off an infinite temptation of sexiness. Coupled with their natural charm, which was a kind of spell, theirs were radiating their magnetism all the time. That was why this kind of creature was a kind of resource goods in the Abyss.

It was noted that these two Succubus were above Level Five. As a biological tool for seduction, this level was very high. Obviously, they were carefully selected by the Six-Armed Snake-Demon from logistics.

However, Garen did not really appreciate this kind of creature very much. Due to his former identity, he preferred purebred humans.

Shrinking his size, he flew in from the main door. A large number of dark blue crystal lights automatically lit up on the inside.

A variety of furniture were available, and the most prominent of which was a large collection of jewels and gemstones of various colors placed at the center.

When Garen saw this, even though he knew that the value of these things were not that great, but because of his Dragon Clan’s nature, his mood was still quickly brightened up.

What surprised him was that there were three familiar figures tied up in a corner and could not move.

They were actually the three Blasphemy Knights who were previously captured by him.

“It’s you again!!” The male knight glared at Garen.

“Master, this is the contract of the three slaves.” From the side, a Succubus wiggled its waist and gently leaned on Garen, handing a black leather paper roll.

Garen took it and skimmed through the contents. It was a Soul Contract which was written in the Demonic Language, and it was nothing more than a stipulation that these three guys could never betray him.

“Then again, I’m a male. What do I want males for?” Garen also felt that the male Blasphemy Knight was an eyesore.

With a wave of his hand, the male knight’s contract was thrown to the Succubus. “Take it to the logistics and sell this fellow. I don’t need any species other than female humans and elves.”

“You!!”

“Don’t!!” The female knight, Irene, begged. “I beg you, don’t sell off big brother!”

“Irene, don’t beg. Isn’t it just re-selling again? At this point, what else is there to be afraid of!?” The male knight was strong-willed.

The other female knight simpered however.

“I’d be very happy to serve such a strong powerhouse like Lord White Dragon.”

“Shameless!”

“What is there to be shameless about? It’s just to live a better life.”

“Even if we fall, we would not be called a knight if we break the Cavaliers’ principle!!” Irene argued.

“Rena! I can’t believe you are such a person!” The male knight showed a disdainful look.

“Alright, alright. At this point, everything is up to me.” Garen walked over, grabbed Irene and looked whimsically at her.

Although she was wearing a dirty knight armor, it still could not stop Garen’s savage sight.

She felt that her entire body was seen clearly as though she was not wearing any clothes.

“Aptitude is good. You can be a seed.”

Chapter 1328: Anti-Summons 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen advanced toward Rena. He also picked her up and sized her up; breasts, buttocks, waist, body figure, muscle tone, and face.

“Your aptitude is not bad too, and even better still. It’s amazing…” At first, Garen thought that Irene, with such an upright and pure personality, might have a better aptitude, but he did not expect Rena, who was so afraid of death, to be better.

The male knight on the side had been dragged out by a Succubus to the Logistics Department.

Garen did not care whether the two knights were loyal to him. He just wanted to have some subordinates whom he could temporarily dispatch for errands.

What was more, Dragons were salacious creatures. It should be time for him to release his long suppressed instinct.

The problem now was that the Wizard Tower must be built as soon as possible. Unfortunately, his plans could not keep up with the changes as he was suddenly banished. It would be very risky if he were to return to the Main Plane to build the Wizard Tower.

“I’ll just build it here then since there’s Lady Vengeance’s support, and she’s also partly considered as my senior sister. There’re also a lot of materials in the Abyss. As long as I have power, I can just wantonly plunder.”

Garen’s mind was made up.

Although he had a way to deal with the Space-Time Spell, the Ultimate Transformation Spell still made him feel very excited. After all, he had long been used to being a human, and changing back to that form would be much more convenient.

Settling down at the residence, there were various slave-chefs who made different dishes from different Planes. Garen had eaten frozen meat for so long, and finally, he could refine his diet. He chose two human chefs to bake cakes and cook meals for him.

The interior of the house was consolidated with Space Spell, and so although it did not look big, the interior was large enough to accommodate several football fields, which was very spacious.

The Logistics Department sent the chefs, servants and other manpower responsible for chores.

After Garen organized all the work in the Fortress, he decided to go and visit the ground of his three major sources of conscription.

He first headed to the Dimensional Random Teleportation Portal.

This was the place to recruit advanced warriors and generals. According to the demons’ style, they would disregard whether it was a wizard warrior or monster that was teleported over and have a fight first. If they could beat the other party, the latter would become their slave. Otherwise, they would grant them the right for a dialogue at an equal level.

Unlike the devils who liked to trade with the creatures, demons primarily used force.

Garen flew for a while, spent more than ten minutes flitting through most parts of the Fortress, and soon descended beside three round luminous spheres like that of white marshmallows.

At the edge of the luminous spheres, there were three Level-Five Wizards releasing a steady fluctuation of Arcane Technique. A large number of elder demon guards were patrolling and staying alert on the outer layer.

When the three Level-Five Wizards saw Garen flying over, they retracted their hands that were releasing a purple arc and bowed to Garen.

“We pay tribute to Third Commander.”

Garen was the third-ranking commander, and the news of his appointment had directly spread throughout the Fortress.

“Resume your work. I’m here to see my three portals.” Garen gently landed on the ground and circled around the three luminous spheres.

“Third Commander, the creatures that teleported through these three portals are inconsistent. Sometimes it’s a one-time group, while sometimes there’s not even one creature in more than a month. This depends on luck.” An old Wizard reported nervously.

If it were not for their knowledge of stabling the Dimensional Matrix, they, who were merely Level Five, would become targets that were preyed on and could be eaten up unknowingly.

“Are there any ways to be more proactive?” Garen asked.

“Of course,” the old Wizard replied. “We can send out demons that are powerful enough through the portal to respond to those demons’ Summoning Spell. Generally, if the Summoner’s contract has a loophole, or the cost isn’t enough, the demon can seize the opportunity to break out of the Matrix’s restraint and capture the Summoner to the Abyss instead to become a slave.

“This is one method. Another one is to have someone with great ability to directly enter the Void to capture the randomly teleporting wanderers. Many travelers from various Planes will encounter a variety of crises, and thus get lost in the Void and cannot find the right direction, so…”

“Understood…” Garen nodded. He was currently in urgent need of a few men at his disposal. “I’m going to try the second method, responding to the summons and capturing the Summoner.”

He was aware of the schemes in this regard.

In the Main Substance Plane, such legends were often circulated.

In order to retaliate or for some cruel reasons, an aristocrat who did not have any foundation in Spellcrafting would use their own blood to engrave the Demon Summoning Matrix to actually summon an extremely powerful horrific demon to massacre a whole territory. He himself would also gain a mighty evil power.

This was actually the second way to summon.

It was not the Summoner who was having the initiative, but the demons in the Abyss who was responding on their own accord. Some of them were eyeing the well-to-do aristocrat’s resources in their territory, while some were targeting the huge negative energy of hatred they bore on them, and some were there for other reasons. Anyway, each had their own plans.

Garen intended to learn from these seniors.

He went around a few rounds and carefully observed the three teleportation portals. As he was about to leave and enter the portal, he felt a slight jump in his body all of a sudden.

The Enneahedron that was almost forgotten by him was actually beating at this time.

He looked at the Enneahedron, only to find that this thing was actually beginning to swim under his skin, and the inside seemed to have absorbed a lot of bloody red mist.

He suddenly remembered the large number of devils that he had just slaughtered in the Blood War. He originally thought that those low-level devils were useless to him, but he did not expect that the Enneahedron would snatch those souls.

“I wonder how much help this thing can be to me.” Garen had some anticipation and let it do its own activities.

Before responding to the summons, he decide to go obtain the reward he was entitled to first.

He went straight to the Logistics Department.

The Six-Armed Snake-Demon had long prepared the souls.

He brought out a team of ten complete human souls from a grayish white tent.

Each of these ten souls was almost like a living person, and there was not any sign at all that they were souls. Indeed, as Lady Vengeance had said, they were extremely whole.

Moreover, the soul fluctuations they released were indeed Level Ten.

“The ten souls are warriors, assassins, wizards and warlocks. There are the races of White Elves, Half-Elves, humans, which were all personally chosen by you. But to be honest, the human souls are not the best-selling ones.”

The Six-Armed Snake-Demon waved its six arms, indicating a few little demons on the side to bring out another group of slave-souls.

That was a group of standard Drows. Each Drows had a chain locked around their neck like a dog. They were all female, and some kind of saliva-like mucus was dripping from the edge of their mouth, looking as if they were tamed until they had lost their mind. However, seeing their curvy body figure, delicate skin and seductive posture, even Garen could not help but be slightly tempted.

These Drows were exceptionally beautiful, and there were innocent-looking ones, charming ones, peaceful ones, and sexy ones. Various styles were available.

“How do they look? They’re also Level Ten-souls, and their bodies can be reconstructed once they’re thrown into the Blood Pool.” The Six-Armed Snake-Demon snickered sinisterly. “The most important thing is that these Level Ten-Drows here are all well-taught and tamed. They can comply with you to do all kinds of tricks. Their physiques are good, so they won’t be easily battered, and they will loyally protect you and guard your safety, just like dogs! Hehehe.”

“Forget it, I still want the original team.” Garen resisted the temptation in his heart and stuck to his choice. What he wanted was efficiency, to have the talents that could really help him get things done, not bodyguards and playthings.

“Well, if Commander wants them, you can come to me at any time. The slaves here are the property of Lady Vengeance, so you only need to pay a hundred soul-cocoons in exchange for a Drow-slave. The price is cheap, absolutely reasonable!”

Garen shook his head. Naturally, he would not believe a word the Six-Armed Snake-Demon said.

Taking with him the new team of Level Ten-souls, Garen went to the Blood Pool at the Logistics Department. After spending some cost and almost using up all his valuable possessions, only then did the bodies of the ten Level Ten-souls were reconstructed. It was nothing more than a simple reconstruction of a low-level body this time, and they would still need to re-enhance themselves step by step again. But since they were originally a Level Ten-soul, and their soul energy, knowledge and memory were still present, the process of re-enhancing would be relatively fast.

The expressions of the ten souls were all indifferent as if there was nothing to live for, and every part of their body was inlaid with a special rune that would make them obey Garen completely. Being subjected to someone as such, no one would be able to see any hope no matter how powerful one could become. Naturally, they would have little to none motivation to continue strive on.

What Garen did not expect was that the load of controlling such ten souls actually occupied half of his soul’s Spirit Power. Even he, the Void Demon Lord who was the most powerful and the expert in regards to the soul, was at this kind of state, not to mention the other demons.

It was no wonder that no one in the Fortress used this kind of method to control a large number of powerhouses.

The load required for this was too great.

Temporarily leaving the souls in his residence, Garen once again flew back to the Dimensional Random Teleportation Portal.

After offering a greeting, he officially flew directly into one of the portals.

Countless Summoning Wills pounced on him like a spider web. In the endless white light, Garen carefully chose. Because his fame had not spread to other Planes, so the ones he received were those with no specific targets, which was the summoning of Abyss Demons using the extensive Summoning Matrix.

Only when he had become famous could he teleport to other Planes, and that there would be people specifically summoning him with his name. At that time, he would not be suppressed by the strength of the Plane. At the same time, there would be an additional summoning-protection ability, which meant that in the process of summoning, his power would be transmitted, and the Power of Abyss would also help him to form a protection against the Matrix, so as to avoid the interruption of the summoning process. When he became even more powerful, he could also enchant and summon the surrounding creatures faraway to protect the Matrix from interference.

Of course this was much later.

What he needed to do now was to first find the one he wanted to choose from the countless Summoning Wills.

“The strength must not be too weak, and the scope has to be more active. Can’t be too rigid, and there shouldn’t be a too strong suppression force around…” Garen carefully deliberated.

After all, some of the top Wizards would also use the demon’s kind of Anti-Summons during their experiment to deceive and seduce the demons to go forward, and then immediately use the Restraint Matrix to capture them for experiments. This was also extremely dangerous. Once the wrong choice was made, he would not even know where he would die at.

Chapter 1329: : Layout 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!

Garen grabbed a white spider-silk and tugged at it fiercely.

The extremely-slender silk was actually much tougher than a steel wire, as it did not snap with such a violent pull.

Garen followed the stretch of this spider-silk quickly, and the entire dragon-body moved like a flowing liquid.

Soon, he saw a large circular hole suspended in the white space. The big hole led to a room that was like an aristocrat’s study room.

A deathly pale young man with blood all over him was lying on the floor. It seemed that he was losing too much blood. An unparalleled resentment was rising from his body, and this resentment was even almost condensing into a tangible black gas.

“I… Andrew Gordra, vowed here… even if I have to give my soul, will never ever let the Malone Household acquire Gordra!!!”

The young aristocrat’s resentment had reached an extremely horrific point. Garen did not know what hatred had brought him to this state, but this did not prevent him from responding to the summons.

If such a soul could be transformed into an Undead, it might be a good helping hand to him.

This fellow, with his strength around Level Seven, was a standard Silver-Striped Knight. He was poisoned with some incurable poison so the body was of no value, but the soul was still at Level Seven.

Garen shook his body and moved in through the hole.

His body slowly formed in the study and quickly condensed from the platinum liquid into a ferocious White Dragon that was slightly taller than a person.

“I heard your summon and your appeal from the Vengeance Fortress. In accordance with the ancient contract, I will fulfil your desire. In return, your soul shall belong to me forever.”

Garen loudly chanted the standard Divine Power Notes of the Contract Matrix.

The young aristocrat in front finally showed some pain and delight from the revenge he was about to get out of hatred.

“Kill… Kill everyone…! This is my only wish…”

Garen leaned down and stared into the other party’s eyes.

“Your wish is my command.”

His voice had just faltered.

A bloody red three-dimensional rune suddenly emerged between the man and the dragon. The rune was like a token, and it rotated several times before instantly blasting into bloody red luminous spots and dissipating.

Garen waved his wings and took out a Soul Crystal. The young man’s soul floated out of his body, turned into a cloud of white smoke, and wormed into the crystal.

After this, only then did he scan around the room.

Although the study was full of aristocratic furnishings, they were extremely shabby and ancient. It was apparent that there were only a few books on the shelf, and the desk had accumulated a thick layer of dust.

“Poor little fellow.” Garen looked at the young man. If the Level Seven-soul were to be assimilated into the Abyss, coupled with this huge resentment, perhaps after being transformed into an Undead, his strength could increase to Level Eight. Entering Level Eight as such a young age, the potential was beyond measure.

“I’ll just treat it as doing you a favor.”

“Damn it! Who snatched my pawn!!” Suddenly, there was a scream of anger from the hole behind him.

There obviously was another Abyss existence that wanted to seize this soul.

“Get lost!” Garen impatiently flapped his wings, and a horrific Level Twelve-strength instantly slammed at the hole, pushing back the fluctuations of the strength that was about to spurt out.

The Level Ten-existence over that side immediately quite down and did not dare to speak a word. But for sure, there would be full of resentment. A Level Twelve-existence actually came over to fight with him, a Level Ten, for a Level Seven-soul. This was simply shameless, alright!?

Garen ignored all these.

He beat his wings and flew off.

Boom!!

The ceiling above was smashed by him, and a dark ice barrier formed by a mixture of frost and negative energy floated around his entire body. This barrier blocked all the dust and dirt on the outside.

Garen charged upward, slammed through the first floor, and darted out of the two-story building. His surrounding was finally an open space.

He had rushed into a vast area from a small space in a flash.

Surrounded by a vast expanse of forest, he was at the top of an ancient blue-grey castle. The fort tip of the ancient castle was shattered by him, and it slowly slanted toward the left and fell.

Horrifying human screams were heard coming from the castle beneath.

“It’s a giant dragon!! The evil White Dragon Clan!!”

“No! That’s not an ordinary White Dragon. It’s an Abyss White Dragon!!”

An old Wizard looked up at Garen in despair from the inside of the castle.

Soldiers gathered, longbows and giant crossbows were set up, and giant arrows with special enchanting luster were fixed on them.

Several Silver-Striped Knights had silver armor on them, and they clustered around a tall knight in a platinum armor, as they rode their battle-horses and galloped over from a distance.

“Dare to destroy the Grand Duke of Gordra’s castle, even if you’re the Dragon Clan, you still have to pay the price with your life!!” The leading platinum-knight roared. The giant sword on his back slowly glowed a faint golden light, as was he as he pulled it out and held it in his hand, he was like a god descending to the world.

Garen flew in the air above the castle and overlooked the bottom, as if watching countless small ants gathering and using a variety of weapons to challenge him.

“The grand duke of a remote little country?” He immediately spotted the specificity of the situation here.

The desire of the Summoner was to kill everyone, and the scope should be within the territory.

“Resolve it quickly.” Garen was now a truly powerful existence in the Abyss. The combat power of Level Twelve could be counted as a massive disaster in any place.

“How to resolve it?” Garen was slightly bemused. All his combat power was focused on melee combat, and it was not very useful for this kind of extensive destruction.

However, the contract still had to be fulfilled, otherwise he could not get the soul of that Summoner which had a great potential.

Scratching his head a little, Garen suddenly felt his wings were touched by many furry things.

He looked down and saw that the giant crossbows and giant bows had shot out numerous sharp arrows and bolts at his wings. The little itchiness he felt from just now was caused by these things.

“How about this.”

With a thought, his hind foot slowly fell off and automatically transformed into a sturdy and tall man with long dark blue hair.

“I’m willing to serve you.” The man had no face, and a vast dark blue chill spread around him.

“I leave it to you… Destroy the entire territory,” Garen said plainly.

The man nodded and flew up high into the air.

Whish!!

Suddenly, he released an enormous dark blue light, and his whole body completely turned into a gigantic blue light ball, releasing stunning blue lights in all directions.

Garen looked up at this fellow and had no idea how he planned to do it. But, he was transformed from his own right hind leg and had the highest peak strength of the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique. His strength was only a little weaker than his own Level Twelve-combat power and was equivalent to Level Eleven.

With such strength, the destruction of a grand duke’s territory in a remote country should not be difficult.

Looking at the massive blue ball that broke out overhead, Garen watched quietly to see what this fellow planned to do.

Whish whish whish…

In the gigantic light ball, countless densely packed ferocious blue frost halberds of various shapes suddenly shot out.

Each of these halberds flew out in high speed, like a cannonball firing into the distance, and slammed into the ground.

The area that was smashed directly erupted huge clouds of hemispherical blue bubbles. The places covered with the bubble halo were all condensing a thick tough ice.

“Meteorology Manipulation?” Garen recalled that at the great completion of the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, there would be a supernatural ability, which was Meteorology Manipulation.

He looked up at the sky, and it was all black clouds. The temperature suddenly took a dive from more than twenty degrees Celsius, and pale blue snow fluttered down.

Fierce shouting were heard coming from the little people and horses below.

When the snowflakes landed on them, they could immediately feel an intense chill from the depths of their hearts.

The halberds were still bursting out of the light ball. Dozens of halberds were flying out every second, turning a regional forest into a world of ice and snow.

“Gordra!” Suddenly, a golden figure shot up from below, roaring the name of the territory and rushing to Garen’s chest, who was circling at the top of the castle.

The golden sword clenched in his hand was stabbed at Garen’s heart like a golden lightning.

“Stupid.” Garen did not make any move, but let him lunge upward to fiercely stab him with the sword at the dragon scale at his heart.

Clang!!

In the tremendously dull crashing sound, the figure convulsed, and the enormous reaction force caused blood trails to emerge all over his body. All his skin erupted, and a vast amount of blood sprayed out and spattered down.

There was not a trace left on Garen’s dragon scale on the other hand.

“Merely a Level Eight-knight…” Garen’s complexion did not change. With his current physique, even if his internal organs were severely damaged, they could also recover by themselves in a very short time.

His 180-point of physique brought him an absolutely unparalleled terrific recovery strength and defense.

Even the Ancient Dragon’s body was far from his current body. Perhaps only the legendary Three-Headed Golden Dragon Kings was likely to have the physical strong that could match him.

This golden figure was obviously the thane here. His attack failed and was seriously injured instead. This instantly caused the morale of the entire castle that was just mustered up to suddenly collapse.

Large groups of soldiers fled and dispersed.

“It’s basically a massacre.” Garen had no interest in this kind of dull matters. He dully flew down to the castle, where there was a pathway connecting to the Abyss Plane.

“Looks like I can just leave this kind of boring matters to them in the future.” Garen felt that he should use all three of his incarnations.

An immense blue chill blanketed the territory. Wherever it reached, all the escaping soldiers gradually slowed down, and their whole body would be covered with a faint blue.

Soon their blood was frozen, and each of them frozen in their original postures and trapped on the same spot.

The blue chill was like a life form as the cold wind whizzed past with an eerie low pitch. The entire castle was completely frozen into an ice sculpture by the tremendous chill in less than a few minutes.

Inside the castle, Garen’s gigantic dragon body slowly descended in front of the hole. He turned his head and spit out a Dragon Breath.

Whoosh…

The huge Dragon Breath was like a white smoke-cloud. It instantly rushed out of the study, turned into countless white stars and scattered around, adding a layer of frozen chill to the entire castle. At the same time, it also brought along Garen’s very own Abyss imprint.

This was to mark this place as his handiwork and territory. Since he was related to Ann the Dragon of Disaster, Garen also decided to simply do something associated with the Dragons of Disaster.

After doing all this, Garen then turned around and wormed into the hole, quickly disappearing.

Chapter 1330: Layout 2

Chapter 1330: Layout 2

The Death Sigh, or as some places called it, the Winter Sigh, and the name of Snake Dorsum White Dragon quickly spread in a remote small country in the southwest.

The fame of the Death White Dragon’s Winter Sigh spread extremely fast, and for this reason, the Central Empire Wizards’ Guild officially issued a statement – to designate the Deputy Commander of the Vengeance Fortress, Snake Dorsum White Dragon Garen as a Catastrophic Level-Dragon of Disaster.

Having the ability to freeze the entire tens of thousands of square kilometers of the duke’s territory within half an hour, Garen’s strength had reached an extensive strategic level.

The Central Wizards’ Guild together with the Northern Snow City confirmed that this Garen was the White Dragon Garen whom they originally banished.

The disaster this time caused more than sixteen thousand deaths and over two hundred thousand injuries, so it was classified as the ‘Deep Blue Freeze’ incident.

Garen’s calamity title, Winter Sigh, was completely set, and was listed on the Dragons of Disaster’s official list.

************************

Snow City

Soaring Wing King stood at the observation deck at the top of the lofty Wizard Tower and gazed at the panoramic view of the entire Snow City in the distance. Snow descended slowly and glided past his beard and hair.Find authorized novels in ，faster updates, better experience，Please click www.webnovel.com for visiting.

He was dressed in a white robe and behind him stood a young man in a black cloak.

The chimes of the giant clock at noon slowly sounded from the distance. Several huge Airships gradually rose from Snow City and turned about to fly away.

“He actually survived the Blood War,” Soaring Wing King remarked.

“Yes, Teacher, and the so-called General Guild has officially classified Deep Blue Sigh as a Dragon of Disaster. You might be criticized for sending him into the Blood Wars back then.” The young man was a little worried.

“It’s just a so-called General Guild.” Soaring Wing King was not bothered. “Submitting to the Gods, away from the real path of Arcane Technique. Don’t worry. I have my own plans.”

“Then Victor will retire.” The young man bowed his head and said respectfully.

“Go, everything will be done according to the original arrangement.”

“Yes.”

After waiting for the young man to leave, Soaring Wing King retracted his gaze from the distance and extended his right hand. A transparent crystal ball slowly emerged from his palm.

“It seems that I really didn’t misjudge you.” He sighed in a low voice, turned around and slowly walked into the Wizard Tower, looking like an ordinary and debilitated old man.

A few years passed in a trice.

Garen had participated five times in the Blood Wars in the Abyss, killing and acquiring numerous souls every time.

The only regret was that his Potential Points had been completely depleted and could only be supplemented by various Demon Cores and high-concentration compounds, which did not have a very high efficiency. During these five years, he would also convert the Soul Energy that was produced in him every month into Potential Points.

He had gotten almost 1100 Potential Points.

The Enneahedron was also enhanced to the point where its color of red was almost black. It seemed to be close to saturation, and Garen did not know what would reaction it would have next.

His current focus was to replenish all the other two attributes. The first to be completed was Agility. Although Intelligence was becoming insufficient, it did not interfere with the development of his overall strength.

Agility was promoted to the limit of 180, while Intelligence was only up to 90 points due to the deficiency of Potential Points.

At this point, all of Garen’s strength had almost reached the limit of a Middle-level Demon Lord, completely restoring his original peak power, except for the Void Original Opus that was still stuck at 70%. There was almost no room for improvement for the rest.

After reincarnating for so many times, all the accumulation of past experiences were almost completely transformed into strength, which was now reflected in this world.

The enhancement of Agility to the limit of 180 did not just bring Garen an increase in speed. The speed limit of this world was 100 points, and upon reaching it, Garen naturally acquired a special ability – Flash. This ability did not consume any Spells, Spirit Power, nor Soul Energy, but only the exhaustion of physical strength. Just like sprinting all the way, although it was merely a physical movement, yet he could reach the point of short-distance space penetration.

The simple increase in speed naturally evolved into this ability. Garen had also discovered that there were natural weird symbols faintly appearing on his scales.

Obviously, this was something that was naturally derived after reaching the limit of the law of the Plane.

Every time he flashed, he could span a distance of a hundred meters, which was the maximum degree after Agility reached 180 points.

Upon reaching Level Ten, the cores that were present would form a type of special spell or special ability or strength that was completely unique to one’s self.

Taking Soaring Wing King as example, his core ability was related to his nickname.

There was also Lady Vengeance, of whom her core strength was to wreak vengeance. As long as the target of hatred was identified, the Vengeance Imprint would be in effect, so that once the target appeared in front of her, any disguise would be of no use. And if the other party’s level was lower than hers, they would then be weakened by the imprint’s oppression, and all their attributes and level would be reduced. It was extremely terrifying.

Meanwhile, some of the powerhouses above Level Ten also each had their own nicknames. For instance, the Storm Judge, the Earth Chant, the Radiance of God, and so on.

These nicknames were actually the embodiment of their core strengths, which was unique to them.

Many of the strengths were derived from the strengthening of the original spells and abilities, and Garen also intended to strengthen himself from this aspect.

He now had Flash and the Poisonous Eye as his ability and talent.

Especially the Poisonous Eye; upon its release after the completion of its charge, the power could almost threaten the existence of a Level Thirteen, which was particularly terrifying.

When Garen exchanged moves with the other deputy commander, this ability almost stripped off a layer of the opponent’s skin. If the other party had not reacted fast enough and instantly shed its skin, that party probably would have taken the hit and would have badly injured its vitality.

At the same time, this also reflected the horrific force of this ability of Garen’s.

A near-perfect horror, coupled with the special talents, Flash and the Poisonous Eye, Garen’s strength was getting closer to that of Lady Vengeance and truly matching the position of being the Vengeance Fortress’ third hand.

**********************

“This year’s Underworld River Wind is about to develop.” Garen settled in his own Fortress and mentioned with his eyes half-opened.

In the vast white cold space, there was nothing around, not even any furnishings. Only a huge knight in a dark blue armor half-knelt in front of Garen.

The knight was covered in thick ferocious armor, and on the shoulders, head, elbows and other joints were sharp and vicious barbed thorns everywhere. A twisted dragon pattern was vaguely seen illuminating gradually with a light blue shimmer on its chest.

“Yes, Master. It is time to collect the soul-cocoons, and perhaps there’ll be some Demon Seeds with excellent qualifications.” The knight answered in a deep voice.

“Andrew.” Garen’s gaze fell on the knight. “In just five years, your strength has improved from your initial Level Seven to Level Nine. Regarding your talent, even I can’t help but to marvel at it. But…”

His tone shifted.

“You’ve now been stuck at this level for two years. Not only there was no improvement in your strength, there’s even some regression.”

“I’m sorry…” Andrew’s head bowed even lower, feeling ashamed.

“Back then, I was satisfied with your hatred and completely destroyed the Gordra Household. This had cut off all your encumbrance, but it has also made you lose the opportunity to perceive more positive things,” Garen said lightly.

“I don’t understand.” Andrew’s eyebrows knitted together slightly under his helmet.

“You’ll understand sooner or later,” Garen replied with a deeper implication to it. “Now, I have a new task to hand over to you.”

He looked at this capable aide of his for these past few years, and his heart was gratified. With the presence of the few capable aides he had trained in the past few years, he was able to have more time for his own cultivation.

Andrew was one of them, and there were also the two Blasphemy Knights who were captured back then. Among them, Rena the female knight had also advanced to Level Seven. Being able to reach this point from the initial low level, she was also considered a very terrific talent. On the other hand, Irene was only Level Six. Even with the large supply of resources, she had not been able to advance quicker, and this showed that her aptitude was indeed worse.

Garen and the three had signed the highest level Underground River Oath, so he was not at all worried about them betraying him.

Only Andrew’s strength was considered the finest among the three assets. The rest were just using their brains to deal with trivial things, while Andrew could be put in an important position.

So this time, as Garen himself had to leave for an important matter, he decided to hand over the task of recruiting to Andrew. In these past few years, through the three major sources of conscription, Garen had recruited more than a dozen generals, all of which were above Level Seven and below Level Nine. There was no stronger existence.

Meanwhile, there were quite a number of cannon fodders. Level Four and Five demons and mercenaries were a dime a dozen with more than ten thousand of them, so Garen was not lacking any of these at all.

“In addition, you can also recommend candidates from the underlings. Those with outstanding military merits can be taken in.” Garen gave a little command. “My trip this time will probably take a while for me to return.”

“Understood.”

“If there’s anything that you can’t handle, you can go find Sean.”

Sean was the chieftain of the Demonic Behemoth squadron in the Fortress, commanding the mighty Demonic Behemoth elites, which was the most powerful deterrent force in the entire Fortress.

After being defeated by Garen, it tried to get payback for the next few years, but to no avail every time. In the end, it was finally convinced and became good friends with Garen instead. Although it did not have much authority, it was a force directly under Lady Vengeance and was not subjected to the two deputy commanders.

“Yes.”

Andrew honestly heeded the command.

Garen was then relieved and allowed him to leave.

Andrew, this fellow really followed him with sincerity and with no other intention. As for the other two female knights, they were still resisting at first. But later on, they went with the flow. Since Garen did not force them anyhow, they directly accepted their fate.

This time, Garen’s true purpose of arranging all kinds of affairs was to further enhance his own strength.

As his body had almost reached the limit, advancing further would require him to upgrade the Soul Ring layers and increase the Soul Limit. This however required a tremendous amount of Soul Energy. Now that he was at the limit of a Middle Level Demon Lord, entering the Upper Level would only need the prolonging of time and a large amount of sentiments.

There were forty years left until the initiation of the Grand Plan, and a mere forty-years was not enough to enter the Upper Level at all. Hence, the only way was to find other routes. Only by hunting a large number of high-quality souls, absorbing them after treating them, and condensing them into Soul Seeds would work.

This kind of high-quality souls did not necessarily have to be of high level; those great scholars and artists with special sentiments also had the potential to be absorbed.

Besides, there might be an overlap in the sentiments of the many high-level powerhouses, and that would not help Garen to condense Soul Seeds.

Just when he was scratching his head, there came an invitation from the Dragons of Disaster.

To organize an extensive raid in a certain layer of the Abyss. Led by Gerdmos, one of the three Monarchs, to plunder the positive energy Plane – the Light World.

That was where the people of Light lived.

These fellows with no necks had always been abhorrent. As one of the main fighters summoned by the Wizards from various positive energy camp, they had a very malicious attitude towards the evil Colored Dragon Clan.

Initially, the Dragons of Disaster mainly spread fear to gain greater abilities and beliefs; this time, they went with the purpose of revenge.

The chief of a certain clan among the people of Light was planning a grand action against the evil Dragons of Disaster. It collaborated with many ethnic groups in the Light World, as well as some ethnic groups from the Heavens and the Light Elves of the kind under Mother Nature.

Prior to this, they had killed a Level Thirteen Dragon of Disaster named Storm Warlock and had actually gotten a Divine Stone unexpectedly.

Gerdmos, one of the three Monarchs, was heading there for this Divine Stone.

Garen still had the Pearl of the Temple he acquired back then in his hands as he had not been willing to eat it. He had been trying to perceive the divinity in it but still had no clue for a long time. If he had the Divine Stone, with the help of the Divine Power in it, he might just be able to understand the divinity.

He somewhat felt that the understanding of the divinity might be good for the Void Original Opus and Soul Limit.

Chapter 1331: Invasion 1

Chapter 1331: Invasion 1

Central Territory – the Primary Plane.

The sacred Azerland Empire was a kingdom within the Central Empire and also the core area of the Fehra Cathedral.

Every year, there would be tens of thousands of pilgrims from all over the world who would piously kneel with every step they took as they made their pilgrimage. The cathedral here spread all over the country. The priests of the Fehra Cathedral would walk around in white robes to spread the glory and doctrines of God. Even the farmers here had a deeper understanding of the doctrine of God.

At this time, at the border of Azerland Empire, a young man in white clothes walked through the door of a pointed small white cathedral on the edge of a farm.

The white clothes on his body had grayed out, and tears and patches were faintly visible at the edges and corners.

The young man had a sallow complexion and was emaciated, yet his hair was still neatly groomed.

Approaching the church, he bowed slightly to the priest at the door, entered the cathedral, and sat on the bench with other people who had come to worship.

He lowered his head and lightly recited along with the choir’s singing.

There were new people coming in. Combined with the more than a dozen people who had entered before, none of them were as pious as he was.

The priest stood at the door and looked at him tenderly, revealing a gentle smile.

He knew this man. His name was Mousse, and he had been living in the nearby town for more than ten years. He was originally a vagrant, but he found a new home here, set up his own family, and had his own children.

Most importantly, Mousse’s piety for Fehra was unmatched by everyone here. Ten years plus past like a day as he constantly came here every day. He even influenced the neighbors around and his own family to believe in Fehra, and he also had a deep understanding of the doctrines of God, not as superficial as those ordinary believers.

“Maybe it’s time to give him more responsibilities…” The priest thought so. He was about to be transferred to a larger parish because of his merits, and he had to find a new person to take over here. Since the last major incident at the Central’s Meteor City, the elite priests and Divine Officers were transferred to the more important areas in Central, and so the defense forces in the areas with fewer supernatural forces here were naturally reduced.

Apart from being pious, Mousse had also worked as a mercenary and a bard. He knew a little Spellcraft, and his Spirit Power might be good. In accordance with his level of piety, he might easily become a Level One priest if he were to change his occupation to becoming a priest.

Thinking of this, the priest took the initiative to walk to Mousse’s side and patted his shoulder gently.

“Mousse… About the matter I brought up to you the last time, how have you thought about it?” The pastor asked mildly. His age was enough to be the father of the other party, so it was normal to use this kind of tone.

Mousse hurriedly lowered his head in fear and trepidation.

“Lord Jacqueffey, can I really serve as a missionary here? As a priest, a real priest. I feel that I still have a lot of shortcomings!”

“No, no, no…” the priest smiled and said. “Your ability, your piety, your concentration, Fehra sees it all in his eyes. All life forms who sincerely commit and truly believe in Fehra will get a bright and warmth return. This is the reward for your persistence all this while after such a long time. Moreover, there’re more people who need you to redeem them and help them.”

Mousse bowed his head and lightly recited the Fehra’s Creed.

“I understand. But can a loser like me really take on such a heavy responsibility?” He was still not that confident.

“Rest assured. With your ability, you can do even better…” The priest patted him in a understanding manner.

Mousse lowered his head and a black line faintly flashed across his white eyes.

*******************

The Aqilean Snowy Mountain

In a certain layer in the Abyss, there was a large snowy mountain in the center surrounded by magma flames.

In an Abyssal level filled with magma, fire, and poisonous smoke everywhere, there actually stood a gigantic, mighty snowy mountain in the center area which had been releasing an incomparable cold air for countless years.

The cold air here condensed into a deep blue triangular ice-cone, which slowly rotated clockwise over the top of the mountain.

At this time, a tall man in black armor was standing on the edge of the snowy mountain. He had long hair, half golden and half silver, and it looked very strange.

A bat-like badge was worn on the chest.

The most bizarre thing was that his feet were not on the ground, but were hovering in the air. Black circuit-like fluorescent lines flashed occasionally from below his foot.

“Gerdmos, it’s up to you.” A voice came faintly from the air behind him.

“How is the gathering of the forces?” The black-armored man asked plainly.

“There’re already one hundred and twenty-three Dragons of Disaster who are in the record who have promised to come and assist. Coupled with the Chaotic Creatures, we just need to be in charge of opening the passage, and it will naturally trigger the friction between the forces of Abyss and the Light World,” the voice replied.

“Then let’s get started.” Gerdmos nodded, reached out his fingers, and gently pressed the air in front. A string of black pearl-like spots suddenly flew out of his fingertips and rushed into the sky.

Pooh!

After a dull explosion, the black pearls exploded one after another like fireworks, and the black fireworks-halo slowly blasted out a black whirling hole in the air.

Hee hee hee…

There was a strange laughter in the air, and large amount of flames and poisonous smoke around were madly sucked into the black hole like an underwater whirlpool, entering in big gushes.

Countless Fire Creatures and demons in the Abyss fluttered their wings, and like a large group of worms, regardless of red ones or black ones, they all swarmed toward the big hole.

“Fresh flesh and blood, flesh and blood! Hahaha!!” Some simple-minded Fire Trolls roared, dripping magma-like sweat all over their body as they flapped their fiery wings toward the black hole.

“It’s the smell of the creatures of Light World! Kill!! Kill them all!” Sturdy Dual-Headed Red Fire Giants treaded their heavy steps, rolling up the magma flowing on their entire skin into magma balls and shooting them into the sky.

Like a densely packed stream of meteors, they rushed into the black hole of the Light World.

They and the Fire Trolls were the majority groups.

Underneath, Gerdmos looked up at the countless black and red meteors flying from all directions into the black hole he had opened up. His face revealed a slight smile.

“We have to act as soon as possible. Our action must not be found out by Fehra.”

“That’s for sure. All the Dragons of Disaster are in place. At your command, we’ll all charge into the Light World.” The hollow voice spoke in a deep tone.

Gerdmos smiled, looking like the most ordinary young man.

“Then… Let the massacre officially begin…”

He thrusted forward, and the entire person exploded and turned into countless red flames. After a large number of flames erupted, his original enormous body was revealed.

It was an incomparably huge Red Dragon.

He had the same three horns, and red flames enveloped the horn in the middle.

His body was hundreds of meters long, and with a flap of his wing, all the snow substances and other demons around him were swayed by the huge air force.

The most striking thing was that the three red luminous balls gliding around him were like Elves flying around him automatically.

Whoosh!

A gust of wild wind blew by, and Gerdmos disappeared instantly on the spot, and circles of obvious ripples appeared at the black hole, as if something huge had suddenly entered it.

Just after he entered the black hole.

The red sky around the black hole pooled together, and large flights of dragons of various colors flew over from a distance.

Among them were the huge-sized Black Dragons, Red Dragons, and the smaller Purple Dragons, Blue Dragons, White Dragons, some Yellow-Brown Poisonous Dragons, Green Dragons; even Three-Headed Chimeras appeared here.

But no matter which dragon, they were all emitting a similar atmosphere.

It was a faint black gas.

Among the large flights of dragons, the weakest ones even exuded the power fluctuation of Level Ten.

The White Dragon Garen incarnated into was also among them. The poisonous snake on his back was extremely conspicuous. Flapping his wings and flying in the sky, his eyes were focused on the black hole in the sky.

“The demons that went before us will attract most of the attention. The Light World will think that it’s just a simple invasion of the Abyss’ forces, and so the forces sent out to suppress us will not be too great. As long as we are fast enough, everyone can quickly reach their designated location to quickly complete the mission assigned to them.” The Dragon of Disaster leading the team was the Dragon of Disaster of the Water Element Plane named Jane, nicknamed the Wrath of Ocean.

The mission this time was assigned by one of the three Monarchs, Gerdmos. If the mission was completed, one could acquire a thread of the true divinity. There was a lot of divinity in a Divine Stone, while the true divinity referred to the divinity that had been disintegrated. Although it might not have much content, it had a very important role in guidance. Just one thread of it could help Garen to perceive the Pearl of the Temple, and what he needed was the method to analyze the divinity.

Other Dragons of Disaster were obviously thinking so.

Jane spoke in a low voice.

“There are thirteen peaks in the Light World, and on each of the peaks are thirteen cities, all of which are made of lights and glass. The glass there is very tough and sharp, unlike the Main Substance Plane. Some of them even know how to use powerful defensive and offensive matrixes that are made of special crystals. All of you need to be careful. We can ignore most of the people of Light. The only ones we need to watch out for are the Keepers of Light. Each of the Keepers of Light were at least at Level Nine, and they are the ultimate powerhouse group among the Light People.

“We are responsible for handling all the Keepers of Light in the Eleventh City of the Eighth peak. In any case, just kill whoever you see,” Jane simply said.

“The four of us are all above Level Twelve. There won’t be any difficulty in dealing with a mere Eleventh City.” An arrogant Blue Dragon said disdainfully. He was the legendary Blue Dragon with the Holy Dragon’s Blood. It was rumored that when the Blue Dragons were in their most powerful period, their ancestors were called Holy Dragons, and they had far more terrific powers and talents than other dragon clans. They had an inborn horrific aura that suppressed the other dragon clans, and at the same time, they were innately immunized to all spells, living in the cold crystal peaks. But unfortunately, after who knew how many thousands of years later, their bloodline had weakened.

“Don’t be careless. King Light can teleport to any peak with the speed of light. Once he appears, we must retreat immediately,” Jane reminded.

“Rest assured. With me around, leaving is not a problem,” the Purple Dragon in the small team said confidently. “I have specialized in Space Spell for hundreds of years, so I’m confident in this aspect.”

“We’ll be counting on you then.”

Garen followed at the rear and did not speak but just flew silently. As long as he could get a thread of divinity, that would be enough. The biggest issue was how to ensure his own safety and get the most benefit at the same time while protecting himself.Find authorized novels in ，faster updates, better experience，Please click www.webnovel.com for visiting.

The Light World, the Plane were the people of Light were at, was well-known for gems and crystals. Returning empty-handed was not his style.

The black hole in front was getting closer and closer, and soon the four dragons rushed in with all the surrounding dragons together.

In a cloud of black mist, Garen could only feel countless cold air lingering around him. This coldness was different from the cold he was familiar with; it was a kind of poisonous chill with a paralysis effect.

The darkness did not last long. As the dragons continued to flap their wings, a spot of white light soon lit up before them.

With a bang, Garen felt as if he had crashed into a transparent barrier. Violently breaking through, he wormed into it.

The sight before him was suddenly clear and bright, filled with a bright white light.

Chapter 1332: Invasion 2 Mystical Journey

Chapter 1332: Invasion 2 Mystical Journey

Countless white clouds layered to form an ocean of clouds. Above it, stood thirteen enormous white mountain peaks, each of them in the shape of a pyramid and aligned in an orderly manner.

Circular cities floated like meteorites, rotating around the peaks.

These cities formed a circle, rotating slowly around the mountain peaks as if they had been doing so for eternity.

Roar!!!

Suddenly, a gigantic Red Dragon emerged in the air above the thirteen mountain peaks. Its body was so long that it was able to encircle the thirteen peaks within it’s the center or its body.

A blazing red fire engulfed the Red Dragon’s body, naturally emitting a high-temperature force field. Garen could see with his own eyes that the corners of the cities above the peaks were melting faintly.

The Red Dragon had three straight horns on its head, the center horn had connecting red lines formed by the fire.

“King Light… Fehra can’t protect you anymore…” The Red Dragon’s thunderous voice echoed throughout the entire sky and ocean of clouds.

Hum…

A white, jade-like shroud of light raised slowly from the thirteen peaks encircled.

The Red Dragon swayed his tail gently, and the light shroud was instantly smashed and shattered into numerous pieces of crystal glass, scattering everywhere.

Large groups of Fire Creatures suddenly emerged from the surrounding air. It was evident that they had used a certain method to conceal themselves before that.

Appearing now, the Fire Creatures charged into the light shroud, as large groups of white-armored warriors and demons also flew out from the light shroud to engage in battle.

These warriors were very special. They were separated from the head and the body; the head was suspended above the body, and the middle part, which should have been the position of the neck, was just a mass of air.

Each of them held a white lightsaber and a shield, and beneath their feet were white light paths as they fought hard with the demons in the air.

The giant black hole also loomed out of the air slowly, endless demons continuously to pour out from the black hole.

Meanwhile, the Dragons of Disaster including Garen dashed to the light shroud towards the Red Dragon.

Boom!!

Just then, an enormous white hand appeared from the ocean clouds below and grabbed towards the Red Dragon.

“Gerdmos, how dare you enter the Light World?! Today your body will remain here forever to become the nourishment of the earth!!” A solemn voice sounded from the ocean of clouds.

The Red Dragon smiled slightly, swooped down flying towards the direction of the big hand.

Garen retracted his gaze and looked front back left right around his surroundings. There were huge dragons and demons everywhere. At the front, the demons and some of the Dragons of Disaster had already begun to fight with the Light Warriors.

Every Dragon of Disaster was equivalent to a Catastrophic Level-existence. Even though every move made would be limited by the pure positive energy of the Light World and they could not display their very own catastrophic range-attack, but just the horrifying quality and strength of the body alone was not something the ordinary people of Light could resist.

“Follow me!” Jane puffed out a Dragon Breath, turning a few Light Warriors flying towards him into ashes. Fluttering his wings, he flew towards one of the mountain peaks.

“Our target is not here.”

The four giant dragons streaked through the battlefield like sharp swords. Following the light shroud, they charged into one of the cities above the peaks.

From far, these cities were no different from the small meteorites that flew around. It was only when they approached it did they realize that the city grew increasingly bigger and humongous. As the distance closed in, the surrounding airflow passed by swiftly.

Garen watched as the city quickly grew from the size of a fist into a grinding disc, and then bigger to occupy his entire field of vision.

“You have an hour to kill all living creatures within your sight. The mission is to completely destroy the city and those who succeed will be rewarded the assigned divinity from Gerdmos,” Jane reminded briefly of the mission that every dragon should know by now.

“So, if our team wants to get the divinity, we’ll have to depend on everyone.”

“Leave it to me.”

Still thousands of kilometers above away from the city, the Blue Dragon took a deep breath, bulging his chest up high like an inflated balloon before fiercely spewing out a Dragon Breath.

Boom!!!

The overwhelming Black Frost Dragon Breath gushed out, instantly covering the space of several kilometers square below. Some of the Warriors and Wizards who had just pounced at him were affected by the Dragon Breath. Instead of turning into ice sculptures, they melted completely in the Dragon Breath.

On the other hand, the Purple Dragon was fanning its wings. Every time they were flapped, a huge Summoning Matrix of a hundred meters in diameter would form below. Groups of violent Abyss creatures would appear from the Matrix. Consisting mainly of Berserk Tigers and Berserk Behemoths that were extremely bloodthirsty, they would kill anyone they saw.

In less than a minute, the Purple Dragon had summoned hundreds of Berserk Creatures, each reaching the degree of Level Five. Find authorized novels in ，faster updates, better experience，Please click www.webnovel.com for visiting.

He raised his snake-neck high again, and his eyes suddenly released two purple light columns, which fell straight down like two laser cutting-lines.

Sizz…

The transparent glass buildings below collapsed under his purple shooting light, and some were cut into two sections before collapsing after a brief moment.

Jane was different from them. He hovered in midair with both his claws raised. The center of his claws was flashing a light like that of a blue seawater as if he was brewing something big.

Garen retracted his gaze from observing his teammates. Looking at the humongous city below, he thought about the skills his own skills. He did now know how powerful the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique could be exerted considering the suppression effect here was too great. It would be considered quite well even if only one-half of it could be produced.

“What should I use?” He gave a thought to it, and his wings slowly lit up seven black-red Death Stars.

In a flash of black light, a man that was covered in black appeared before him. He had seven black-red death points on his back.

“Seven Lives, I’m counting on you,” Garen ordered lightly.

“Understood.” The man’s muscles were unreasonably sturdy like no one else’s.

His power at this moment was roughly similar to that of Garen’s at about 120 points. Although it was not comparable to Garen’s own body, it was considered very scary.

But Seven Lives was unlike Garen. There was a major difference between them…

“First Star!”

Pap!

Seven Lives stretched out his hands and abruptly tapped at dozens of acupuncture points on his chest. His movements were so fast that both his hands were like the Thousand-Hands Guanyin as they brought out countless afterimages.

Squeak…

It was only the First Star, and his muscles could be seen swelling up madly like they were being inflated.

Garen, who was at the back, felt his eyelids jumping non-stop. He was connected to Seven Lives in body and in mind, so he had a complete understanding of all his attributes.

With just the activation of the First Star, Seven Lives’ Strength had risen to the limit of 180 points, which was similar to his.

“Second Star!”

Yet Seven Lives was still not satisfied, he reached out to tap on the second acupuncture point again.

Numerous afterimages merged on his chest and finally turned into a triangular gesture with both palms joined together.

A vast amount of muscles seemed to be deforming as they twisted and floated behind Seven Lives. He was no longer flying with Garen’s strength, but the muscles at his back had actually condensed into a pair of flesh-wings. The whole body’s muscles were no longer like muscles, and he looked more like a heavy-duty robot wearing an armor.

With the Strength reaching the limit, Seven Lives did not break through this point. However, a layer of transparent cuticle-like matter gradually appeared around his body.

He gently made a grip.

Boom!

A cloud of gas directly blasted out from Seven Lives’ fist. His strength at this Plane had even reached the horrific effect compared to when he was at a weaker Plane back then.

Landing quickly on the ground and under Garen’s watch, Seven Lives grabbed hold of a huge building that was tilting toward him, turning it and flinging it out fiercely.

Boom boom!!!

The several tens-of-meters wide building was cast out by him as if it were an artillery shell, landing at a speed comparable to bullets at an area where it was mostly populated with the people of Light.

A massive mushroom cloud slowly rose, and a large number of people of Light were completely wiped out by the explosion which was comparable to a small nuclear bomb. Even the bodies’ limbs were not necessarily found.

Seven Lives decided to simply pace slowly in the city. Eyeing the buildings at random, he would use a special technique to grab and hurl them out. Spacious paths were formed around him as a result of all the flinging he was doing, and the people of Light madly pounced on him. But no matter what spells and attacks were produced every time, not a trace of any of it was left on him. That layer of cuticle would completely block off all the attacks.

When the three Dragons of Disaster in the team saw this kind of force, even they were slightly stupefied. This was the horrific effect of the strength reaching an extreme point.

Garen hovered at a high altitude. Even without wings, he could float in the air with the power of his own Spellcraft.

Seven Lives’ destructive power was even stronger than his, whose strength was restrained. In this kind of situation, having him carrying out pure destruction was sufficient.

From afar, he saw a group of Level Nine-Keepers of Light was finally dispatched. They were divided into three batches, and the first batch charged right away at Seven Lives. However, Garen was not concerned at all.

Seven Lives did not just merely have this ability as he had also inherited some of the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon’s ability. The reason he was called Seven Lives was that he actually does have seven lives…

If he could not be killed seven times, then no matter how many opponents there were and how strong they were, all their attacks would be meaningless.

“Looks like your incarnation is being surrounded, Garen. Are you not worried at all?” Jane asked with a smile on the side.

“It’s just a bunch of ants,” Garen responded faintly. The Soul Divine Weapon, the Despair Skull, was in his hand without anyone knowing when.

After a vast number of weak souls died, they floated into the sky in a way that was invisible to the naked eye. However, they were intercepted and absorbed by the Soul Divine Weapon on their way to the Heavens.

At the same time, the mysterious Enneahedron in Garen’s body was also absorbing them.

Garen felt the potential aura of the Soul Divine Weapon growing continually, and his mood was becoming increasingly cheerful.

The felt extremely delighted by the screams made by the countless lives below.

“Such wonderful sounds…”

“Is it?” Jane glanced at him. “Be careful, I’m about to start releasing…”

As soon as his voice fell, Garen felt a huge dazzling blue explosion in his hand.

Seawater!

It was endless seawater!!

The dark blue endless seawater continued to expand and transform as it suspended in the sky, quickly turning into an unparalleled giant.

The giant was composed of seawater and was dark blue and translucent. He only had a sturdy upper body, and he was raising his two huge fists.

Roar!!!

Garen was also dumbfounded at the sight of this fellow. This was not an ordinary Water Element Giant.

This was…the King of Water Element…!! A Level Fifteen-top existence!!!

Chapter 1333: Trouble 1 Mystical Journey

Chapter 1333: Trouble 1 Mystical Journey

The King of Water Element was blue in color, and it opened its mouth to spew downward.

With a bang, countless water bombs flew down and densely rained onto the city below, turning into a tall Level Five Water Elemental Elder, directly engaging in battle with the people of Light.

Garen hovered on one side and did not intervene. He just quietly observed the battle around.

He was not being idle but was paying attention to the dangers that might arise.

The Light World was not a stable place, and there were not only these low-level people of Light.

Of course, it was also likely that there was a lot of wealth here at the same time.

Garen closed his dragon eyes and maximized his awareness. Numerous Spirit Power like that of silk screens were released and spread around toward the surrounding voids.

“The most precious place… in this city…”

The gradual increase of the Potential Points of the Soul Divine Weapon alone could not satisfy him.

“This side!” Suddenly, Garen’s body moved, and his whole body flew straight towards the city’s west side.

Jane hesitated before deciding to follow suit.

Garen was not worried about Seven Lives at all. Even if he was killed seven times, at most, it would need a little longer time for his own body to recover and to re-grow it. As for Jane, who was following behind, there would be a way to shake him off.

The two giant dragons quickly flew to the front of a tall glass tower. The figure of an elderly man sitting in a lotus position slowly emerged from the air in front of the tower.

This old person of Light had an amiable complexion, and his eyes were shut slightly, like a corpse without any breathing and energy fluctuations.

“This site is off-limits.” The old man spoke in a low voice.

Garen’s Spirit Power penetrated the tower. He could see a mass of white light that was beating like a heart shining in the inside of the tower.

“Move in!”

Garen suddenly charged forward and lashed his golden tail like a whip at the old man.

“Crystal.”

A crystal-like round shield appeared before the old man and steadily bore Garen’s dragon tail slam, while he sat in the air unshaken.

Jane did not listen to Garen but flew in an arc line from the side toward that mass of halo. His slender green body abruptly stretched out to become thinner, and the head was strangely thin and long like a noodle. He instantly dashed to the tower.

“Whoever grabs the treasure first, owns it!” He roared in a deep voice.

Garen only smiled slightly, and looked cautiously at the old man, and turned around to retreat.

The old man did not even look at him but extended his right hand to form a big hand in the air and fought with Jane.

The two entangled in battle and were equally matched.

Garen took the opportunity to retreat. His body shook, and suddenly the black seven-star wings automatically flew back to his body. At the same time, it brought back a vast horrifying potential aura. Clearly, Seven Lives did not just kill one or two high-level Keepers of Light during the massacre.

Some small Space Equipment appeared in the hands of Garen, and he threw all of these objects into his own Space Ring.

The city quickly fell back under his wings. Garen carefully searched for the places that could be plundered.

Boom!!

A tall and huge building like that of a palace was plunged through by Garen from a high altitude. After smashing through the roof and stirring up a commotion on the inside for a while, he shot out of it along with the raging bellows of the people of Light, as he snatched something from the inside.

“Kill him!!”

A few Keepers of Light gave chase. Even though their speed was not as fast as Garen, but they used a pure white disc-like flying tool to repeatedly teleport in the city, tailing him closely behind.

These Keepers of Light were surrounded by a strong Light aura. Some parts of their bodies even had a photochemical reaction and were completely like glass, emitting white light.

Each of their back had countless pure white light-filaments, and they were waving gently like white feather wings.

Each of these light-filaments was a high-concentration agglomeration of the Light Element, which could burn and vaporize any substance in an instant due to the exceptionally high temperature. There was also the conceptualization of some matters into essence involved, not just a simple increase of temperature anymore.

Garen was not bothered by all these. After plundering a palace, he continued to charge at a museum. Some of the people of Light on the street who were not skilled in attacking fled everywhere, while those who could not escape in time were directly crushed to death by his huge body as he landed.

The Keepers of Light yelled in rage from behind and tried to stop him, but their speed was lagging by one step every time.

After Garen’s wings were restored, he could cause chaos and confusion within a hundred meters with a slight vibration of his wings, totally preventing them from identifying the direction of pursuit and could only keep up after his bum.

“We can’t let him simply fly like this anymore!” A Keeper of Light made up his mind.

“Rest assured. Lord Henary has already set out. The other two Lords have already teleported over here and are suppressing a few Dragons of Disaster on the other side.”

The whispers of the Keepers of Light fell into Garen’s ears.

He frowned slightly and sped up.

He was feeling a faint, inexplicable uneasiness. The Light World had always been Fehra’s most loyal group of supporters, and so it was impossible for Fehra not to have any contingency plan.

“Must be quick!”

He quickly sensed the area that he ran his eyes over.

The mission was to destroy the city sufficiently and it would be enough. At the moment, the Dragons of Disaster, together with a vast group of demons and Summoned Creatures, had caused enormous chaos, destruction, and casualties in the city, hence, the mission could be said to have been completed.

Almost none of the buildings in the entire city was complete. Most of them were ruined, some were blazing fire, black smokes were rolling into the sky, forming a column of smoke.

Regardless of how strong the forces of the Dragons of Disaster were, it still was not possible to surpass the forces of the entire Light World gathered together. Hence, fighting a quick battle and finishing it quickly was the core tactic.

Estimating the time, Garen once again rushed out from a huge and magnificent mansion. With a spurt of the Dragon Breath, he exterminated dozens of crystal arrows that were in pursuit from behind.

Suddenly, the whole world shook.

“Gerdmos…!! How dare you!!” A voice that was filled with infinite light rang through the entire city from the sky.

Pure white flowers descended from the sky, the countless lotus-like flowers rotated and slowly fell.

Lots of white-winged Elves appeared in the air and were intermittently visible. Their emergence was also accompanied by a faint sacred song.

Garen promptly looked up and saw a gigantic human figure in a golden armor, radiating a terrifying white light all around him, and on the back was a halo like that of a sun.

He held a sword with both hands and ferociously slashed downward.

A gigantic Red Dragon appeared in front of his giant sword out of thin air, and the horn on the head directly went up against it.

Then, there was a dazzling light.

Garen’s line of sight was directly submerged by the infinite white light, and nothing could be seen at all.

The endless amount of light energy wrapped around his body like a tide.

An intense burning sensation traveled through the scales of the skin, shocking him immediately.

“Must leave now!”

It was impossible for Fehra’s true form to appear, and so the one that appeared here must be his incarnation that was temporarily stationed here. Since his incarnation had appeared, the battle had clearly reached the end.

“Leave behind the Divine Stone!!” The incarnation roared, and the voice slammed into Garen like a ferocious wave.

His entire body was in a terrible pain, and he spurted out a mouthful of blood. He was instantly greatly appalled.

Just the voice alone could cause him fatal injuries!

“Must leave now!” He forcefully fluttered his wings, and his body flew away in the direction from where he came from.

Although it was all but white light before him, it was obviously a kind of blindness effect and would not persist for long. Garen had already memorized the topography of this place.

The mission he came for this time was just to be an onlooker and mingle about to obtain a thread of divinity. It was never his plan to be the main force against the enemy.

The other Dragons of Disaster were obviously thinking the same.

Garen heard a painful dragon roar from afar, and then felt the fluctuations of the Dimensional Jump from the Space-Time Spell. Clearly, someone had started to run away.

It was chaos all around as if countless life auras were closing in quickly.

Boom!!

A heavy thing aggressively stuck itself to his tail, pulling down his body that was rushing upward.

Garen shook his faint golden tail right away, and that unknown object was directly flung away. He continued to fly high up into the sky.

Amid the blindness effect, he could only see white and nothing else in front of him. He could only return the original way he came from based from his memory instincts and senses.

The screams of demons and Summoned Creatures continued to ring out below.

Ow!!

A sudden screech of pain sounded, shocking Garen.

The screech belonged to Gerdmos! He was obviously injured in the battle by the incarnation.

In the air over the city that Garen could not see.

A clump of dark red ball suddenly burst out of Gerdmos and landed on Fehra’s big hand.

At that moment, the ball suddenly exploded and instantly turned into countless red flames, blotting out the sky and covering the earth as they gushed down at Fehra.Find authorized novels in ，faster updates, better experience，Please click www.webnovel.com for visiting.

“You dare to detonate the Divine…!” Fehra’s voice was submerged in the endless rumbles of the explosion.

His entire body was completely surrounded by flames, and a large amount of formless divinity turned into red lines like that of spider threads.

Garen’s sight was almost back to normal. He too saw the countless red silk threads that drifted down and felt the divinity in it.

“The divinity of the Divine Stone! This is troublesome!!”

He ignored these divinities and flew directly out of the city and the mountain, rushing to the huge Abyss black hole not far away.

This was not the time for looting but to escape to save yourself.

Boom!!

A thunderous noise came from behind Garen. Gerdmos and Fehra’s incarnation seemed to be fighting each other in the endless flame.

“Ha ha ha!! The mission is completely over. Dear all, this is the reward for all of you!”

Gerdmos seemed to be in an exceptionally pleasant mood. A vast amount of deep red silk threads suddenly shot out from the flames, and each thread automatically chased after the Dragons of Disaster that was flying to the black hole.

Garen was also caught up by one of the threads. The speed of these lines was strangely fast as if they had no mass. Just a flash in the space and a few kilometers was crossed.

The silk thread wormed into his claws. Garen tightened his grip and gently stashed it away. With a flapping of both wings, his whole body instantly disappeared on the spot and directly appeared in the black hole.

Blitzkrieg!

There was no doubt that Gerdmos’ attack tactic had been successful. In the short period of raid time, he mounted a sneak attack on King Light, seized the Divine Stone, and then retreated when Fehra’s incarnation had just come out. Although he was injured, the reward he reaped was far beyond such an injury.

“Still trying to escape!!”

Entering the black hole, Garen was about to return to the Abyss when he felt a distortion behind him, and a white light penetrated through it, aiming at his back.

Hiss!!

The beam hit him on the back, scorching him all over the body as his scales smoked.

Not only him, all the surrounding demons and giant dragons who had fled back were also struck by the beams.

Numerous demons were spontaneously ignited and turned into white ash, while the Dragons of Disaster could hold out for a longer time. Even so, several of them were still torched by the beams. They screamed in the flames, which had a sacred aura in it, and burnt into a large pile of ashes swiftly.

Resisting the pain on his back, Garen accelerated his escape toward the Abyss.

Pooh!

After passing through a layer of film once more, the familiar and chaotic power of the Abyss came over him, quickly entangling with and offsetting the power of the beam at Garen’s back.

Chapter 1334: Trouble 2

Chapter 1334: Trouble 2

The power of Abyss had an extremely mighty devour and repulsive nature.

In the face of external forces, if it could not devour the other party, it would then completely eliminate it.

Garen flew out of the black hole, and by the time he returned to the Abyssal layer with berserk fires, he was already half-dead, which was still considered quite good. The other Dragons of Disaster did not even have the strength to fly and were free-falling, crashing into the sea of magma below falling into a deep sleep.

Fortunately, no matter how weak a Dragon of Disaster was, its dragon scales, which had a natural strong defense, and force field would protect it from being harmed by the mere magma on the surface.

Mustering his strength to fly out of the midst of the dragons that were like dumplings entering a wok, Garen gathered his wings and slowly descended on a dark solid volcanic rock.

He looked up at the bloody red sky and saw that the black hole was slowly contracting. However, he did not see the figure of Gerdmos, one of the three Monarchs. Presumably, he should be fine.

Garen glanced at the thread of divinity lying quietly in his Space Equipment. This was a true divinity, which had been disintegrated and analyzed by Gerdmos. Judging from the explosive nature of the Divine Stone, this divinity should be of fire attribute. Although it was not much of a right match with him, it still had its research value.

Even though he did not actually face a strong opponent in this blitzkrieg, the risk was indeed not small, especially the last move Fehra made out of rage. That beam was evidently a long-lasting kind of attack; if one could not return to the Abyss as soon as possible, then just that light beam alone would directly kill a Dragon of Disaster.

All the Dragons of Disaster, including Garen, were critically injured by it.

Standing on the rock, Garen turned around to inspect the wound on his body. In the middle of the wings on his back, the scales were directly burned… and something like a large piece of white crystal was formed at that spot. These crystals also exuded a pure light energy fluctuation that disgusted him.

“With such an obvious fluctuation, if I’m not in the Abyss but the other Planes, I’ll definitely be discovered by the people of the Fehra Cathedral in the first place.”

He looked up for a while until he saw no more Dragons of Disaster coming out, only then did the black hole finally shrunk and disappeared. Everything was completely over.

“It’s time to go back…”

Garen flapped his wings and headed toward the exit of this layer.

It was a huge underground cave. The cave might seem to head underground but in fact, as long as one entered through it with a special method, one could return to the Ten Thousand Abyss Plain at the topmost Abyssal layer.

Sweeping his sight around the tired and weak Dragons of Disaster, it was not that Garen did not have the idea of snatching the divinity. But for such a thing as the true divinity, one would only need a thread of it to learn the method of disintegration and analyzing. Once it was grasped, everything else would be much better. Having more threads was of no effect to him. After a brief consideration, Garen decided not to do it as it was unnecessary.

After searching around, he did not find the temporary team of dragon clans he was in.

“Hey, the White Dragon over there. If you can escort me back to the Natural Plane, I will use the Prickle Gem to repay you!”

A Natural Plane-Green Dragon was about to be submerged by the magma. Large pieces of white crystals coagulated all over its body, most parts of his body were obviously hit by the beam from just now.

This fellow’s aura, which should have been at Level Eleven, was now rapidly debilitating. His situation seemed very bad.

Garen was the more normal one compared to the others he saw nearby, as he could actually still move about freely even after taking a hit of the white light. Among all the Dragons of Disaster, only a dozen of them was able to do this.

“Me?” Garen looked around and could not spot any other White Dragon. Obviously, the other person was referring to him.

“Sorry, I’m not interested.” He lightly declined. The Green Dragon was instantly disappointed and wanted to say something more, but Garen had already fluttered away from his sight.

Continue flying forward, Garen soon met a few Dragons of Disaster who asked for help, all of them looking extremely weak.Find authorized novels in ，faster updates, better experience，Please click www.webnovel.com for visiting.

This Plane was not the Plane that Gerdmos permanently remained at. He himself probably had the thought of plundering these Dragons of Disaster. In any case, the Dragons of Disasters were never a united group, and it was just a name for the group.

But since he was present, Gerdmos would absolutely not allow any existence to destroy his rules. And so, Garen could only suppress this tempting idea.

Feeling the divinity in the Space Equipment, Garen faintly felt that this time, he might be able to use this thing to analyze the divinity in his Pearl of Temple.

For the other Dragons of Disaster, a thread of true divinity probably could only speed up their progress or chances of becoming a demigod; but for Garen, he could totally build the Energy Machinist’s Willpower Neuroprocessor and use the astonishing computing speed that was far beyond that of the quantum computer in the technology era to analyze the essence of divinity.

The divinity itself was a kind of sentiment, a sublimation of one’s understanding of the self and the foundation of one’s existence. At the same time, it also contained a kind of enlightenment and understanding of certain laws of the universe.

Once the understanding reached an incredibly high level and was incomparably compatible with the law of the universe, the creatures would naturally be able to resonate with the power of the universe due to this kind of compatibility, thereby improving the evolution one’s self and turning into a Divine Creature, close to the status of a demigod.

Hence, divinity was actually a kind of knowledge, an extremely complicated and profound information. It was an interpretation of the laws of the universe.

Garen only knew this from Ann’s books, so although he had not completely condensed his own divinity, he could sum up all the knowledge and information through the analysis of the divinity of other creatures.

In theory, his original soul was equivalent to a demigod level. The Demon Lords were not inferior to the demigods in the understanding of the laws of the world. It was only because they were not compatible with the laws of this world that they could not be a Divine Creature right away.

What Garen needed only was to understand the compatibility principle of this world, and it would be enough.

Soon, a huge black cave appeared in front of him. A few powerful Dragons of Disaster had just flown in and left an extremely intense aura of Light. They were obviously fatally injured by Fehra’s incarnation. Being able to be faster than Garen, the weakest aura of these fellows were of Level Thirteen, while there was even a Level Fifteen being the strongest one!

Garen had just tucked his wings away and landed at the mouth of the cave when he felt a black shadow appearing behind him and disappearing in a flash. A Level Fourteen Black Dragon with bloodshot eyes darted straight into the cave above his head, giving the impression that it was just a flickering shadow.

“How swift and fierce! Going through the Abyssal layers also requires physical strength… this fellow actually dared to fly at full speed.”

Garen felt that he need a good rest.

He glanced at his own status.

‘Garen – Strength 180 (100), Agility 180 (100), Vitality 180 (100), Intelligence 90. Potential 963%. Soul limit 180.

Status: Overall attributes declined, under the suppression and the curse of the Light… (All elemental resistance declined by half, easily found by Light attribute creatures, whereabouts could not be concealed)

“Damn it!” Garen could not help but cursed at the sight of the state of the attributes.

The three major attributes had all dropped by nearly half, and the elemental resistance had declined by half, especially the latter. This meant that he was initially immune to Level Nine-spells, but now, he might only be immune to Level Five-Spells and could only forcefully resist those of higher levels.

And if resisting forcefully, with his current 100-points of Vitality and weak state, he could only resist the frontal attack of a Level Nine-Spell…

“This is troublesome…” He rested for a while, trying hard to conceal the fluctuation of his aura, and began to fly along a special trajectory inside the cave.

The cave was not long, but each meter of flight was extremely difficult. One would need to resist the traction of this Abyssal layer, which was as great as the gravity of a planet.

Garen flew out a fixed trajectory pattern like a bee in the dark, and finally rose and rushed up to the sky.

Not knowing how long he had been flying, the darkness in front was finally faintly brightening up.

****************

Boom!!

The corpse of a huge Black Dragon crashed to the ground, splattering a large amount of blood and dust.

On the yellow plain with a huge black hole, everywhere was covered with incapacitated Dragons of Disaster. This was the path one must take when coming out of the Abyssal fire layer as it was the exit of the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains. All the Dragons of Disaster that had flown out before did not die in the raid but instead fell at this exit, which was almost a safety point.

Two tall men in red robes hovered in mid-air, and one was gently wiping the bloody sword in his hand.

The other person was the one who had previously gathered all the Dragons of Disaster to assault the Light World – Gerdmos.

He was smiling as he looked at the Black Dragon that was on the brink of death below.

“Noas, although I’m very sorry, I have a reason to do so.” Gerdmos seemed to have not been injured at all. His whole body was intact, and he was toying with a blood-red round stone in his hand.

“You… actually dared… betray the Disaster Scroll…” The Black Dragon’s eyes were filled with madness and rage.

“Betray?” Gerdmos did not have the slightest fear but just laughed lightly. “I never intended to betray the Disaster Scroll…”

There was a faint glint of contempt in his eyes.

“The Dragons of Disaster’s pitiful state like stray dogs should be reversed by me, Gerdmos.”

He opened his arms wide.

“Can’t you see? This endless Abyss has given me an unparalleled special talent. Can you still not see the current situation? Whether it’s the Void Creatures or each major Pantheons, between these two giants, we’re only an insignificant weak force, surviving in the cracks…

“Only by gathering the power of all the Dragons of Disaster, converging them into one and into my body… can we then have a glimmer of hope…” Gerdmos’ tone was monotonous, but his words were absolutely crazy.

His back was vaguely beginning to distort a horrifying shadow. A mighty power surpassing Level Fifteen and exceeding even that of the demigod was violently fluctuating around him.

“Come on… merge with me as one… to create a new future that belongs to us Dragons of Disaster…!” He slowly paced toward the Black Dragon on the ground.

“Ann… will not let you go!” The Black Dragon weakly gave a final roar of anger.

Boom!!

His entire body suddenly exploded. His soul together with his body completely turned into a huge bomb and disintegrated completely.

Chapter 1335: Eve 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

All the flesh and blood was devoured by Gerdmos in the explosion. A ferocious mouth split open from half of his body, swallowing all the flesh that shot toward him from the explosion.

“A pointless choice.”

Gerdmos straightened up, the mouth on his body disappeared naturally as if it had never appeared before.

Next, he slowly made his way towards the Dragons of Disaster who were on the verge of death. Unlike Black Dragon Noas, most of these Dragons of Disaster were no longer strong enough to fight back, they did not even have the strength to struggle or self-destruct. They could only watch as Gerdmos devour them.

The other man dress in red robe stood behind watching without making a sound.

*********************

Garen flew through the dark cave slowly, there was only silence in front of him.

Bang!

He vaguely heard a huge explosion that suddenly rang from the front.

“Explosion?”

Garen paused for a little.

“How can there be an explosion here?” His vigilance heightened. This was the exit of the Dragons of Disaster, so if there was an explosion, perhaps it meant that there was a conflict.

Who would be guarding the exit when the Dragons of Disaster were critically injured? At such a coincidental timing too!?

Garen raised his guard.

The exit was in front of him, shimmering in white but he stopped and no longer moved forward.

A black Salamander with toxic all over its black body slowly fell behind his steps. He was clearly as suspicious as Garen was.

Neither of them spoke, but they exchanged glances as both felt that the situation was quite odd.

Garen stopped and did not move forward. He glanced at the Salamander, waiting for him to go ahead first so he could see the results.

The Salamander seemed to be toying with the same idea as well as his eyes fell on Garen.

Both of them looked at each other.

“Seems like something might have happened…” The Salamander spoke first.

“Seems like it,” Garen nodded. “Are there any other exits here?”

“No, this is the only exit,” the Salamander shook his head. “To be able to grasp our departing time so accurately means that there must be a spy. Without a mole, how could anybody knew in such a short period of time of our secret gathering and raid, and our almost immediate departure as all of these happened in less than an hour.”

“Maybe we can find Gerdmos,” Garen said in a hushed tone.

“Hehe…” The Salamander chuckled, “if you are willing to go, I have no objections.”

Garen could sense his doubts toward Gerdmos’ intention and stopped saying further.

After a while.

“Then let’s wait for more dragons first and we’ll all rush forward together,” Garen spoke again.

“Alright.”

The two Dragons of Disaster waited quietly in the dark.

Soon enough, several huge Dragons of Disaster came from behind.

The Salamander explained the situation briefly. A few of the dragons who still had contact with those outside tried to contact them but there was no response.

Still pausing to move forward, the Dragons of Disaster’s looks changed.

Nobody dared to just go out like this.

Minutes and seconds passed by and soon, more than twenty Dragons of Disasters had gathered together.

Garen stood among the crowd of dragons without making a sound. There were those who were stronger than him in the crowd so naturally, he had no place to speak up.

Among the colossal dragons on the spot, the most powerful one was a gigantic Bass Dragon that went with the nickname of Plague. Plague was surrounded in the middle by a group of dragons, his two long yellow brows hung down his old face.

There was no trace of force field from his body as if he was not much better than the average Dragon Whelp, but no dragon dared to look down on him.

He was publicly acknowledged as the highest Level Fifteen peak.

Moreover, he was the standard Wizard Dragon. This kind of Elder Dragon could live over five thousand years, and each of them was extremely clever with countless trump cards in their hands. No matter what situation they encounter, they would not panic at all.

“It seems that we have a traitor amongst us. Since this is our only exit and it has been blocked, our companions who have gone out beforehand would have most probably perished.”

Bass Dragon said in a low tone, “I’ve tested with a Prophecy Spell and the highest wheel of fate shows that we are now in an extremely critical moment. I am unable to predict much details as the one who cast this danger is too powerful. But there is one thing I understood, and that is…”

His huge dragon head turned and looked around.

“Only by uniting that all of us would stand a chance!”

“That dangerous?” A rare Red Crystal Dragon frowned. Crystal Dragons were extremely rare and they were immune to all sorts of spells. They had an incredible yet terrifying melee talent, but they did not have Dragon Breath nor supernatural powers so they could only rely on equipment.

This Crystal Dragon was wearing a golden crown on its head, looking wild and badass.

“Just speak up whatever idea you have. The longer we stay here, the more danger we’re in.”

Bass Dragon’s eyes swept through every single dragon in the crowd.

“I’ve heard that Your Excellency, King of Fantasy, has an extremely powerful Divine Weapon called the Infinite Fantasy. It’s able to create several ultimate phantoms that are close to an entity. Not sure if it’s true though?”

He looked at a petite little Purple Dragon. This Purple Dragon was a small female dragon with a calm expression on her face.

“So, are you saying that we could create illusions to confuse the other party? What if matrix sort of encirclements are formed?” The King of Fantasy asked.

“Even if it’s matrix, I will have a way to consume a large amount of energy,” Bass Dragon shot a mysterious smile.

“Your Excellency Moon, Your Excellency Green Hurricane, Your Excellency Fordoo, your strengths can be our backup…”

Bass Dragon was no doubt the most knowledgeable old guy on the spot. At a moment like this, he was so familiar with the techniques of each Dragon of Disaster as if he was enumerating his family’s valuables. He was even able to arrange each of them in the most appropriate position so that they could put their abilities to good use.

But the arrangements only included beings that were Level Thirteen and above. For the rest of them, they only played supporting roles as covers.

Garen was also one of them.

His biggest lethal effect was the Poisonous Eye that could kill Thirteen-Level existences in a flash. Other than having an unparalleled speed of shooting and the sudden flash it possessed, beings that were one of two levels above him could be caught suddenly even if it may be unintentional.

After Bass Dragon was done arranging everything, a group of Dragons of Disaster approached the exit slowly.

The light source exit was a distorted natural Teleportation Point. Upon entering, one would automatically be transmitted out of this Abyss layer. Not only that, it could accommodate up to tens of thousands of creatures at the same time.

The twenty over Dragons of Disaster walked over slowly, each of them conserving their energy. Some of them had their muscles tensed up so tight that their scales showed the same color, some of them had a layer of various protection spells upon themselves, some of them turned their bodies invisible that even a trace of force could not be noticed.

Some of them even cloned themselves into several avatars so that others were unable to distinguish between the real one and the clones.

Garen even saw a Dragon of Disaster’s body that straight away melted into a pile of sand, approaching the light source exit in a fluid-like manner.

He stood in the middle of the queue, looking at the line of Dragons of Disaster that slowly approached the light source.

“Charge!!” Suddenly, Bass Dragon roared.

All the Dragons of Disaster accelerated simultaneously and rushed toward the light source at full speed.

********************

Boom!!

A huge explosion rose from the exit of the cave.

Gerdmos was slightly stunned but his expression quickly returned to his original, indifferent expression.

Looking at the twenty over dragons that suddenly stormed out from the cave, he smirked.

“You old Plague, I knew that would be a little trouble over here with you…”

He turned around and looked at the other person dressed in a red robe.

“It’s all on you.”

“Leave it to me.”

The red-robed person smiled.

They shook hands with each other.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!!

All around the plain, red lights burst out from the ground heading towards the sky.

The blinding red lights beamed upwards to the sky straight like pencils, encircling all the fleeing Dragons of Disaster.

“Separate,” the red-robed man whispered softly.

With a huge buzz, the entire encircled area where all the Dragons of Disaster were at disappeared together. Even the red lights that broke out from the ground moments ago also vanished together.

Just as the red lights disappeared, dozens of Dragons of Disaster flew out of the cave once again.

“Phantoms, huh?” The red-robed man’s expression was unchanged. With another point of his finger, several beams of red lights continued rising and once again, enveloped all the new Dragons of Disaster and they completely disappeared again.

“It’s useless. No matter how many times you use a trick like this, it’s useless,” he said calmly.

Boom!!

Suddenly, his face changed slightly. There seemed to be something that caused a huge explosion and shock waves that managed to injure his internal system.

He raised his arm and a golden wound slit open at the back of his right hand. Drips of golden blood trickled down from the wound.

“What a good move! Divine Weapon Self Destruction!!”

Gerdmos who was by the side had a slight change of expression as well. Divine Weapon Self Destruction also depended on the Divine Weapon itself. The Divine Weapon Self Destruction did not have a great impact generally in the hands of humans. They were irrelevant to those who were already below the Divine Power, but for Dragons of Disaster, the worst Divine Weapons in their hands were at least created by Middle Divine Souls. Once these Divine Weapons self-destruct, the tremors caused would be extremely terrible.

“Nevermind, they have no more than three Divine Weapons in their hands!” Gerdmos said in a hushed tone.

As soon as his voice fell, he could see dozens of Divine Weapons shot out from the cave, exploding in all directions. It seemed to be radiating to all the areas around.

“They’re all fake!” Another red-robe man yelled.

Of course, Gerdmos knew they were all fake, but so what if he knew? What if there was a real one mixed among the fake ones?

He could not help but retreat quickly. The other red-robed man seemed to have the same thinking as him and retreated as well.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh!

To his surprise, all the Divine Weapons had a powerful surge force that broke through the blockade of the surrounding spells, going in all directions.

“Could they be real?” Gerdmos waved his hand and a large cloud of fire rushed toward the Divine Weapons.

Roar!!

One of the Divine Weapons could not withstand the scorch and straight away turned into a huge Green Dragon screaming in pain.

“It’s them! They’re trying to escape!?” Gerdmos’ expression changed. His body flickered as he instantly moved to the front of the Divine Weapon with the strongest force and reached out to grab it.

Boom!!!

Chapter 1336: Eve 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The tremendous explosion instantly spread around the entire cave. Huge mushroom clouds accompanied the terrifying red shock waves as they spread out to the surroundings.

Gerdmos paled, completely stunned by the self-destruction of the most powerful Divine Weapon.

“Plague!” He bellowed. He was already heavily injured from the battle with Fehra’s Incarnation and so he was unable to use half of his strength anymore. Now after being hit by such a powerful Divine Weapon, his injuries immediately increased from the original fifty percent to an eighty percent of damage. Even the sacred fire was severely impacted and lost half of its strength.

This was an extremely powerful Divine Weapon. Even if he was one of the three Monarchs, he would not have been able to withstand the impact from the immense shock waves of the Divine Power and was fatally injured.

After being duped and looking at the ‘Divine Weapons’ shooting across the sky, he dared not approach and could only wave his arms to use fire clouds to block them.

“Doomsday Rain of Fury!” From the other side, a red-robed man opened his arms, the light of Divinity radiated from him, turning into red lights that shot into the sky.

The sky rumbled and clumps of dense, red clouds appeared quickly…

Boom!

A red meteorite fell from the sky and crashed onto the ground.

A second one followed, then a third… Countless meteors and meteorites fell from the sky and blasted as they crashed onto the gray-black plains.

The plains that were already rugged before became even bumpier with more pits.

Under the bombardment of the meteor and meteorites, some of the Divine Weapons that were scattered around straight away disappeared into phantoms, and some revealed their real true forms. They were all fleeing dragons, while some others were indeed Semi-Divine Weapons or Divine Weapons.

Garen was amongst them as well. An enormous meteorite fell right in front of him and with a bang, the huge shockwave made his body receded at least a few meters backward.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a red-robed figure appeared before him. Gerdmos was holding a shrunken Dragon of Disaster by its neck, blocking his path with a ferocious look.

The intense blood breath and scorching Energy Field immediately fell on Garen.

Boom!

He suddenly felt his body sink, his body value that was already weakened by half dropped once again.

“The sixth one.” Gerdmos had a calm expression as he reached out to grab his neck.

An invisible pressure locked onto Garen’s neck, making him breathless and weak.

“It’s Soul Coercion!!” He was shocked. Such a situation could only occur when the gap between souls was too large. The power of Gods, the power of Divine Souls, he never knew what kind of nature they were.

Now that he was truly facing it for the very first time, he immediately understood that this was simply an ultimate sublimate soul. However, what made it different from a True Soul was the state of the sacred fire of the soul that had the power of pure faith. They used that faith as a mean to strengthen themselves, unlike True Soul who just absorbed all the power of a soul.

Faith was only a pure part of the strength of a soul.

Gerdmos grabbed onto Garen with a surge of an inexplicable aura of death.

Garen had a hunch that the second he touched this hand, his entire body including his Soul and Fighting Soul would be instantly taken away by the other person.

But he could watch as the arm inched closer and closer, unable to defend himself.

The difference between a Level-Twelve and a true God was indeed too big. Even after Gerdmos was heavily injured and he could not even unleash twenty percent of his powers, the changes of the nature of the strength was far beyond Garen, even as a Middle Demon Lord, could handle.

As the huge hand got closer and was about to touch the scales at Garen’s throat.

“Ah!!!”

Right at this moment, Garen suddenly shrieked.

A black necklace around his neck exploded by itself, black smoke immediately broke out of it and wrapped Gerdmos’ right arm.

“Ann!” Gerdmos’ expression changed and he immediately retreated.

But it was too late.

An exceedingly gigantic dragon arm shot out from the black smoke and grabbed onto his right arm.

“Gus…”

Ann’s seemingly perfect figure loomed behind the black smoke, but the voice that sounded from him was clearly a man’s.

“No! No no no!!! Ann, that’s not me!!!” Gerdmos’ face twisted more with fear.

He yelled as he started running towards the back.

Drained, Garen looked at him escaping. The black smoke that turned into a dragon arm held him tight and soon disappeared from sight.

Not long after, gigantic transparent distortions blasted on the distant plain and the sphere-shaped distortion lasted for more than ten seconds before slowly dissipating.

“Go!” Suddenly, a brass-colored dragon claw grabbed him and lifted him up before flying away swiftly into the distance.

It was Plague the Brass Dragon!

With a solemn expression, it held onto Garen as it flew, turning back every now and then to check behind.

“That was just a projection of Ann, it won’t hold him back much longer. We have to leave immediately!”

Garen felt weak to the point that he could barely open his eyelids.

The struggle just now seemed to consume much of his strength.

“Why… did you save me?” He asked softly.

“Why? That necklace of yours represents the subordinates approved by Ann. Saving you is equivalent to giving him face. Among the three Monarchs, Ann is known as the most brutal dragon of killing. Once when he was furious, he swallowed up billions of creatures in just one breath. But because he comprehended the space-time laws too well, Fehra and the other Gods could only suppress him, not kill him, because if they kill him now, he would be able to reverse history and return from the past.”

Garen’s eyes opened wide. This was the first time he had heard of such a strong description of Ann from another dragon race.

Brass Dragon said in a hushed tone.

“Even plenty of powerful existences don’t even know how many Ann truly exists. He’s able to pull all three of his figures to the same space-time. He’s the most powerful Dragon of Disaster in history, and the most legendary dragon of the Dragons of Shadows. Your nature has a trace of a Shadow Dragon which can break free under the imprisonment of Divine Power because the Divine Imprisonment is just a kind of imprisonment and you Shadow Dragons are best at imprisonments.”

He cast a glance at Garen.

“Seems like you don’t know anything at all.”

Garen just recovered a little bit of strength.

“He didn’t tell me much.” He could see that Plague the Brass Dragon was really trying to save him.

There was a change in Brass Dragon’s eyes. “They’re catching up!”

Garen sensed a threat rapidly approaching him from behind.

Looking back at the sky behind him, a gigantic Red Dragon was flying towards them. There was a trace of bloodlust in the dragon’s eyes.

“There are a few powerful disciples of Ann in the Abyss, let’s pray that we can survive till their arrival.” Brass Dragon finally spoke the truth. He rescued Garen due to his relationship with Ann, which was a good enough reason for Ann’s disciples from the Abyss to come to the rescue. What he had been looking for all along was this unknown rescue.

Garen understood and no longer spoke so he tried to restore his strength.

His current body attributes had been weakened mainly because of a ray of Fehra’s Divine Power that broke his Level-Nine spell immunity.

Facing these Divine Power natured attacks, he almost had no strength of resistance at all. Even with a stronger physique or if the other party weakened, his attributes were weakened by half so it was completely meaningless.

“Seems like I must study divinity and establish the Wizard Tower…” Garen had made up his mind. Facing the suppression of Divine Power this time around, his powerful physical strength did not do him justice at all.

Turning back to see, Gerdmos was chasing behind.

“We can’t let this guy catch up with us.”

As Brass Dragon flew, he threw something behind.

Boom!

The object exploded and turned into a giant made of elemental gas. Right when the Elemental Giant raised his fists preparing to smash downwards, Gerdmos’ mouthful of Dragon Breath pierced through the giant’s stomach, and his entire body started burning and slowly dissipated.

Brass Dragon started throwing all sorts of treasures messily behind. They had the most extreme self-destructive power that made those treasures unleash its great powers, but this kind of explosion could only be used once as it would self-destruct.

It was only a mere dozen seconds of effort and Gerdmos was getting closer and closer, and each time Brass Dragon threw out a treasure, it was just to block him.

Within the dozen seconds, he had already thrown out various high-leveled treasure, all of which were top-notch treasures that could make any non-Divine creature envious.

But Brass Dragon still threw everything out freely.

“If you have any tricks up your sleeves you better use it quickly! If we continue like this, we’re going to die!” Brass Dragon rushed Garen in the midst of pressing affairs.

Garen closed his eyes for a moment, turned his back and opened his eyes suddenly.

Whoosh whoosh!

Two white-blue rays burst out and shot towards Gerdmos.

It was the Poisonous Eye, which was also currently Garen’s most powerful attack.

He only tried its effect but unfortunately, when the two rays landed on Gerdmos’ body, they did not even leave a single mark on the scales.

He did not even need to defend an attack that could actually hurt a Level-Thirteen.

“Only Divine Power natured attacks can hurt him!” Brass Dragon explained impatiently. “Whatever Ann gave you in the past, just take it out quickly and use it! If he catches up with us, we’ll all die!”

Whoosh!

Just then, a huge fiery wing swooped by him. Although Brass Dragon dodge in time, half of his body was burnt black.

Garen did not possess anything that Ann gave him, he had not seen Ann for a very long time already.

“I’m the only hope of the Dragons of Disaster!!” Gerdmos yelled from behind. “If all of us merged as one, then we can truly become the greatest Dragon of Abyss!! All of you can’t escape! You can’t escape!!!”

He seemed to have gone absolutely crazy.

*******************

In the endless, pitch dark canyon.

At the center of the ancient matrix, under the hazy halo, Ann’s eyes that were closed tightly slowly opened.

“Gus… why did you force me… I didn’t mean to, I really don’t…”

She mumbled repeatedly, helplessness and sorrow all over her expression.

Slowly, a black obscure black ring appeared before her that displayed Gerdmos who was chasing after Garen and Brass Dragon.

The sadness in her eyes deepened.

“Gus… why did you forget everything I said back then?”

As she muttered, she held out her hand and scoffed.

Her slender hand went straight into the Light Screen image and grabbed Gerdmos.

“No!!! No!! Ann! It’s not my fault!! Let go of me!!” Gerdmos was only as big as a worm in Ann’s palm.

“We used to be so in love with each other…” Ann spoke sadly, “I loved you so much…”

She closed her eyes and popped Gerdmos in her mouth.

Chomp chomp…

The crisp chewing accompanied by the screams of Gerdmos and the faint forces of Divine Power disappeared in Ann’s mouth.

She chewed slowly as if she was tasting the last taste of her once good friend.

“No!!!” Gerdmos turned out to be not completely dead yet, his sacred fire let out a heartbreaking scream till the very last moment.

Gulp.

But everything disappeared along Ann’s gentle swallow.

The Light Screen vanished, and Ann sighed. However, it did not give off the feeling of falsehood, but it was like he really lost a true friend, a former lover.

“It’s you again… hooligans…” Ann’s half-closed eyes opened wide. “If it weren’t for you guys, Gus wouldn’t have to die. Everything is your fault. Seems like I will have to have a good chat with all of you …”

Chapter 1337: Development 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was a soft swoosh.

Gerdmos’ entire dragon body disappeared from behind suddenly.

As Garen and Brass Dragon were flying, they watched as Gerdmos, somehow, was suddenly swallowed up by a gigantic black hole, and there was no more sound at all.

“What happened!” Brass Dragon was shocked but still did not dare to stop and continued to fly forward, only coming to a stop gradually after flying out tens of thousands of meters away.

Garen broke out from his dragon claws and was finally able to fly independently. Only he could sort of guessed what had just happened.

Without a word, his eyes were fixated on the direction in which Gerdmos disappeared from.

“Thank you very much, Plague.”

“It’s really a great loss this time,” The old Bass Dragon responded with a wry smile as if he had guessed something right. He looked around the surroundings.

The two dragons had somehow arrived at a large golden desert.

“This is the Desert of Dead Souls. We seem to have flown over hundreds of thousands of miles,” the Bass Dragon sensed the area. There were no creatures at all. Clearly, they were all frightened away by their Draconic Aura.

“What are your plans next?” Garen glanced at the burned area on his back. The Divine Crystals were like maggots that clung onto him obstinately, it was indeed troublesome.

“I live in the Maggots Abyss, you can come to visit me if you’re free. The pressing matter now is to get rid of the Divine Power of your body. Getting rid of these things is not as easy as it seems,” Brass Dragon said helplessly.

“Is there a time limit for this state of weakness?” Garen was slightly shocked.

“It’d be nice if there was,” Bass Dragon sighed. “If your confrontation awareness isn’t strong enough, then he won’t be able to eat away your strength on a daily basis and convert all energy into Divine Power and strengthen himself. Fehra’s power is just that overbearing and disgusting!”

In the Abyss, he was not afraid at all to mention the God name, Fehra, who was far away at the Mountain of Heavens.

“Even I would need at least five years to get rid of it completely. Alright then, I’ll go back first. The other two Monarchs will definitely punish Gerdmos for destroying the order regarding this matter. Whatever happens after, we have nothing to do with each other anymore. Just a pity of my Divine Weapon though…”

He had a pained look on his face.

“The Upper Divine Weapon…” Garen’s face pained as well. The only thing that managed to injure Gerdmos severely was the only Upper Divine Weapon that the elder dragon took out.

He was no doubt a Level-Fifteen elite existence, his ample collection was indeed terrifying.

One Divine Weapon was already very powerful, but every single Divine Weapon was well-established and the owners could be traced. One destroyed was just one less weapon, but the elder yellow dragon was actually willing to use an Upper Divine Weapon to self-destruct.

Seems like the water behind him ran pretty deep too…

Garen reminded himself to stay vigilant.

Both dragons were somewhat restraint with each other. After exchanging contact information, they flew in the direction of their own nest.

Garen had somewhat gained a little benefit from the raid this time around. The analyzed true divinity was a huge help for him to build an analysis system of true divinity.

The whole void was now constantly trying to invade this world and the Gods of this world were actively responding against the invasion of the void.

Every creature was vigorously accumulating all their strength under this huge crisis, even Gerdmos, a Colossal Dragon that was comparable to Divine Soul.

The main force of the battlefield was still in those three places.

The Main Plane, Mountain of Heavens, and the endless Abyss.

From the information that Garen received from the snail man, it showed that there were already tens of millions of Void Creatures that had passed through the raid of the Gods’ and churches’ powerhouses and were scattered into the major empire regions of the Main Plane.

They straight away entered dreams of all creatures, almost impossible to be identified or found.

The church’s powerhouses were trying to distinguish them by various means.

As for the Abyss, there seemed to be no movement. In reality, nobody knew exactly how many Void Creatures had entered this place, they were just not exposed.

Without any further sign of danger, he returned to the Vengeance Fortress safely.

The first thing Garen did was return to his own place to rest in the attempt to get rid of the Divine Crystals that were negatively affecting his state.

*******************

In the dark Secret Chamber.

Dense blue ice crystals were condensed all over the black metal walls.

The ground was covered by a thick layer of white-blue snowflakes as well.

Garen squatted in the middle of the Secret Chamber, a faint white gas was constantly squirting out from his mouth and nose that kept the room temperature stabilized at a constantly low level.

Under the erosion of this white gas, the Divine Crystals on his back were slowly melting at an incredibly slow speed. If it was not for extreme fine observation, it would be completely impossible to see the Divine Crystals melt.

“Your Excellency Garen.”

Suddenly, a black mist appeared in front of Garen that quickly condensed into an enormous Wild Boar.

The Wild Bear weirdly stood on two legs and was dressed like a gentleman. A hoof was even slowly reaching up to the black tophat on the top of his head.

“It’s you, Gru.” Garen recognized him. This guy was just like the snail man. They had entirely given up on entering Dream World with their bodies and became a messenger between the great Demon Lords.

“What’s the matter?”

Garen shrouded in the white gas. The Wild Boar could barely see his situation but only sensed a huge surge of Chill that came rushing towards him. He shuddered and spoke hurriedly.

“Your Excellency Garen’s strength is getting stronger and stronger and no doubt worthy of being the Deputy Commander of Vengeance Fortress. Uh… I’m here because I have two news.”

“Speak.”

Garen responded calmly, too lazy to even open his eyes. As the white gas shrouded around him, he could sense nothing although the Wild Boar was standing face to face across him.

“The first news, after the information that you sent reached Mother Stream Alliance, two beings came forward claiming that they are your old acquaintances and they hope to see you,” Wild Boar said as he was weighing his words.

“Old acquaintances?” Garen opened his eyes, “What kind of old acquaintances?”

“One female and one male. From their looks, they seemed a bit broken down,” Wild Boar answered hurriedly.

“Let them come, we’ll know when we meet. What about the other message?” Garen closed his eyes again.

“The other news is that a Demon Lord nearby hopes that you’re able to share some of the tasks. The Alliance’s plan has reached the point where fortified points have to be opened up in the Abyss. However, in order to not attract the conscious of the Abyss to resist, the required manpower has to enter slowly. The three other Demon Lords nearby have already shared out some of the manpower. After knowing that you have a firm hold here, they hope that you can also join in.”

“Aiding the manpower…” Garen sank into deep thoughts and did not reply immediately. This was a big risk. Once discovered, even Lady Vengeance would be the first to kill him.

“A certain date a year later, Deception Demon Master Sandola will come to the Abyss. We are now just preparing for Her Excellency, Lady Deception,” Wild Boar whispered.

“Is there any benefit?” Garen was not a master of free labor. Moreover, he was not even aiding his own Endor’s people. Naturally, he had to be remunerated.

“Of course,” Wild Boar responded quickly. “Her Excellency, Lady Deception promised that whoever lends a hand in this matter, every single one will be rewarded a Ten Million Level Incantation Stone.”

Ten Million Level!

Garen was slightly moved. An Incantation Stone was something used to store Souls. It being Ten Million Level meant that it had at least tens of millions of Average Souls. Even during the Blood Wars, after he had been secretly snatching so many Souls from the Abyss for so long, he could still not get hundreds of thousands of souls. If he was to be able to get a Ten Million Level soul, perhaps he could use a Semi-Divine Weapon to filter and absorb through and think of the best way to increase his Soul Limit.

Moreover, if he studied divinity thoroughly, the number of souls needed would be greater.

However, the time span of one year was too short. He was still not finished with analyzing the divinity on his hands. With the information all undigested, he would be biting off more than he could chew.

He thought about it carefully.

“I’m in no rush, I don’t need too many things at the moment. But still,” Garen paused, “even though I may not be able to assist, I can provide supplies and safe hiding spots for those coming to aid and hunt.”

The Wild Boar smiled with joy hearing Garen’s words.

“Even if it’s just that, we are extremely grateful to you. All the while, the Abyss never had many supply points. Therefore, if you can guarantee that you can provide the supply points here, it’ll be of great help in our development.”

“No problem, we belong to the same camp anyway, helping each other is what we should do.” Garen nodded, “alright, you can go now.”

“Alright, thank you for your generosity.” The Wild Boar then slowly turned into black mist and disappeared.

Garen once again closed his eyes and started to get rid of the Divine Crystals on his back.

*******************

In the following two months, Garen never stepped out of his residence. The three Blasphemy Knights, Irene and the other two, were responsible for all the miscellaneous affairs whereas Andrew was in charge of leading the Winter Army to join the Blood Wars.

Garen gave all of his war trophies to him for distribution.

There was no denying that Andrew was talented in leadership. After signing a contract with Garen, his strength was piled up under a large number of resources and soon reached the breakthrough point. He had been stuck at the peak of Level Nine for now.

After getting Garen’s guidance, he also understood the real gap between Level Nine and Level Ten and above, and so he began to form his own unique ability.

During killing, this guy formed an incredible energy field which he termed Demon Halo, which was purely based on Garen’s powerful frost energy field. He broke into Level Ten successfully.

This was good news.

Garen finally had a subordinate who was a powerhouse good enough as a line-up.

As for him, he was totally ignorant of the outside world, devoting himself to cleanse out the Divine Crystals even though the process of removing it was extremely slow and boring.

Hence he began to rebuild the device that Energy Machinists mostly rely on, the Willpower computing brain.

During his time as an Energy Machinist, the computing speed of a Willpower brain was even more powerful than the most advanced brain of the Mech era.

To analyze divinity, the brain of Willpower had to be the best method to analyze.

Every time during a Blood War, he would hand his Semi-Divine Weapon to Andrew to allow it to continue absorbing a large number of souls. Then, he would absorb the souls from the Semi-Divine Weapon and convert them into potential points.

As more and more potential points accumulate to the point that they were impossible to use, Garen would slowly turn it towards his intelligence.

In the time of accumulating the establishment of his Willpower brain, Garen set his place as a receiving point, welcoming the first batch of Void visitors at the same time.

Chapter 1338: Development 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So this is the Vengeance Fortress?” Five men and women dressed in various clothes, looking as though they came from the circus, walked out of the Teleportation Light Portal slowly.

The Light Portal was the fixed-point teleportation portal that Garen had ordered some Wizards to make. It led straight to a place called the Green Oakstone Plane.

Similar to the Primary Plane, most of the inhabitants living here were humans.

“Looks like it,” replied a man who looked like he might be the leader in a low voice. “This is the territory of Winter Sigh, and according to the information, this place should be relatively safe. We can choose to join the Blood Wars under the name of Winter Sigh, and we can also use this place as a base for exploring the surroundings.”

“Let’s rest here for a few days before we make our preparations,” said a voluptuous woman softly.

There were only a few elder demons, more than two meters tall, standing guard around this teleportation portal. They did not even look at the situation over here and isolated this small area completely.

There was a newly-opened shop in this area, with all sorts of potions, scrolls, and magical items displayed on the counter within. The shop owner was a drowsy little Succubus. It was the relative Garen’s two Succubi Subordinates had brought over.

The visitors from the Void took a stroll around the area and only found one hotel, one restaurant, and that one shop.

Every other part of that huge space was empty. They were clearly the first batch of visitors to arrive here.

Garen had put the few Level Ten powerhouses he had signed contracts with in charge of ensuring these shops’ safety. They were scattered across a few spots around the area, and they seemed to be doing their own thing, but in truth, they were keeping an eye on everything that was happening in this area.

The visitors from the Void bought some scrolls and potions from the shop, and then looked for a Level Ten powerhouse, receiving the Winter Sigh’s dragon-shaped insignia that allowed them to participate in the Blood War. After that, they left the city hastily, clearly in a hurry to join the slaughter in order to obtain more power and progress.

Lady Vengeance barely governed any matters here at all. That was why nobody really interfered with what Garen was doing in his own territory, and no one batted an eyelid even when he carved out an area and turned it into a temporary supply point for Void Creatures.

Anyone who could set up a supply point in the Abyss had to be either extremely crafty or extremely powerful.

If Garen had not used his connections with Ann, there was no way he could have gotten such immense authority from the start either. At the most, he would have had to work his way up the ranks from his initial position as an advanced thug, racking up contributions slowly.

But thanks to his relationship with Ann, he could leap all the way to the top because of the fact that he once studied under the same teacher as Lady Vengeance. He became Deputy Commander of the Vengeance Fortress, wielding awe-inspiring authority. That was also a stroke of luck.

Once the first batch of visitors arrived here, they realized that this place was relatively stable and decided to set up base here, beginning their Blood Wars to accumulate slaughters. Soon enough, word got out. There was a second batch, a third, a fourth…

Now, there were more and more visitors from the Void seeping into the major planes. They disguised themselves as various races and came to the Abyss one after the other, arriving at the supply point Garen had set up. Using the Vengeance Fortress as their base and Garen’s name, they began to spread massacres everywhere.

Within a mere five or six months, the name of Winter Sigh began to spread rapidly.

And after an attack by a powerful Level Thirteen Thunder Elemental, the name instantly reached the pinnacle of popularity.

This Void Creature whose host was a Thunder Elemental had stirred an uproar by killing three of the opposing Hell Army Warlord-general’s four sons. As a result, it was pursued for more than ten thousand miles and somehow managed to return to the Vengeance Fortress, barely avoiding death.

It wore the insignia of Winter Sigh, Garen’s symbol, so with that, Garen instantly became famous.

At the same time, the Vengeance Fortress’ reputation as a supply point was also beginning to spread through the ranks of the Void Creatures, with more and more Void Creatures arriving here. They carried Garen’s insignia and symbol, hunting and slaughtering things all over the place. His influence grew, further and stronger.

Out of the several hundred fortresses that already existed in the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains, the Vengeance Fortress was originally just another new fortress, and the weakest one to boot. But these Void Creatures surged in by the dozens, massacring many devils around the area and even some of the more unruly demons.

The influence of the Vengeance Fortress also began to increase rapidly.

The businesses, such as shops and hotels, that Garen set up in the supply point area also began to gradually increase in number, and the rate at which he earned soul-cocoons sped up as well. His wealth snowballed, and the Void Creatures from all those different planes also brought plenty of rare materials that could be used for trade, greatly reducing the time Garen needed to construct his Wizard Tower.

Once he became aware of this beneficial cycle, Garen gave a share of the materials he had obtained as taxes to Lady Vengeance and the other Deputy Commander, instantly earning the approval of the Lady and the support of his colleague.

With the support of Lady Vengeance, Garen could easily suppress even some advanced-level disturbances that appeared at the supply point. His powers were drastically reduced right now, but with Lady Vengeance’s support, even the strongest disturbance could be suppressed in the shortest possible time.

And the army under his control had also begun to search around for the materials required to build a Wizard Tower.

Large amounts of resources flowed ceaselessly into Garen’s private space.

As his injury healed, he also bought many Wizard Slaves who were Level Five and above to help him construct the Wizard Tower.

Everything seemed to be on the right track.

In the blink of an eye, a year had almost passed.

*******************

In the sky above the Vengeance Tower, Garen flapped his wings slowly as he flew. He looked down on the half of the fortress that was under his jurisdiction, patrolling it.

The Winter Army already had about five hundred thousand soldiers on reserve, comprised fully demons of different types. At the same time, Andrew had also built up a special elite assault squadron called White Feather. There were only ten members in this team, and they were all pinnacle powerhouse Wizards from everywhere, from all the different planes. The highest-leveled one was Level Twelve, and the lowest was Level Ten. They all had vast resources as well as considerable authority. Some were even the heirs of some powerful factions that had come here to gather experience. They came from all walks of life and signed temporary short-term contracts, stating that they would only fight on behalf of the Vengeance Fortress for a short while. They could form a powerful Three-Dimensional Rune Matrix, and at their highest power, they could even temporarily confine a pinnacle powerhouse for some time. It was very impressive.

The army reserve and White Feather.

These two comprised Garen’s greatest asset. His own powers were shocking, but that also meant he naturally needed to use many more resources. Thankfully Garen could make use of the Void Creatures’ hunting and spreading out, and he also grabbed half of yet another large piece of land by the shores of the Underground River. That way, he could harvest many soul-cocoons every year to make up for his losses. Like this, he was more or less breaking even.

Garen looked down from his vantage point in the sky and saw many hunting teams come and go through the fortress’ side door. They all wore the insignia of Winter Sigh. Some of the returning teams had suffered heavy losses, while others had a full bounty. And the exiting teams were all fully armed.

With such intense slaughtering going on, the area also spawned houses of desire opened specifically by Succubi, functioning as a place for the powerhouses in the middle of their slaughters to vent their desires and frustrations.

The place had a large collection of humans, Elves, and Succubi as entertainment tools.

Garen’s two Succubi subordinates came up with this idea, and this also brought him a significant amount of profit every month.

There was even an auction house built in the small area. One of the Level Ten powerhouses Garen had signed a Soul Contract with in charge of hosting and running the auction house. Occasionally, when a small team obtained a treasure or item that was not easy to deal with, the auction house would simply buy it at a low price and auction it off at a higher price.

More and more people were gathering at the auction house nowadays, and even the powerful beings from the fortresses nearby would occasionally send their Projections over for a look.

The area, less than half the size of the fortress, was actually developing rapidly.

Every second of every day, Garen was earning a tremendous amount of wealth and resources. At the same time, he could also mobilize many various combat forces.

By the time he glided across the sky above the auction house, satisfied, Garen’s injuries were already half-healed, and his power had also returned to Level Eleven.

Since he was flying lower now, he carried a treasure with him that hid his aura in order to maintain his dignity and authority as a Deputy Commander.

Soon enough, Garen flew to the most central part of the area. There was a spot there that was left empty, and about a hundred Wizards were busily casting spells there, building a tall cylindrical tower. There were also many Engineering Puppets floating outside the tower, laboring away constantly, looking busy as a swarm of bees.

The Advanced Wizard in charge of this place saw Garen land and hurriedly walked up to greet him.

“Deputy Commander, progress has reached up to 80%, and all the Magical Formations are more or less complete. All that’s left is the Tower Soul. You just have to find one last Tower Soul, sir, and complete the Enchantment, then everything will be complete,” explained the Wizard calmly.

“Very good.” Satisfied, Garen raised his head and looked at the giant Wizard Tower, almost a thousand meters tall. For the sake of this tower, he had later expanded the area, until it covered a large piece of land outside the fortress as well. In order to expand the territory of the fortress, he had worked several tens of thousands of little demons and other slaves to death.

The entire Wizard Tower was like a slender, long white staff. There was a ball of pure white ice suspended above its peak, and a transparent ring of pale silver power circled around its middle.

There were four dragon statues depicting Garen himself in different poses built around the base of the Tower. The backs of these statues were all connected to the Tower, so they helped to secure the base while also functioning as decorations and defense matrixes.

The Advanced Wizard explained to Garen.

“If we can completely finish building it, the whole tower will have a flowing barrier of white electricity. In our initial test designs of this electric barrier, we found that it can reach Level Thirteen and can withstand twelve Level Thirteen attacks. If we have enough energy in the Energy Pools, and if the attacks come at a frequency of no more than one attack every five seconds, theoretically, the electric barrier could even defend the attacks infinitely.”

“Not bad…” Garen nodded, satisfied. His dragon eyes slowly lit up with pale blue lights.

The Energy Machinist Willpower Neuroprocessor was complete. He had a large number of potential points as back-up, and besides, he had done all this before, so he did not encounter any bottlenecks.

That was why he could reach the pinnacle that he had once accomplished within a mere month. Now, he was already beginning to rebuild the Biochemical Pool and the experimental platform.

With the large number of resources he earned from the Blood Wars and his businesses, Garen probably only needed a few months to create the best models of the Biochemical Pool and the experimental platform.

When that happened, it would no longer be just a dream to recreate the Energy Machinists’ Biochemical Army. This type of army would truly be a powerful military force that was loyal to him and him alone. The Biochemical Pool could create regular armies and soldiers, whereas the experimental platform produced absolute peak-level elites. The two complemented each other.

But all this was secondary, because the Abyss never had a shortage of cannon fodder and soldiers.

What Garen truly had his eye on was still the Willpower Neuroprocessor’s immense computing power.

The Energy Machinist training method he was recultivating was the most standard NIS training method from back then, because this training method was the most original. It may not result in the best creatures or effects, but the increase in computing power was excellent and evenly distributed.

And right now, Garen’s eyes stared straight at the Wizard Tower. Instantly, his computing power spread out rapidly, and soon he obtained a series of matrices and structural data, proving that the Advanced Wizard was not lying.

“I hear that a lot of the materials you guys bought recently came from the dragons?”

Garen asked suddenly.

The Advanced Wizard paused and then reacted.

“Yes, the teams that returned recently seemed to have sustained significant casualties, but the materials they brought back all had a different degree of increase in quality, and most of them came from White Dragons. We’re guessing that they might have come into conflict with White Dragon Mountain.”

“White Dragon Mountain…” Garen mused.

Chapter 1339: Construction 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“We suspect that the most recent hunting teams may have come into conflict with the dragons of White Dragon Mountain,” said the Advanced Wizard worriedly. “The White Dragon Mountain’s in the sixteenth level of the Abyss, it’s the territory of the Abyssal Demon Dragons. I’m just afraid that they might come here and demand answers.”

Garen thought about it for a while.

“Don’t worry about it too much, the White Dragon Mountain is still far away from the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains. I have Lady Vengeance behind me, and no matter what, even if they come here, this is still my territory. Even a pinnacle powerhouse would not be able to do much. You guys just do your own thing.”

The Advanced Wizard still wanted to say something, but Garen stopped him.

“Alright, carry on.”

“…Okay.” The Advanced Wizard heaved a long breath. After he signed that contract, he had basically thrown his lot in with Garen, so he could not help but worry about these other troublesome possibilities.

Leaving the Wizard Tower slowly, Garen headed toward the right to continue his patrol. This was Andrew’s base.

Recently, he had opened a new large-scale fluorite mine nearby and was currently gathering people to go down and excavate it. At the same time, he was using these fluorites to construct a military base nearby, specifically there to defend the mine.

Garen casually waved his hand through the air, and instantly a half-moon screen appeared before him, displaying Andrew in his suit of armor sitting on a high seat as he discussed something with a bunch of people who looked like merchants.

“Looks like these are merchants from other planes. The development of the fluorite mine was on the right track as well…”

Garen did not disturb them. Turning off the screen, he checked on the progress of Irene and her two companions.

After he sold off that male knight once, the man had gone through a round of torture before Garen bought him back again, and this time he was a lot more obedient. He worked quietly and properly with his two companions, having clearly experienced the brutality of the Abyss’ slave market.

All three of them experienced changes in their personality, growing colder and more extreme. Garen transferred them, putting them in charge of punishments and other miscellaneous jobs.

That put them to good use.

The other vacancies were filled by the remaining Level Ten powerhouses.

“Sir, Kratos is requesting a meeting.”

Suddenly, the Succubus’ voice came from Garen’s bracelet.

“Kratos…? Why is he here?” Garen was slightly shocked. Back then, Kratos nearly killed him, and now he still dared to come to Garen’s territory. Before this, there was no trace of him at all, not even a glimpse of his shadow.

“I don’t know, but he did not come alone…” replied the Succubus in a small voice.

“Bring them back to my mansion, I’ll be back there in a moment.”

Garen thought about it for a moment and gave the orders.

His mansion was the safest place. Many powerhouses had placed many matrixes there, and Lady Vengeance had also personally installed a single-use secret mechanism that could be activated at any time to devastating effects. Even if the attacker was a pinnacle powerhouse, he would still have the time to escape and ensure his own safety.

Turning around and flying back toward his mansion, Garen quickly drew a rune in the air with his claw.

Instantly, the rune in the Void exploded apart and vanished.

“White Feather, awaiting your orders.”

A gentle woman’s voice rang out slowly in the air.

“Target location, my mansion, set up a Collaborative Matrix. The guests this time might not be that easy to deal with,” Garen said determinedly.

“Understood.”

***********************

In the giant white mansion floating in mid-air.

After he shrank himself, Kratos’ body was only two meters tall. He was shaking his dragon head and looked left and right, considering the decor in this mansion.

Nearby, there were two other white-robed elders seated with him. Compared to properly he was sitting, these two elders were both closing their eyes slightly, sitting quietly in place, completely motionless. They seemed to be pretending to sleep.

Vaguely, several powerful auras gradually appeared outside the mansion. Kratos was not particularly strong, but his senses were unnaturally sharp, so he could sense that several auras, each at least Level Ten, were slowly surrounding this place. His expression also grew slightly solemn.

But when he turned around and glanced at the two elders subtly, his heart instantly settled again.

“For our clan to produce a new generation descendent like this, not bad.” One elder opened his eyes, his expression actually comforted.

“Yes.” The other elder spoke concisely, responding with only one word.

“Please have some tea.” A Succubus waved her seductive waist, dressed only in a thin translucent veil, as she came up and served them three cups of blood-like tea.

“Has your master not returned yet?” Kratos ran his hand down the Succubus’ thigh, his eyes narrowed pervertedly, as he asked in a low voice. “It doesn’t really matter if he keeps me waiting here, but if he wastes the time of these two lords from the White Dragon Mountain, isn’t Garen thinking just a little too much of himself?” He purposely raised his voice as he said this.

One of the two elders frowned slightly, but did not respond.

“I see, so it’s the Elders from the White Dragon Mountain who have come visiting. It’s Garen’s fault for not greeting you in time.” Just as the Succubus was about to explain, a clear voice came instantly from outside the door.

The doors were thrown wide open, and Garen’s shrunken body flew in slowly, landing on the ground. He was just about as tall as a man.

“Since you know that we’re from the White Dragon Mountain, I believe you must also know the reason we’re here, yes?” One of the elders stood up, looking at Garen with an admiring gaze.

“The reason you two are here…” Garen paused slightly. “I truly don’t know. May I know why the two of you have come to our Vengeance Fortress? Pardon my bluntness, but my relationship with the White Dragon Mountain isn’t that good, is it…?”

“You’re being modest, Deputy Commander.” One of the elders laughed. “Although it is true that we’re not on the best of terms, no matter what you’re still a member of our White Dragon Mountain. The blood of the White Dragons flows through your veins. I believe even you cannot deny this, no?”

“That is indeed…” Garen did not know what these two were planning by coming here, but faced with two Level Fifteen pinnacle Ancient Dragons, even he had to be cautious.

“Then that makes things easier.” The elder continued to smile. “There have been indeed many misunderstandings between us in the past, but seeing that we’re connected by blood, none of that is a problem. Our Ancient Parliament has unanimously decided to allow you back into the Main Clan, back under the Main Clan’s protection. The Vengeance Fortress can also act as a base for our Main Clan in this area, what a happy coincidence.”

Garen looked at the smile on his face and felt his heart sink.

He did not know how his reputation reached that place, but seeing as the White Dragon Mountain had already sent someone here, that clearly meant they were planning to get serious.

The reason he had to escape to the Abyss in a hurry was that of two emissaries from White Dragon Mountain, and now that he had finally steadied his footing and begun to develop his influence here, that damned place still had the nerve to send someone here and try to take over his territory?

Could things really go that well for them?

He smiled coldly in his heart. Well, if you want to play pretend, two can play at that game.

“Although I desperately want to return to the great White Dragon Mountain Main Clan, unfortunately I’m also facing some challenging problems over here…” Garen’s expression was full of deep regret.

“Problems?” The other elder raised his eyebrow. “The two of us are here to solve your problems for you.”

The two Level Fifteen pinnacle powerhouses would be the strongest people here, aside from the Fortress Master. They did indeed have the right to say something like that.

“Oh?” Garen’s heart sank. What they were saying was becoming slightly obvious now.

But if two Level Fifteen powerhouses really wanted to make things difficult for him, all he could do was run away in an instant. However, without Lady Vengeance here right now, it was practically impossible to keep the two of them here.

In truth, by coming here, the White Dragon Mountain was already making their intentions quite clear.

They did not really care about him when he had not really developed yet in the past, but now that he was making ground and had such a vast enterprise under his belt, some of the for-profit organizations within the White Dragon Mountain was trying to devour him whole under the name of the Main Clan. White Dragons were selfish and self-centered by nature, so it was understandable.

But understanding it was one thing, for Garen to just submit to the White Mountain… That was bordering on a daydream.

“Whatever problems you have, just state them all and we’ll solve them for you,” said the other elder concisely. Anyone could tell at a glance that he was the straightforward and cold type.

“My biggest problem now is that I can’t steady my footing here in the Fortress… I lack truly high-level powerhouses here to help me hold the fort. That’s why many of the mercenaries from the outside planes don’t listen to my authority at all.” Garen’s expression was helpless.

“Although I really want to return to the Main Clan as well, I’m still facing someone who’s trying to challenge my position as Commander right now.”

He came up with a random excuse.

“Oh? Who dares to challenge your position?” The old man raised an eyebrow. “Tell me who it is, and I’ll eat ’em!”

“It’s a guy called Nylirica.” Garen looked troubled as well. “I still haven’t recovered from the injuries I sustained from the last time I agreed to his challenge for a duel, and now I have no choice but to accept yet another challenge. After all, this concerns the position of Commander. These are the laws of the Fortress, and also the laws of the Abyss.”

“Nylirica?” The two old men exchanged a glance, indicating that they had never heard this name.

“That’s fine, we’ll deal with this person for you,” the slightly colder old man replied in a low voice.

Garen could tell that the two old men had stayed in their nest for too long and were not so aware of the ways of the world. Although they were powerful, they seemed slightly stiff when it came to these matters. They bought Garen’s story, hook, line, and sinker.

Garen’s heart was decided. As long as they went off in search of this Nyrilica, everything else could be easily dealt with… Once he thought of that, he began to approach the two old men passionately.

“This isn’t just an excuse of yours, is it?”

Suddenly, Kratos’ words instantly cooled down the atmosphere that had just begun to warm up.

The two old men looked at Garen suspiciously once more.

Garen hurriedly explained, “An excuse? Kratos, I know I offended you before, and we have some bad blood between us, but how could I possibly dare to simply lie to these two Ancient Dragon Masters? You just have to ask some questions around the Fortress to know whether or not this Nyrilica is the troublesome problem I said he is, so there’s just no way for me to lie, now, is there?”

“That’s true. If he’s strong enough for you to find him troublesome, this guy must be no ordinary fellow. Such a being can’t possibly be unknown around the Fortress. We’ll just have to ask any passerby and we’ll immediately know the truth,” said the slightly friendlier elder, nodding his head in agreement.

The atmosphere instantly calmed down again.

“But who knows, maybe you found an outsider to be your accomplice, trying to…” Kratos did not complete his sentence and instead began to laugh evilly.

Garen saw the two elders turn their suspicious gazes upon him once more.

He cursed inwardly. These two geezers were pretty easy to fool to start with, but this Kratos was getting in the way. It looked like Garen needed to find a chance to kill off this guy as soon as possible.

The intent to kill rose in his heart.

But on the surface, he continued to perpetuate his lie.

“If I could find such a powerful outsider to collude with me, haha, do you really think I would still only be a Deputy Commander?”

Kratos was merely at the pinnacle of Level Nine, and yet he dared to act so bold in front of Garen.

Garen’s gaze on him instantly turned vicious.

Ans Kratos actually met his gaze, completely unafraid.

“I hear that Commander Garen was initially ambushed by the emissaries from the White Dragon Mountain, and that was how your essence as one of the Dragons of Disaster was revealed. In the end, the Snow City from the Primary Plane chased you here into the Abyss. It wouldn’t be surprising if you harbored a grudge against White Dragon Mountain…” Kratos had even investigated the intel about this matter thoroughly. Right now, he was staring at Garen with a malicious gaze.

“This guy…!” Garen’s heart sank, and as expected, he saw that the two elders had grown suspicious.

Chapter 1340: Construction 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The White Dragon Mountain is by no means a single entity, there are many factions within it as well. Yes, I do hate those two emissaries to the core, but that has nothing to do with these two powerhouses before me. Besides, they’ve come here especially to help me solve my problems,” Garen retorted. “I have no interest in pushing away my own helpers.”

He looked at Kratos.

“However, you, Kratos, made an enemy of me in the past. You knew that these two masters are here especially to meet me, and yet you came along with them. Add that to your words from earlier, and are you sure you’re not here just to raise suspicions between us?!”

As soon as he said that, the two geezers’ gazes on Kratos changed slightly as well.

Kratos was completely flushed red as he stared at Garen with eyes full of hatred, but he did not know what to say just then either. His antagonizing attitude aimed at creating a rift between them was too evident earlier, which made it hard for him to deny right now.

“Alright, both of you, take a step back. After all, Kratos is here on behalf of Wanku Fortress. He’s here on business matters this time.” The friendly elder hurriedly tried to smooth things over.

“Hmph.” The other elder harrumphed coldly, and his gaze on Kratos had become slightly unfriendly as well.

Kratos knew that he could not stay here any longer, so he decided to just leave. Before he left, he gave Garen one fierce glare.

Garen hesitated but still did not make a move.

Kratos was here on behalf of the Wanku Fortress, which meant that if Garen attacked him now, he would be attacking the Wanku Fortress. That would definitely greatly anger the Wanku Fortress Master, and then it just would not be worth it.

Besides, since Kratos dared to come here alone, that must mean he had done all the necessary preparations. If Garen attacked and still could not keep him here, things would get very troublesome.

Garen persuaded the two elders properly and then sent someone to follow Kratos. As expected, the guy still had another bodyguard, another mysterious character with an obscure aura who followed closely behind him.

After he settled those two old geezers, giving them all sorts of tasty food, delicious drinks, and fun distractions, Garen turned around and left the mansion. Bringing two members of the White Feather Guard with him, he headed straight for an underground cave outside the city.

*******************

Upon entering the underground cave, taking many twists and turns in the dark tunnel, he walked on for goodness knew how long, and finally saw the wall at the end of the cave appear before him.

Garen gestured at the two White Feathers behind him to stop, and he walked forward alone.

He knocked the wall lightly. The stone wall immediately began to fade on its own, like an illusion, and Garen instantly walked into another dark black ancient temple.

There was a faint illusion-like fog permeating through the temple. If you were not paying attention, you would feel as though this fog was everywhere, but when you looked at the fog carefully, you would notice that they did not seem to exist at all, and it was the distortion and refraction of light.

By now, a few figures had already gathered in the temple.

When they saw Garen enter, the figures all turned around.

“Commander, why did you summon us here so urgently?” said one voice drily.

“An important event is approaching, and this is the crucial moment right now. We should avoid meeting as much as possible, just in case anything goes wrong,” someone else said softly.

“I have an extremely troublesome problem that I need your help with,” said Garen seriously.

The group before him was a small group called Proof of Deception. They were an underground organization, and even the weakest of these members were at Level Twelve. One of them even vaguely had the aura of a Demigod.

A Demigod! That was a being as powerful as Lady Vengeance’s true body, that was more than enough to become the Fortress Master of a fortress in the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains.

Such a being had actually appeared in this small group, and that was also the main reason Garen treated this group so solemnly.

If it were not for the fact that he was backed up by the almighty Ann, he probably would not even have the right to sit here and talk to these beings on equal terms.

Although Proof of Deception treated him relatively respectfully, they were not his subordinates. When they heard that he needed help, they instantly fell silent.

“This matter could even provide you more souls in preparation for the important event around the corner.” Garen smiled faintly. “I believe all of you are still fretting over a source of Advanced Souls, no?”

“Oh? You have a way?” said the leader of the Proof of Deception, the one that almost seemed to be a Demigod.

Garen smiled.

“I wouldn’t say I have a way, but I happen to have two ready-made souls…”

“If we can have two more pinnacle souls among the offerings to the Deception Demon Master, perhaps we might be able to speed up milord’s rate of regeneration?”

“But what about the chaos that may cause?” said Proof of Deception’s leader, frowning. “Every Level Fifteen peak powerhouse has deep roots and foundations. When they’ve reached that level, even if they die, their souls will be retrieved by the God they revere. If we steal such a soul, our troubles will be endless.”

“I’m not afraid of trouble.” Garen’s expression darkened. “Besides, didn’t we come to this world in order to create trouble?”

He was stuck at a bottleneck, and there were only two ways someone with enough power could break through to Level Twelve. One was in divinity research, but that required a Wizard Tower to block out the Gods’ detection.

The second was the method he had newly discovered, utilizing the Enneahedron and the evolution of his Void Original Opus.

Throughout just the past year, he had seen some Void Creatures use the Enneahedron with his own eyes. They slaughtered indiscriminately within a few short months, and went from lower than Level Eight all the way up to Level Thirteen, advancing so quickly that even Garen could barely believe it.

These Void Creatures only stopped when they reached Level Thirteen, having apparently reached a bottleneck. But such a speed of progression had already surpassed how Garen’s pace from back then.

According to his secret observations, those Void Creatures also seemed to be the souls of middle-level Demon Lords. Just like him, they had all sorts of special abilities, with a great variety of methods and incredible survival power.

If it were not for his relationship with Ann, Garen would have been in danger of losing his position as Deputy Commander a long time ago.

He exchanged communication methods with the people from the Proof of Deception.

Only then did Garen leave the Deception Hall, bringing the two guards who knew nothing and were only in charge of his safety back to the fortress.

The Blood Wars were going to start very soon. This also happened to prove an opportunity…

Garen’s Wizard Tower was still missing the last Tower Soul, but this problem was easy to solve. He would not trust any other creature’s soul to become his Tower Soul, so Garen simply decided that he would not have one. Instead, he would connect the Wizard Tower to his Willpower Neuroprocessor, using his own Energy Machinist computing core to control the Wizard Tower directly.

After all, the computing power of a Willpower Neuroprocessor was immensely terrifying, and controlling a mere Wizard Tower was nothing to it.

Finally, now that the matter of the Tower Soul had been settled, the construction of the Wizard Tower was finally approaching completion.

*****************

The tall, white and slender Wizard Tower began to spin slowly.

Several floating construction platforms circled around it, carrying the many Wizards and Demons in charge of inspection.

The team of Wizards in charge of construction was also there, carefully overseeing all the data and changes.

A giant crystal displaying complicated colorful lines was floating beside the Wizard Tower, constantly displaying the balance and changes of the many elements within it.

Several hundred Wizards and familiars circled around it. Surrounded by people, Garen stood not two hundred meters away from the Wizard Tower, raising his head and looking up at the tall tower that pierced through the clouds.

Most of the staff in the area around it had already been dispersed temporarily, to prevent any accidents and subsequent casualties.

But even so, there were still many onlookers here for a piece of the action. Some of them were Demons, others were travelers from other planes, and there were even Void Creatures, all watching the happenings over there from a great distance away.

The whole Wizard Tower was situated in the lower left corner of the Fortress, close to where the city wall used to be. However, Garen had expanded the area of the Fortress, turning this place into a large oval. As a result, the Wizard Tower was now the center of this oval.”

“The last Divinity Barrier Enchantment.” The Advanced Wizard in charge of construction clapped his hands.

An old and frail Level Nine Peak Wizard walked up to the tower slowly and began to levitate.

The Divinity Barrier was just a classic spell that had been standardized as a formality. It was a Level Nine spell, so any Level Nine Wizard could do it. The only problem was that to enchant something with this spell required the caster to pay a heavy cost.

Usually, to enchant something with a spell of the same level, the spellcaster’s spellcasting level would immediately drop from the peak to the same level as the spell. That was an entire level’s worth of cost. And since it was a Level Nine spell, the enchantment of such a high-level spell would also take up some of the enchanter’s lifespan.

The old Wizard was using this enchantment as a cost in exchange for Garen’s protection over his son, a Level Five Wizard.

And for such a giant Wizard Tower, the lifespan and Spirit Power required would also be astonishing indeed.

After this enchantment, the dozen or so years left in his lifespan would also be completely exhausted, and he would die for real. Although there were a great many powerhouses in the Abyss, there were still many things a Level Nine Wizard could do. They were still considered above average in power.

To have one die for merely an Enchantment would be a huge loss to any faction.

Looking at the old Wizard’s back as he walked up to the Tower, Garen lowered his head slightly in a show of respect.

When he lowered his head, all the other powerhouses also lowered their heads respectfully.

The old Wizard’s robes were slightly worn. Reaching out his thin and scraggly arm, he slowly pointed at the giant Wizard Tower.

A pure white ring of light blossomed from his arm.

The rings came one after the other, growing in number, gathering densely and forming a pure white board around the old man’s arm.

There were countless circular marks all over the board, almost material in their essence.

The old man looked at the round board in his hand attentively, and his face was rapidly deteriorating away. His already thin muscles also shriveled up rapidly, what little blood that was left in his face gradually turning pale. It was as though all the life in his body had gathered into white board of light around his hand.

He began to recite a chant in a soft voice, and many tiny tadpole-like runes also began to appear on the board of light.

As the runes he sang increased in speed and number, the runes on the board increased as well.

All of a sudden, he swung his arm.

The board of light shot out explosively, crashing straight toward the Wizard Tower ahead.

Vroom!!!

Like a stone crashing into the water, countless transparent space ripples appeared on the surface of the Wizard Tower.

The sky instantly turned dark, and a pillar of pure white light descended from the sky, landing over the Wizard Tower. Even the blood-red sun of the Abyss could not hide it.

This was an instant of brilliance, obtained in exchange for ten years of life and all of his life force.

The old Wizard’s body slowly transformed into specks of light, fading away.

Garen could vaguely hear the sobs of a young man, and he sighed slightly.

“As of today, the Cold Winter Tower is officially completed!”

His voice was magically magnified, trembling and spreading into the ears of all the creatures around him.

Far away, the two Ancient Dragons from the White Dragon Mountain also heard his voice, turning their gaze toward his direction in the distance.

Chapter 1341: Deception Demon Master 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The construction of the Cold Winter Tower also signified that Garen could now officially increase his own Arcane Art abilities. It took him quite some time to reach that stage.

It did not matter how many other eyes he had caught with this move.

A Level Twelve being building a Wizard Tower was not really that big a deal, but the only thing that caught their attention was the scale of this Wizard Tower. It was just slightly too big.

But considering Garen’s position, all the observers decided to put it aside.

Upon completion, the Wizard Tower was surrounded by a circle of white electricity, and the white sphere of ice floating above the tower slowly shone with a colorful light. That was the aurora-like effect of the Elemental Ponds absorbing a great amount of elemental power from the Void dimension.

Garen asked the Wizard in charge of the design to step up and burn all the design blueprints for the entire Wizard Tower in front of the crowd, while also transferring the key and password that allowed entry.

Only then Garen did walk up to the entrance of the tower alone, slowly.

As everyone watched attentively, he spoke the password.

“True knowing is everything.”

Whoosh.

The door to the Wizard Tower opened slowly.

Garen walked inside, and the door closed again behind him.

Everything went back to the same calm silence it started with, all of the onlookers and builders carefully watching every movement within the Wizard Tower as they held their breaths.

About half an hour later.

Vroom!!

The entire Tower instantly lit up, and a silver veil of flowing light slowly began to envelop the statues of Garen’s dragon body, placed around the tower.

“We did it!” The Advanced Wizard in charge heaved a vicious sigh of relief.

All the Wizards and Demons who had participated in the construction process also heaved a sigh of relief. This proved that Garen had taken complete control of the tower, and it also showed that there was nothing unusual at all with the operations of the tower.

The Cold Winter Tower officially marked its presence in the Fortress, on the ground of the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains.

Although it was still a very small tower right now and could not be compared to those peak-level Wizard Tower that had stood for several thousand, or even ten thousand years, Garen still believed that one day it would truly grow into a symbol of incomparably immense power.

**********************

The formation of the Cold Winter Tower meant that Garen’s Arcane Art Level could finally have a chance of breaking through.

He dived head-first into the Wizard Tower’s Elemental Pond and simply decided not to come out. The six Main Elements — earth, water, wind, fire, light, and dark — would naturally form a force field that was elementally-balanced in the middle of the Elemental Pond, so Garen stayed right here, sensing the different flows and principles of the different, almost material elements.

His Wizard Level instantly increased.

In a few short days, he had broken through his initial Level Five and reached Level Six.

After he successfully entered Level Six, Garen began to simultaneously construct the Biochemical Pool and experimental platform, while also performing his research experiments in order to escape the Weave spell. The Willpower Neuroprocessor’s computing power was extremely immense, and while he controlled the operation of the Wizard Tower, he could also simultaneously perform two other high-difficulty missions. And because he had the energy provided by the Elemental Pond, these analysis quests of that level only required several months now, as opposed to the several years at least that Garen would have needed to take initially.

This level of efficiency was not something that could have been emulated normally.

As for regular Wizards, they would need at least several dozen years if they wanted to escape the Weave.

But the importance of all this would only come into play after the upcoming important event.

The Deception Demon Lord who originated from the Void, that terrifying being at the True Soul Level, was finally about to descend here.

***************

The blood-red moon shone with viscous red light, and as a result, the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains did not look that different from how they did in the daytime. Here, the only difference between night and day was the level of brightness.

Garen kept the two Ancient Dragons occupied with the best food, drink, and activities until they were so engrossed in the enjoyment that they had nearly forgotten their initial motives. Over the past few days, their space equipment had been stuffed to the brim with all sorts of resources and treasures. At first, they had come here specifically to have Garen return to the Main Clan, but now they would rather Garen delay his return to the clan however long he could, so that they could play here for longer, earning more things in the process.

Garen did not know what Kratos was doing here, however, since all he did was accompany the two geezers with their feasting and festivities. Of course, he had to pay his own way through this, since Garen naturally would not foot the bill for him.

Under the glow of the moonlight, the Vengeance Fortress was colored with a faint hue of peacefulness.

The pillar of red rune smoke rising into the sky from the top of the Fortress also seemed to have dimmed somewhat. Lady Vengeance had gone to another Fortress, and aside during from the Blood Wars, she was not here most of the remaining time. Everything within the Fortress was completely managed by Garen and the other Deputy Commander.

“Something seems to be wrong with the energy forces,” said Kratos, frowning, as he hugged a beautiful lizardwoman. He was used to being cautious, and now he was in his rival, Garen’s territory. He had no choice but to be careful and cautious.

“Wrong? What could be wrong? We’re inside the Fortress now, and even if some Demons or Ghosts attack the city, can’t you see all those Demons patrolling outside? Garen’s patrol guards and checkpoint Wizards aren’t there for decoration purposes only. If anything happens, they will also raise the alarm immediately.”

One of the old Dragons was examining a treasure before him with a magical tool that resembled a magnifying glass, his face filled with intense excitement.

“To think we’d find something as good as this here as well, hahaha, we were so right to come out on this trip!”

Beside him, the other Ancient Dragon was slowly sipping away at a cup of thick, pale-green wine, his expression completely intoxicated.

At first, the two of them had been slightly wary, but by now, they were completely engrossed in enjoying the material pleasures.

A few sexily-dressed beautiful ladies from different races performed a provocative and seductive dance routine in the middle of the Hall. The music permeated through the hall, and there were even little Demons who were specifically there to unleash fantasy-like smoke and light effects for decoration purposes.

“Speaking of which, we’ve been here for so many days now, why hasn’t Garen indicated anything? He just keeps telling us that he’s busy, and refuses to follow the two of you back to the Main Clan to report. The way I see it, it’s highly likely that he has some other plans in mind,” said Kratos in a low voice.

“Other plans? Hehe, with the two of us here, what other plans would he dare have? In the Abyss, aside from the Abyssal Demon Dragons, the White Dragon Mountain is the strongest dragon clan around. As a White Dragon, no matter how you look at it, he wouldn’t possibly dare to completely offend the Main Clan,” said the Ancient Dragon with the magnifying glass nonchalantly.

“But you can’t not be wary,” advised Kratos.

“We don’t need you to remind us of that,” said the Ancient Dragon with the wine in displeasure.

“Sigh…” Kratos kept getting the feeling that something might happen.

Vroom!

A wave of imperceptible energy suddenly reached them from afar.

It was very much like the calm before an energy storm, and the three of them paid it no heed.

But what they had not noticed at all was that a faint red fog was gradually seeping in with the air from outside. It entered their nostrils, soundless and traceless, odorless and tasteless.

Slowly, several black figures gradually appeared within the shadows in the corners of the hall, walking toward the three of them. The strange thing was that the two Ancient Dragons, Kratos, and all the Demons and creatures around them were all oblivious to the approach of these shadows. They were right in front of them, but it was as though the dragons and the rest could not see them at all.

The black shadows grew closer and closer, closer and closer.

“These two are the sacrifices, Master Garen has indeed chosen us a decent gift…”

One of the black shadows spoke in a low and deep voice.

He reached out his hand and abruptly grabbed the neck of the Ancient Dragon before him.

Bam!!

There was an instant, enormous explosion between his hand and the Ancient Dragon, the surge of chill and ice bursting and splattering everywhere.

The two old dragons instantly jolted awake, countless layers of defensive spells lighting up with various colors all over their bodies, covering every inch of skin. It was the automatically-triggered defense from the many spells and items they carried and wore on their bodies.

But the defensive layers, at least a hundred in all, did nothing to make them feel safe.

The large black hand pierced through the wall of defensive spells as easily as one would poke through paper, grabbing straight for the old dragon’s neck.

“Descend, Thunder!!!” The eyes of the dragon who was caught shone with terror, but pinnacle powerhouses were naturally incomparable to regular creatures. All of his power instantly gathered at his brow, and a rune there immediately began to emit an unbelievably blinding blue light.

That was his very own unique Core Spell that he had condensed and formed ever since he entered Level Ten, an instant-activation rune that he had been working on all this time. In it, he stored the terrifying energy he had been accumulating for several hundred years.

The rune emitted a crisp ‘ka-chak’ and exploded directly, turning into a cloud of blue mist that shot toward the black shadow.

At the very instant that this tremendous explosive power was about to burst, destroying everything around it in the process, the black shadow figure actually grabbed it with one hand and condensed all of the power into becoming an even smaller blue pearl.

“Meaningless struggle,” said the black shadow calmly, reaching for the old dragon’s head with a whoosh.

But to his surprise, the old dragon’s body instantly flashed once. Somehow, it was an Instant Teleportation Spell. The teleportation power of this spell was very impressive, and it activated at lightning-speed as well. That also meant that it took a lot of time to prepare, so the old dragon had clearly used a single-use magical item to keep it on him beforehand.

The flashing returned to normal in a moment, and the old dragon returned to his original position, his expression slightly panicked.

“A Demigod!!?? Who are you… I’m the White Dragon Mountain’s…” Poof!

The large hand squeezed his head until it burst, and the impenetrable dragon scales put up no resistance whatsoever. A faint wisp of a translucent soul was pulled out by that large hand and stuffed into the black shadow’s mouth.

“If it weren’t for the Confusion Dew that Garen provided, these two guys might really have eluded us,” said the black shadow thoughtfully.

The black shadows around him exploded apart instantly, and all the remaining creatures that were still alive nearby abruptly died and melted like wax. In the large hall, the other old dragon was also finished off by two more shadows working together.

After the shadows dissipated from the three of them, they raised their hands and saw that a large portion of their palms had completely shriveled up. The initially healthy skin and flesh had instantly become as thin and dry as sticks.

“Cough cough… one Kratos got away.” One of the black shadows seemed to have taken a final blow from the Ancient Dragon before he died and was grievously injured as a result.

“He didn’t get away, that guy was just an illusion, a projection to start with. His true body was never here to start with,” said another black shadow in a deep voice.

The Demigod black shadow wiped the blood from the corners of his mouth. His forceful suppression of the Ancient Dragon’s explosion just before he died had also cost the Demigod a high price.

“It doesn’t matter, what can a Level Nine brat like that do, even if he does have a protector? Prepare to receive the Demon Master’s arrival immediately.”

Although the three of them noticed that one had escaped, they had no intention whatsoever of chasing after him, with the clear intention of causing trouble for Garen. Otherwise, there was no way a Level Nine could have escaped this easily from the clutches of two Level Fifteen Peaks and a Demigod, no matter how strong that Level Nine was.

More shadows began to slowly appear behind the three of them, and then all of the shadows began to set up a great many red candles and white human bones, while also using a black oil-like liquid to paint complicated matrices on the ground.

*******************

Far away, Garen stood on the middle level of the Cold Winter Tower, looking into the distance through the crystal glass.

The radiation surveillance area of the Cold Winter Tower spanned half the Fortress, so he knew every detail about everything within this half of the Fortress. Naturally, he was also very clear about the assassination over there. The powerhouses from Proof of Deception’s attack on the White Dragon Mountain emissaries took place directly under his watch.

He could even clearly see that Kratos was escaping from the Fortress desperately under the protection of a mysterious person.

“A Level Fourteen guardian…” Through the senses enhanced by the Wizard Tower, Garen could easily tell just how strong the powerhouse protecting Kratos was. “Too bad, if they were surrounded by many matrices, we should be able to keep them from leaving. Looks like those people from Proof of Deception sincerely intend to cause me some trouble… They want me to take a share of the burden.”

Naturally, Garen understood their intention. But that was fine, he was already a member of the Dragons of Disaster, after all, and he was also a Void Demon Lord to boot. It was not quite possible for him to mix with the White Dragon Mountain. Might as well make his stand clear as soon as possible.

He raised his head and looked at the sky, where the blood-colored moon was growing an even more vicious shade of red.

Chapter 1342: Deception Demon Master 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In terms of the dream power that only Void Creatures could sense, there was an incomparably immense storm of dream power gathering slowly at the place where the attack just happened.

Garen had long since sent away any related personnel in that area. That was why he was not worried about any accidental casualties.

“Commander, a strange assault took place just now…” Andrew’s hurried projection appeared behind Garen, kneeling on one knee as he spoke hastily. “The two Master Ancient Dragons were attacked by unknown powerhouses, and are currently…”

“Don’t mind that too much,” Garen interrupted him. “I’ve already arranged for this matter properly, just go around that area and settle everything else.”

Andrew fell silent immediately. Looking at Garen’s expression, it was obvious that this was all within his plan. Andrew’s heart gave a jolt, and he did not say any more.

“Yes. Allow me to take my leave.”

After his projection vanished, soon enough Irene’s projection also appeared behind Garen. Garen had given all four Generals a projection communication device that they could use for emergency communications.

“Milord, how should we handle the assault incident? The commotion this time was too obvious, the other lords are already hurrying on their way here,” said Irene with a serious expression.

By the other lords, she meant the higher-ups within the Fortress, such as the other Deputy Commander and the Demonic Behemoth leader.

The White Dragon Mountain was attacked by Level Fifteen powerhouses. It was highly likely that something like that would cause a huge riot, so it was a big deal for the entire Vengeance Fortress as well. That was why they had no choice but to be spurred into action.

“It’s fine, I’ve made the necessary arrangements for this, just tell them that they don’t have to worry.”

Garen said offhandedly.

Irene frowned, but seeing Garen’s calm demeanor, she chose not to say anything as well. With a bow, she vanished from the spot.

Garen looked at the site of the assault quietly.

Over there, a large amount of dream power was gathering into a giant funnel-shaped tornado, the energy forces so terrifying that even regular Demons could vaguely sense it.

Very soon, as time passed, several lights of different colors flew toward the center of the energy tornado. That was the other powerful presences, gone forward to see what was going on. Among them, Garen even saw the Demonic leader and the other Deputy Commander.

Meanwhile, Garen himself watched that enormous tornado quietly.

Soon, a request came from his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

“A powerful guest is requesting entry.”

“Approved.” Garen quickly allowed entry.

Immediately, he saw a wisp of black smoke fly into the Wizard Tower instantly, and in no time at all, it had darted to the eighth floor, where he was. It condensed into a humanoid figure of black smoke behind him.

The figure emitted a faint aura of divinity. It was the Demigod from Proof of Deception who had assaulted and killed the Ancient Dragon earlier.

In his arms, he carried a white and flawless baby girl. The baby girl was wrapped in only a ring of white cloth, and she did not cry. Instead, she looked at Garen with deep and ancient eyes.

“I’ll be relying on you for a period of time, Master Garen,” said the baby girl in a deep voice, speaking in the most standard form of the Void Language.

“It is my honor to be of service to the Deception Demon Master.” Garen smiled slightly, turning around and bowing at her.

As soon as the baby girl was born, her aura had already reached Level Six, as expected of a terrifying being at True Soul Level, who had accepted the sacrifice of two peak Level Fifteen souls.

“Don’t worry, Kunder will protect me at all times within this period of time until I regain my powers to a certain extent. Within this period, I will need you to start Blood Wars and create a large amount of slaughtering so that I may absorb many souls in order to regenerate myself,” said the Deception Demon Master calmly.

“But Lady Vengeance’s side… and the White Dragon Mountain won’t take this lying down,” said Garen, somewhat troubled. “I would suggest that we lay low for now.”

“It’s fine.” The baby girl waved her hand. “The White Dragon Mountain have their own things to worry about, I opened up two Void Crevices there, that’ll keep them busy for a while. Considering your relationship with Lady Vengeance, you should be able to deal with that, right? As long as you don’t fail, so what if you overstep your authority and start some Blood Wars?”

“Since Your Excellency, Lady Deception has considered everything so carefully, I’ve no choice but to agree.” Garen put away his troubled expression. Of course, he knew that she would have everything arranged properly, after all, a Demon Master was not invincible as soon as they descended here either. She needed time to grow, and this growth period would be the time when she was at her weakest. It was only right that she would make all the necessary arrangements.

“As a reward for your help this time, I can help you solve the bottleneck you’ve found yourself at regarding the condensation of your True Soul,” said the Deception Demon Master calmly.

Garen was stunned for a moment and then overjoyed. His Void Original Opus had been stuck at 70% for a long time now, and even potential points could not increase it. If he had the guidance of a true Demon Master at True Soul Level, he would naturally be able to progress much more efficiently.

At first, he was not too pleased about a Demon Master Level descending near him, but right now, he felt as though it was more than worth it.

Over the past period of time, he had been using the Willpower Neuroprocessor to analyze it for quite a while, but he still had no clue, and leveling up felt like it was a long way away. Now, he could finally see some hope.

“In truth, the problem is very simple.” The Deception Demon Master gave a cunning smile. “Your Soul Rings are too weak… In other words, you need a great deal of soul inspiration to condense into Soul Seeds and Soul Rings. It just so happens that I have a method here that can collect the essence of soul inspirations, thereby speeding up your condensation of the Soul Seeds and Soul Rings.”

“Oh? Please enlighten me, Demon Master,” Garen hurriedly asked respectfully.

“Actually, in every soul, there will be some degree of inspiration according to the contract rules, it’s just that some have more than others. Usually, if this inspiration is not accumulated to a certain extent until it undergoes a fundamental change, it won’t be successfully activated, so no one will pay any more attention to it. The ones that people notice are the inspirations of the successful, no one really pays any heed to the failures or those who don’t have the halo of success. But this is an error… My method is able to gather up the countless inspirations and form a complete Soul Seed or Soul Ring, speeding up your level increase progress,” said the Deception Demon Master with a smile.

“A method like this surely comes with a heavy price, right?” asked Garen carefully.

The Demon Master nodded.

“You guessed right, this method needs you to condense soul divinity until your soul reaches the Demigod level at the very least, only then would you be able to prevent the amalgam of soul inspirations from mixing up your own purity level. If you don’t have soul divinity, it would be very easy for the large amounts of impurities to pollute your own Soul Ring, and your gains would be outweighed by your losses. You might even cause your own level to drop.”

“So it still comes back to divinity in the end?” Garen was thoughtful.

“divinity is a very mysterious thing that exists in this world, it is an evolution and fundamental change of the soul, but it’s high and almighty. It has the ability to command all the souls, just like a king, and can even activate the power of a world’s most fundamental laws.” The Deception Demon Master’s words were clearly meant to goad Garen into creating slaughters of his own accord. He needed to condense more Soul Rings, after all, and that would require him to instigate more slaughters. It just happened to coincide with her needs, resulting in a straightforward and honest ploy that Garen had no choice but to follow.

“I understand.” Garen’s way going forward from now on gradually became clear to him.

If he wanted to achieve the True Soul, perhaps it was truly as the Deception Demon Master said.

He needed to first achieve divinity and the Demigod level, then he had to collect a large amount of soul inspiration essence to form even more Soul Seeds and Soul Rings. Only then would he be able to achieve a breakthrough in the Void Original Opus, and eventually reach the True Soul.

“In the very beginning, since the inspiration won’t repeat, it’ll be very easy to condense the Soul Seed. But as it goes on, there will be more repeated inspiration, until finally you reach a day when most of the inspirations you get are only reruns. It will become harder and harder to condense new Soul Seeds and Soul Rings, and that’s when the Demon Lords have to continuously explore new frontiers, accumulating lots of different inspirations, regardless of how long it will take,” the Deception Demon Master continued.

“And right now, you guys have an unprecedented opportunity. This world has many different inspirations from our world, and barely any repetition at all. divinity is also a shortcut to condensing Soul Seeds and Soul Rings. divinity, plus a large amount of soul energy, is actually already equivalent to a high-level Soul Ring. That’s why the more divinity you obtain, if you can complete them, you’d actually also be able to turn them into Soul Rings and Soul Seeds.”

“In other words, I can use divinity to condense Soul Rings, and I can also find soul divinity. Once I’ve reached soul Demigod level, I can slaughter souls at a large-scale and may be able to gain inspiration from it,” Garen concluded.

“That’s right, the former is stealing divinity, it’s a lot more dangerous than you’d think. There are already a lot of powerhouses fighting for divinity, and even some Gods. The latter is much safer, you just have to steal one type of soul divinity. As for the remaining slaughter, perhaps even normal people would be able to provide you with enough inspiration to condense your Soul Seed.” The Deception Demon Master gave him two options, but both also required slaughtering and stealing.

Still, Garen had no other choice right now.

******************

In the blink of an eye, more than two months have passed.

The Deception Demon Master simply took up residence in the Cold Winter Tower, absorbing many souls and soul cocoons every day. Sometimes, she would even go to the area around the Underworld River, killing and plundering indiscriminately. Thankfully, she did not attract the attention of any powerful beings. After all, she only slaughtered relatively weaker creatures.

Under her constant ushering, Garen also started some small-scale attacks against the Demon Fortress opposite them.

He had five hundred thousand soldiers in his reserve army, and their average was level was above Level Two. There was also the elite team of Wizards, the White Feather. That was enough for him to start a small-scale Blood War in his own.

And within the Wizard Tower, because Garen had his Divine Power Barrier, he officially began analyzing the divinity ahead of schedule.

Firstly, he gathered all the divinity together and merged them into the Pearl of the Temple. Then he isolated the true divinity that he had obtained, researching it with his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

The largest benefit of the Willpower Neuroprocessor was that it could automatically utilize the large amount of information and inspiration from the storage of Garen’s memories, computing and analyzing them.

Garen just needed to input the command and could leave the rest to it. It would automatically carry out the command and analysis.

The divinity he got from Gerdmos was a wisp of divinity regarding decay. It was full of all sorts of inspirations and understanding regarding decay. Even though it was only as large as a strand of hair, it actually managed to contain several tens of thousands of pb worth of information. Even the Willpower Neuroprocessor could not completely finish analyzing the information in it within a short period of time. After all, it was not a mess of nonsense inside, it was all advanced inspirations, such as words and diagrams regarding decay, and even things like personal first-hand experiences.

Since there was so much information there, it was no wonder that becoming a Demigod required centuries at the very least. Some even took up to a thousand years.

Garen put it on his quest list in his mind and glanced at the estimated completion time.

‘Fifty-eight years – sixty years.’

Such a period of time was already god-like to most advanced existences, but Garen was still unsatisfied with it.

And after he added the divinity analysis mission, the energy consumption of his Elemental Pond instantly reached a new level. And this was the true divinity that Gerdmos had analyzed before. If it was a completely disorganized divinity, it would probably take even longer.

Thankfully, the computing speed of the Willpower Neuroprocessor was actually based on the strength of one’s Willpower, and the strength of one’s Willpower had its fundamental roots in the strength of one’s soul.

Since he had no other way, Garen had to choose this method, the slowest way to strengthen his Soul Seed.

That was to hunt for high-energy crystals, such as Soul Cores…

He had also tried ready-made Soul Cores, but they had barely any effect on him anymore. A Level Nine Soul Core could only give Garen one-third of a Soul Seed. Clearly, this was just as the Deception Demon Master said, most of the inspiration inside had repeated and was gradually becoming unable to condense into more Soul Seeds.

But he had obtained a large Soul Seed upgrade from the Suffering Knight back then, so he might still be able to do that now. Maybe if the quantity increased, there might be a slight change in quality.

Besides, those that could condense Soul Cores all tended to be Necromancy creatures. As a result, Garen soon began to make his plans around an Undead settlement nearby.

Chapter 1343: Trade 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The area nearby Vengeance Fortress was a mysterious place flagged with white mist. Almost all creatures that enter would be lost and returned to their starting points. Apart from higher level existences that could enter and leave at ease, the rest could not.

This land was a white zone wrapped around by the lingering clouds.

There were white towering trees and bushes everywhere. The plants here were all in withering states. There were no leaves, only dry branches. Even the bushes were mostly shrubbery without sheds of leaves, only thorny vines winding in threatening gestures.

A group of living beings in black were slowly heading for this mist.

This group of creatures was led by a tall tough man followed by a mix match of demons, humans and elves. There were even a few Air Elemental Beings.

The lead was a man with cold features. The shape of his muscles was obvious from his clothes.

“It’s here.

“All the soul crystals that the lord needs are here.

“Pay attention and don’t wreak too much havoc.”

“And we, White Feathers, need your advice?” An Air Elemental Being with white fabric shrouded around him coldly smiled.

“My only wish is that you don’t ruin the matter,” The leading man coldly blurted.

And it was at this moment.

Wham!!

With the dull crash, a puff of white air current exploded within the white forest. These air currents whooshed open like broken strings, spreading out to all direction, howling an ear-piercing screech.

“Quick! They’re getting away!”

An Air Elemental Being shouted out.

Those on the team immediately took action. The casters put out a large electrical web and rays of positive energy.

There was also a huge explosion that scattered the white air currents apart, creating a powerful murderous soundwave.

“Disastrous Rain of Fury!”

A demon in black robes wedged open his cape and tore apart a scroll.

Rip!

Bright yellow flames gushed out of his eyes as a large fiery three-dimensional sorcery formation appeared on the air.

“Boundless Electrical Web!”

An eye-catching electrical current rune beamed up in the palms of another Air Elemental Being.

Two large level eleven ripples spread out from the two an overlapped between one another.

“Uniquely level eleven spellcraft!!”A terrified voice was heard from the woods.

“Compound spell, go!!”

Bounteous air currents surged to one direction, toward the team in a distance.

But it was all too late.

An enormous red light beamed from the sky and over a hundred fireballs the size of a knuckle dropped down like raindrops.

Each fireball exploded before it touched the ground like a red firework on a slow release.

The forest was ignited and crackled in flames. The sound of collapsing and crackling kept buzzing on.

The great fire distributed quickly.

With the descent of the rain of fury, the entire vicinity within several kilometers was engaged in this massive level eleven spellcraft.

Apart from this rain of fury, a few of the cracks and nooks of the space was stretching out in shapeless transparent and invisible electrical web.

These electric current unseen by the naked eye were as thick as a baby’s limb. Countless streaks of electric web conjoined together to form an even large electrical current web, locking the surface tightly that no living being could escape from such fate.

The demons and Air Elemental Beings were masters of the same White Feather team were well coordinated to the point of flawlessness.

“The combination of two level eleven spells is basically the same effect of a level thirteen spell… How powerful!” The lead gasped lowly in admiration.

Everywhere in sigh was burning in red flames. The glaring light scorched and scattered the entire white mist. Screams and wails could be indistinctly heard.

“These Souls of Mist race aren’t strong in combat but they have a way with soul powers.

“Perhaps we could collect some valuable data for commander,” The man in the lead said in a low voice.

“We will pay attention,” The casting demon of the White Feather demon lightly nodded. “The lead force is about to come out, everyone be on alert.

“Do not let even one escape.”

“Understood,” The White Feather comrades answered.

Swish!!

A white vapor soared for the sky and flew to a distance.

“I’ll go!” An Air Elemental Being shot like a sprung arrow, chasing after the white vapor.

The two parties could be seen intertwining from afar, with an occasional blast of energy source rippling.

Nearby, steams of white vapor gathered to be a large white cloud, plunging towards everyone.

A female elf of White Feather calmly raised her arm, an emerald ring in her hand lit up in green.

“Divine weapon!!?? No!!!” The white bat whimpered in pain. Green vines and branches grew out of his insides and almost in an instant, the large white bat was completely covered by these green vines.

The female elf smiled and took a step back.

“Helena, you have already broke through level twelve yet you use a divine weapon on a level ten undead, that’s too much, isn’t it…?” Someone from the team laughed.

White Feather was masters of various paths paid handsomely by Garen. Most of them has a mysterious past but he wasn’t bothered by their history. As long as they had the ability, he couldn’t care less about anything else.

The majority of these fellas came from mysterious and powerful backgrounds as a handful of them possessed semi-divine and divine weapons. Garen himself only possessed a semi-divine weapon that was gifted by Soaring Wong King.

Divine weapons were hard to come by as it couldn’t be purchased in the market. Only those family and forces that cultivated deeply would have access to them.

This elf was only level twelve yet she dared show her divine weapon off. It could be due to either overconfidence and arrogance or not fearing of any accidents that may occur.

Those who entered White Feather would naturally would not be the latter.

“As it is a request from lord commander, how could I let him down,” The female elf smiled in response.

“The earlier leader here is only a clone.

“Be careful everyone.

“Although only a Level Ten Non-Failing, we still must be wary,” The leading man warned in a loud voice.

“Everyone here is an important edit of our Vengeance Fortress so it’s best not to have any fatality from a tiny mishap.”

“You really are as naggy as grandma!” A Dirt Elemental Rock Monster impatiently commented.

The man smiled awkwardly. He was one of the generals under Andrew. He was in charge of the team here because Master Andrew himself couldn’t stand the arrogance of these people.

But up until now, everything has been going on smoothly.

Seeing the earlier killed white bat dispersed, a white sharp rock fall from within. The man sighed within. He recognized it. This was the soul core which was the target of the task. Although a part of this clan leader’s soul core, but at least it was a start.

There were flames and electrical current everywhere and only the area where everyone stood and moved about at, the flames and current would spontaneously avoid.

A level ten clan, was swept away in one go by the elites of White Feather.

******

Peak of Cold Winter Tower.

Six oval-shaped swirls of various color floated in the air, forming a large circle. It consisted of yellow direct elemental look, blue water elemental pool. Green wind elemental pool, red fire elemental pool as well as black and white negative and positive energy pool.

Within the six main elemental pools was a silver elevator in the tower. It was solidified with a layer of semi-transparent hazy film.

Whirl…

A soft whizzing of elevator sound was heard.

Garen was slowly raised from the center. He was wearing a black armor with high defense.

This was full body armor specifically for a deputy commander of the fortress.

It was heavy and large, weighing more than a ton in weight. A regular living being wouldn’t be able to wear it, much less hold it up.

But to Garen, he could shrink his dragon body to fit into it yet still maneuver with ease and as carefree as could be.

Behind the armor were decades of pitch black whips braided with metal silks. It could also said to be tentacles that could be controlled by spirit power. Garen used them as extra hands.

This set of armor was built with a special bone attribute. It could not be influenced by arcane energy flow or transmission. It could also prevent any injury that results from possible explosion towards the body due to experimental spellcraft so Garen put it on.

His motive this time was to adequately mobilize the elemental pools.

The six main elemental pools were respectively connected to six elemental plane rich with various elements which in turn, connected to the violent energy windstorm plane. They used an enormous force field to cluster the violent energy elements so that they were tamed and gentrified into complete energy source for the system.

Garen’s mission up here to was to use the torrenting energy current to execute an Energy Machinery creation familiar to an Energy Machinist.

He walked out of the elevator platform and first went to the most gentle blue water elemental pool to look at the whirling blue swirl. He slowly extended his claw to dab lightly of the blue elemental fluid.

The highly concentrated elemental fluid was gasifying on his claw.

Garen brought it to his mouth for a taste.

“Not bad, concentrated enough,” He nodded, satisfied.

He swept a glance over to the screen in the mind of his willpower. The remaining quota on the usage of the water elemental pool appeared there.

“Idle energy source – 32%”

Garen left the elemental pool and found two empty nests specially vacated in a corner of the tower. He left them out as space for biochemical pool and experiments.

He gently sprinkled out a bronze metal ball.

This was a biochemical pool seed that Garen created. He was, after all a top Energy Machinist in the Mech world and had collected various research information. He created a biochemical pool seed easily, utilizing the abundant materials from the abyss.

Of course, this would only work if it were him as he stood above the civilization of the Mech World, having countless amassed formulas and theorem at his disposal. After an execution of a complicated calculation, a biochemical pool seed that was most up to standard and pure came to light.

The establishment of a biochemical pool signified that an Energy Machinist could officially nurture his own Energy Machinery and bio-soldiers.

Garen quietly watched as the biochemical pool seed dropped to the bottom of the empty hole. It rumbled and tumbled a bit before ripping out a black fluid.

The fluid was thickening and amassing and quickly occupied the entire space in the hole.

It hasn’t been ten minutes when the biochemical pool was completed.

This was a large pool that was oval in shape and filled with green glowing liquid. The condensed liquid was bubbling like the wriggling of creepy crawlies. It emitted a dull green glow.

Around its edges was a startling black protection ring that formed a layer of isolation that separated the air within the space of the biochemical pool and the outside world.

“Biochemical pool established… Connecting command control…”

An instruction order was heard from his willpower mind in Garen’s brain.

“Connection succeeded.

“Name defaulted to Pool No. 1.

“Testing Nutrition composition… Test succeeded, composition complete.

“Please insert cultivating Energy Machinery seed.”

Garen was not in a rush to carry out. For starters, an Energy Machinery template was not easy to come by and another thing was that an Energy Machinery required a smart chip to be controlled with. He was lacking in the methods of controlling. It would be fine in a technology world to use a simple method of electrical energy source as the driving force of the smart chip but it was easy for elemental wizards to cause interference here. So although he could easily create a smart chip, preventing interference was the main difficulty.

Moreover, once his biochemical pool was built, it has another function.

Chapter 1344: Trade 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen flashed a faint smile.

Clap clap clap.

He gently clapped.

With a rip, a boundless distorted black hole appeared before him. A string of bloody rune characters and symbols flashed in the black hole. A female snake face appeared in the middle.

“Snake Princess, have you found the person I want?” Garen said to the woman in the black hole. He was conversing in the standard void language.”

Snake Princess was one of the few Demon Lords in the main plane who contacted Garen. Her powers were astonishing. She was the level thirteen Great Druid and a merchant of treasures and materials in Green Oak Forest.

“I’ve only found one of what you want. After explaining the situation, those who would willingly accept your request isn’t much unless they’re left with no other choice,” Snake Princess gently answered.

“It’s alright, as long as you can find it,” Garen was not bothered.

“This person’s descended body took a fatal blow. Apart from his soul being able to communicate, he isn’t much different from a living corpse. He has tried many ways, even consulting the Church’s pastors but to no avail. Now it’s up to you,” Snake Princess reminded. “But, I need to warn you that this person has quite the background. If you’re not certain then it’s best to reject this task. Although you’re at the abyss, the lesser the feud the better.”

Garen’s brow raised.

“How would we know if it works without trying?”

Snake Princess nodded in display that she understood.

“And the other thing that I need, have you found it?”

“Of course, I have plenty of resources. As long as it isn’t a divine weapon or top level soul, everything else is inexhaustible!” Garen opened his arm and sighed, “It’s Heaven for the powerful and hell for the weak.”

Indeed, the abyss connected to multiple planes. The Underworld River absorbed large amounts of sinners’ souls and fashioned a trade of soul for other resources.

Sometimes clones of gods would conceal their identity to seek what they wanted here.

“It looks like the abyss is a great place but I really don’t have a background like yours.” Snake Princess shook her head. “Alright, I’ll teleport the person. You place the stuff up there.”

Garen nodded and retrieved a dilapidated black helmet from his space equipment. This was a Holy Light Helmet from ancient dynasty. Although it was decrepit, the formation on it has great research value. It found favor amongst positive energy professionals. Moreover, it has quite the historical value and was priceless in the nobles’ clique from the main plane.

Behind the black helmet was a white line that released a dull white glow.

Garen swiftly placed the helmet on the right edge of the black hole and gave it a push.

With a swoosh, the helmet was swallowed into the darkness and another item came out of the left terminal of the black hole.

Garen extended his claw to press on this thing, then pull outwards.

Badum, it was a long black coffin.

Hiss…

Abyss aura from within the wizard tower quickly eroded towards within the coffin.

Any creatures that came to the abyss would naturally become a living state of the abyss template through the abyss aura. Their capabilities and vitality would rise with overall strengthening in resistance.

Of course, this was if the living being stayed in the abyss for a long term but for the earlier event where it was eroded by the abyss aura the moment of entry was a first for Garen to witness.

He cut off communications with Snake Princess and placed the coffin aside. He changed the black hole.

A large fish head appeared in the black hole. A black fish head.

“White Dragon King, this really isn’t the time.” There was flesh and blood at the edge of his mouth as if he was in the middle of a meal. He did look dissatisfied with the interruption.

“Black Fish King, I’m here on official business.” Garen smiled without being offended. “Have you found the person I want?”

“I found two, but their levels’ a little low. Do you want them?” Black Fish King asked.

“What level?”

“Level three,” Black Fish King answered.

“Only level three huh…” Garen frowned.

Level three void parasite creatures. How could such a weak void being enter this world? Struck by incomprehension, Garen gave it a thought.

“Never mind then. Don’t you need back up there? How many do you need?”

The moment he heard it was something he needed, Black Fish King immediately wiped his mouth and was in full spirit.

“I’m here at Central Empire, the strongest territory of that god. My alias as a Great Duke requires a few talents on the assassination part. I don’t need your men to come straight over but I’m thinking of sending some over to you for some secret training. How about that?”

“Condition?” Garen frowned.

“They’re void parasites. One person to participate in blood wars each month, no question on life or death. I’m giving you combat power for free and you’re asking for conditions?” Black Fish King widened his eyes.

“I don’t have that much time to teleport them back and forth for you.” Garen was impatient.

Black Fish King hesitated.

“Then how about this? Aren’t you lacking in divine weapons? I can’t do divine weapons but semi-divine weapons, I can gather a few. Do you want them?”

“You should mention that earlier! Of course I want them!” Garen immediately flashed a bright smile.

“One semi-divine weapon as compensation. Let’s set it to a year, how about it?” Black Fish King immediately bargained.

“Deal.” Garen locked in on the deal.

“One week later I will set up the teleportation formation. Confirm the coordinates and I will send people over,” Black Fish King briefed and cut off the connection.

The black hole slowly dispersed.

Garen turned his attention to the coffin that he dragged out.

Walking over to open the coffin, a beautiful female elf wearing a feathered headband lay quietly in it.

“Honorable White Dragon King, I am Lola, the main party of this trade.

“My parasitic body is damaged quite severely but I do not wish to abandon this body.

“I hope you will be able to assist in repair.”

A voice transmitted into Garen’s ear via soul power.

“I’ll try but dare not guarantee.” Garen could tell the crucial damage of this body.

The body of the elf harbored a massive amount of positive energy fluid up to level fifteen. This fluid at a certain stage replaced her blood and maintained the body’s circulation that this top class Demon Lord was trapped in this body, unable to grasp control.

This sort of trouble… No matter countless methods were deemed useless…

Garen felt the pinch. It was taking apart a ticking time bomb and he did not know which part could trigger it.

This level fifteen energy was enough to tear apart half of his newly built wizard tower.

He dragged the coffin into the biochemical pool.

Opening the isolation chamber, he carried the female elf and placed into the biochemical pool.

The clothes on the female elf was naturally disintegrated to nothingness by the high level corroding liquid, leaving her completely naked.

Hence, it was led to the abnormal scene, the female elf was covered from head to toe in white scribble lines. That was the skin’s inability to sustain the flow of positive energy within that the surface burst into thick cracks.

Through these cracks, it could be seen that white glowing position energy fluid were slowly moving.

“Sample has entered the biochemical pool.”

“Warning, warning!”

“Energy of sample is overly concentrated, immediate neutralization required!!”

His willpower mind immediate issued an alert.

It was fortunate that the biochemical pool has the function to secrete so as long as there was sufficient energy, it would secrete corroding biochemical limitlessly.

Garen wielded his claw and a streak of blue line flew out of the water elemental pool not far away, pouring into the edge of the biochemical pool.

Large amount of biochemical liquid was swiftly poured into the pool. The corroding nature of the biochemical liquid and the positive energy within the elf counteracted, causing a hissing sound.

It could be seen that there were still other large few major energy source in the elf and they began to circulate.

Garen watched as his heart skipped a beat. If these energies were to explode, the entire Cold Winter Tower could be completely destroyed! The level of the energy was close to a Demigod level. No wonder Snake Princess gave a word of advice to refrain him from taking the job.

He paid his full attention, devotion and spirit onto this female elf.

All the calculation ability in his willpower mind was left to keep the energy balanced between the biochemical pool and within the elf.

But strangely, the positive energy in her body seemed to take growth itself as even though the corrosion was counteracted for a long time, there was no sign of weakening.

This gave Garen a pain in the neck.

“I have tried many methods of different civilization. Other Demon Lords have engaged technology in attempt to solve my problem, but shame…” The elf’s voice was heard with a hint of regret, “If you’re able to solve my problem, I will gift you a Soul Ring as a reward.”

Soul Ring!

Garen caught himself breathing heavily. He got to give it to this top level Demon Lord who was liberal with money. He could guarantee she was any regular top level Demon Lord or else talking about gifting a Soul Ring wouldn’t be this at easy.

Other Demon Lords did not have Garen’s kind of talent. He could gather many top science and technology. The knowledge they accumulated would be as complete as Garen’s.

Over ten strategies scanned past his mind and Garen immediately locked his focus on one.

“I may have a way that is able to solve your problem,” he said.

He suddenly thought of a great idea.

If he could heal his person and get his name out there, perhaps it would open up a big business among the void creatures.

Since he could not find command controls of a smart chip for the biochemical pool, he might as well forego it and use biochemical pool to create and nurture bodies!

He could specially provide satisfying bodies for descending void creatures! He could shorten the time for void creatures to strengthen themselves. He could guarantee their safety while they were nourishing and strengthening themselves.

He could use this method to ask for Soul Seeds in return.

Garen was hit with a revelation. The various biochemical knowledge accumulated over several worlds finally came to play.

Perhaps other Demon Lords would have his accrued knowledge but to reach the height he was at would take many, many years. Moreover, they may not have the strong calculation ability his willpower mind has. He was backed by the abyss and Ann who has his back. The environment was definitely secured and blood wards could be first as the void being’s first testing field.

He has great resources and influence combined. This secured and safe advantage wasn’t something the other Demon Lords could compare to.

Chapter 1345: Absorb 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He has such an advantage.

This way, he could completely establish the most well-equipped logistics and trial base for void creatures. It would be uniquely irreplaceable.

He was struck with a series of thoughts yet Garen’s hands did not stop.

He started to walk to the side of the biochemical pool. His claw swiftly drew up tiny tadpole-like symbol at the side of the pool.

His claws were huge but the symbols he crafted were fine and intricate, giving an illusion of delicate beauty.

“I’ll leave it to you.” The female elf may have seen too many promises so she casually answered without much expectation. She then slowly closed her eyes. This was the only body part she could be in control of.

Garen did not bother with her. He was now completely focused on the new symbols he engraved.

“Establishing structure scan on bio-sample.”

Instruction from his willpower mind echoed in his head.

A layer of dull white glow permeated over the elf.

“External cells in collection… Cultivating beginning…”

Garen watched with his eyes wide open at another elf body born of the biochemical pool through combination of cell nucleuses from the elf’s hair cells. It started from a loaf of meat into a complete body that was exactly the same as the female elf.

Both bodies were almost identical. The only difference was that the duplicated body did not have the vast positive energy and assembly of other few energy sources the original has.

The duplication process took no more than ten minutes, completed under the watchful eyes of Garen.

The duplication was actually the simplest process. The next step to come was the hardest.

The concern to solve was to have the female elf able to take control of her own body as well as take off the load of overfull positive energy in her body.

“Only precise transfer can be used…” Garen frowned. In the biochemical technique known to him, only this method could nail down this situation.

Precise transfer, was a process to transfer blood and bodily fluid, combining both in one body. He could use such foundation to balance out the strenuous burden in the body.

A duplicate could sustain half the burden. If that an additional body to balance it out, it should be able to dissolve the problem in the original body.

“But the precision requirement for the precise transfer is overly high… There may be a lot of Demon Lord class masters who are well versed in technology and civilization in this world, but they don’t have my strong willpower mind. This technique perhaps could only be done by name…” Garen guessed in his head. The Mech World that he went to was a mother stream in a faraway place.

He arrived at that place by chance, an existence without a hint of life source.

“Please be careful, I will be performing an energy transfer on you.”

“Please try your best to keep your soul ripples calm.”

“It’s best to refrain your body from any changes,”

Garen reminded.

“No problem,” answered the female elf in a low voice.

Garen nodded.

He extended his claw and aimed accurately at the female elf.

Swoosh!

Large amounts of white silk threads shot out from the edge of the biochemical pool, wrapping the two bodies nice and tight.

******

An area of void darkness, in a faraway astral space borders.

If the internal plane, primary substance plane as well as upper plane formed a top-to-bottom unified structure,

Then the astral would be the space they discharged amounts of impurities, useless garbage and corpses.

It would be at the bottom of this humongous structure. It discharged massive quantities of rubbish, floating into the astral.

Thus engulfed by the astral creatures that resided within. The astral creatures that grew stronger from the engulfment would invade other major planes and be crushed by powerful existence in them.

This formed a standard cycle of substance source.

Astral, just as its name suggested, seemed like a world of countless stars. It was multi-colored with heaps of rubbish and energy compounds. They glimmered various shades of danger as they floated around, harboring massive astral energy and air of deadness in them.

It was said the place where the gods had fallen was hidden within the astral space.

Even for gods upon their passing, would be pulled into the boundless astral space by force, becoming a part of death.

This was a place that the God of Death could not manage.

This was the borders of astral space, in endless void darkness.

An enormous space as huge as the silvery white moon was rotating, tumbling, closer and closer to the astral space.

Within the space was vast green plains, river streams, high mountains, a sun that looked real, forest, hills, flora and fauna as well as creatures of various races. Anything and everything could be found there.

It was as though a silvery white moon was a complete little plane.

“Ravenwer! You think you could escape from me by running here?”

A loud and sharp sound cut through the void. Just the tremor of the sound brought about mammoth energy and law. The surface of the silvery white moon appeared in severe billow and distortion.

“The dignity of god permits not blasphemy!!” A stern voice came from within the moon. It sounded like a man and a woman.

Swoosh!

A silvery figure appeared on the moon surface. Separated by a white protective layer as he watched the void on the outside.

The figure was glowing in silver. He wore an elaborated and grand silver armor. He was handsome. His pale blue hair was fluttered slightly to the back.

He held in his hands two shields. A tower shield and a little round shield. On them were carved a lion and a unicorn respectively.

“God of Spring Water and New Moon, this is your Divine Kingdom?” A large white eye ball stretching over thousand meters appeared in the void.

It was rotating, its blood-shot eyes reeked of greed and bloodshed.

“In my Divine Kingdom, my power will increase by a fold.

“If you have guts, then follow me in.” Ravenwer tightened his grip on the shields as he exclaimed.

He has already informed the gods that he was well acquainted with. They were in the midst of rushing over but whether or not he could hold on until their arrival would depend on now.

“Divine Kingdom? It’s just that small little plane wearing a weak armor…” The large eyeball regarded as beneath it, “Go, my children.”

The iris beamed in red.

Wham!!!

The loop of red in the center of the eyeball surged out tides of void creatures.

They were black creatures in appearance of bats but they were different from your regular bats. Their speed and strength were off the charts. Their claw and fangs glimmered in dull red. Black fogs in shape of eyes hung over the top of their backs.

These bats varied in size. The larges one were as big as football fields while the small ones were the size of face basins. When they swarmed out the eyeball, they were still in compact sizes. They quickly expanded as they flew out in a short distance. The swarm raced towards the silvery white moon.

The large eye ball swiftly rammed onto Divine Kingdom moon.

“Destroying a plane, isn’t as though I’ve never done it before! Die!!”

A screeching voice in the void made a dash to the moon and quickly faded away.

It could be indistinctly seen that creatures, souls, holy spirits were fighting at close quarters with the void bat army in the moon.

That large eyeball was in intense battle with the owner of Divine Kingdom, Ravenwer.

Numerous silver runes shackles appeared around the silvery white moon. Arcanic and divine runes were covered all over that its impact would be unimaginable.

The shackles sealed off the situation internally. No one could see clearly what was happening inside.

More than ten minutes later.

Crackle!

With a crisp noise, the entire silvery white moon cracked open a huge rift.

Wham!

The moon broke apart from the middle, scattering heaps of an awful mess, pulling over by the astral space’s gravity.

A white eyeball the volume of over ten thousand meters leaped up from within.

“You will be the first sacrificial offering of my coming to this world, hahahaha!!!!” The large eyeball laughed arrogantly in a sharp tone.

With a swipe, it disappeared out of sight.

All that was left was a two-section silvery white moon mimicking two large piece of land falling towards the astral space…

******

God of Spring Water and New Moon, Ravenwer has fallen.

The primary plane was shook. There were many water elemental clans within the elemental plane that worshiped the God of Spring Water and New Moon. A moderate Divine-Power level god has fallen?

But the truth was, the divine images that many water elemental clans worshiped lost its divine glow. Divine names and literature in the divine temple cracked open.

This meant that Ravenwer did not just abandoned his divine duties, he has completely passed.

Various Churches of North, East, South and West as well as the center of the primary plane immediately called for an emergency notice.

What they had thought was a small concern of a void rift invasion, played an important element in the oracle to the fall of Ravenwer.

This shook the churches.

The thirteen empires of the East combined their statement to clear as well as keep watch the borders of all void rifts to prevent any possible intrusion of dangerous creates into the primary substance plane.

This was a colossal project as out of the thirteen empires, each empire’s territory surpassed over a hundred million square kilometers. They could only depend on far distance wizard towers to communicate and disseminate tasks. To monitor such a huge territory would require manpower and resources far beyond anything in comparison.

The union of west ocean also halted their internal battle and small-scale divine war as in the oracle. They teamed up together to clear and administer all void creatures.

The area of the ocean was much larger than land. There was still the boundless sea waters that was equivalent to several plates of land. This project was on a larger scale.

The gods of human, elf and dragon divine system from the center and remaining two directions released an oracle all together, targeted towards any void creatures to summarily execute. Their souls would also perish.

The impact brought about by the fall of a moderate Divine-Power level god in his own Divine Kingdom to the world was unparalleled.

Before all this, even an invasion of void creatures to Meteor only caused a slight reaction. They didn’t think that there would be a strong existence amongst the void creatures. And because of this, no one thought that they would be a threat to the almighty supreme organization that was high above.

And now, this threat truly existed.

The upper plane with Fehra as the leader of many gods became wary. They move in numbers and no one dared to move individually.

******

Outer layer of black hole, void.

A huge floating black crown was slowly headed to another world in the black hole.

The crown’s diameter expanded in ten thousand light years. Its volume was beyond huge and in it were revolving planets and meteors.

Right in the middle of the crown, within a black palace that was surrounded by distortion, rock pillars of various sizes erected on the ground. Each pillars bore a bloody eye that was wide open. The eye shimmered dully of different patterns and designed. This represented different communication signals.

A total of eight rock pillars in a circle, forming a standard round formation.

Chapter 1346: Absorb 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Hahaha!!! Indeed, Banishing Eye of Massacre to that world is really a smart choice!!” A red Stone Pillar laughed proudly yet savagely.

“Eye of Massacre doesn’t have the restraint of our Mother Stream Alliance and Void Temple there.

“He can eat whatever he want and I’m afraid this may be a big problem,” Another blue Stone Pillar voiced in a female voice.

“Our Alliance now has newly additions of Lords and True Spirits.”

“Even if Eye of Massacre develops to its peak, we can still team up to suppress him.”

“There’s nothing to be afraid of,” The red Stone Pillar impatiently rebutted.

“They would definitely lay siege on Eye of Massacre there.”

“It’s a great opportunity for us to probe their ability,” said the black Stone Pillar in a low voice.

“Eye of Massacre’s ability is equivalent to our powerful True Spirit.”

“If they are of no cause of concern to us then we can just take them by force.”

“If they could easily encircle and suppress then we should head to Void Temple and there to discuss…”

“I think it’d probably be unsettled…” Another green Stone Pillar gently laughed, “Eye of Massacre’s most terrifying ability is to self clone. Just give him time and he could clone multiple young selves in a short time. These young bodies are revered for their same ability as him to limitlessly engulf as nature.”

“Let’s play by ear… We’ll just prepare everything we can…” The black Stone Pillar gently summarized.

******

Garen spent over ten days at Cold Winter Tower before his first body precision operation was completed.

He has the massive calculation ability of his willpower mind to thank for, he successfully had the duplicated body sustain half the original body’s energy.

This greatly eased the pressure of the positive energy in the elf’s body onto the soul.

After reducing the pressure by half, the female elf’s own strong top level Demon Lord’s soul was enough to regain control over the body.

In order to thank Garen, she immediately left a dull red Soul Ring as compensation for this treatment.

And through this female elf with a mysterious background, Garen’s reputation took off. Many Demon Lord therapists that couldn’t treat elves before made way to the abyss in attempt to learn from his experience and techniques but could only retreat once they realized that it was from Garen’s own willpower mind that this method worked.

The practice of willpower was development crystallization of another civilization system. If it was without Garen’s teachings, it would be impossible to master. Moreover, even if the way of cultivation was obtained, it required at least many many years of fumbling about before it took shape. In such a rushed environment, there weren’t any time for them to take their time in learning.

Hence the reputation that a White Dragon commander of Vengeance Fortress was a powerful therapist swiftly spread out within Void Creatures.

Many of the severely wounded Void Creatures taken in by over hundred fortress of the abyss came to look for Garen for treatment.

But soon when his rates were published out, even more Void Creatures became intimidated.

This was because Garen’s rate started from one Soul Seed and went up to a Soul Ring.

Such an expensive price to pay was not something a regular Demon Lord could afford.

But Garen wasn’t bothered by this. If they came to him for every little sickness or wound, then he would be taking business away from a lot of therapists and offending those from the same trade. It would also take up a lot of his time. The loss outweighed the gain.

He wasn’t lacking in materials neither in manpower.

Every small-scale blood wars every few days, Garen would gain substantial spoils, not just souls but riches in space equipment of dead fighters that would go into his and a few other coordinators’ pockets.

Furthermore, he received taxes from endless stream of trades by Void Creatures that made him well-heeled in no time.

But after obtaining the Soul Ring, and dull red Soul Ring at it, Garen went into seclusion. He needed to digest this prize given by that top level Demon Lord.

******

The Soul Ring was determined by color, with the lowest being colorless, then red, orange, yellow, green, blue and purple color stages. This meant the increase in terms of density.

The dull red Soul Ring was the second stage, red. Its concentration was more powerful that of a colorless Soul Ring. The higher he went, the concentration required and difficulty of density would increase.

The Demon Lord elf was generous. It would be easy to imagine what kind of stage Soul Rings she herself possessed.

So compared to Deception Demon Master’s massacre suggestion, Garen felt that this way was safer and much more secure.

He has reached the point of his sixth Soul Ring. The first five Soul Rings were the lowest, most basic colorless Soul Rings.

And the highest he has was a dull red Soul Ring. This was his wealth accrued for a period of time arriving in this world.

There was also the Pearl of the Temple. If he was greedy at that time and absorbed it to be used as Potential Points, then he would be able to advance further anymore.

After Garen has deciphered a decadent divinity, he realized that he didn’t have the ability to continue analyzing the divinity of the Pearl of the Temple. Just that streak of decadent divinity require decades to completely analyse. So he extracted the divinity and poured it into the Pearl of the Temple that he could use it like a Soul Ring to absorb.

If the Pearl of the Temple was used as a Soul Ring to absorb, it could provide him great Soul Power of one complete Soul Ring.

Upon learning that the stage of his Soul Rings was lacking, Garen prepared to focus on increasing the level of his Soul Rings.

******

Clang… Clang… Clang…

A lingering bell and heinous laughter rung above Vengeance Fortress.

The small-scale blood wars has begun.

There were tight shouts, screams and howls heard indistinctly outside. Abyssal Demons from every layer started to gather.

The blood wars was not fought solely on military force of the fortress itself. The leading players were the abundant demons from many layers of the abyss. They were set by various layers of Thanes of Abyss to join the killings in order to delight the will of the abyss while chipping away the quick-growing population.

Garen entrenched himself in his wizard tower. Large crystal screens in ocular form were erected around him, displaying a bird’s eye view of the entire scene on Vengeance Fortress.

Staring from above, extensive amount of Abyssal Demons and mercenary groups from different worlds surged out endlessly from within the fortress. Amongst them were small demons, large demons, Sawtooth Tail Demons, Chained Hammer Demons and Elephant Demons as the main force.

There were some never-before-seen Corpse Cannibal Monster, Corpse Ghoul, Decayed Zombie, Zombie, and so on and so forth. A few rare Chaotic Abominable Snowmen appeared in the army. They were all silver and white, lugging a huge rock and ring and rings of drifting ice hung beside them. Their bodies were even taller than the tallest demon.

Bartoyen Demons teleported by a few fortresses locked in confrontation with them afar. These were two monsters of completely different nature. Each of them having level ten and above abilities.

There were large amount of troops amassing over from the outer world as well as Aboleths ^1 . These smiling fish persons were covered with dull blue poisonous thorns. They wielded extended limbs that was tied to their limbs. Each of their attacks brought about frozen effects. Their body’s defense was as tough as steel. They were at least at level three in combat power.

“Even Aboleths are here… Could it be that Salt Water Marsh noticed the development at my side?” A sense of alert struck Garen.

Salt Water Marsh was one of the strongest demon prince of the bottomless abyss, residence of Demogorgon ^2 but this strong Demon Thane rarely participated in Blood Wars. It should not be much of a problem…

“It could be the intention of a few clan commanders.” Garen was too lazy to think further. He has Ann to back him. Ann was one of the three Dragons of Disaster and was at moderate Divine Power level. She was also the fiercest Dragon of Time and Shadow. Her fierceness was far from being compared to gods or Demon Thanes. He believed Demogorgon would not be willing to be sucked into this…

“Upgrading my ability is main priority.” He closed his dragon eyes and scanned through his stats.

“Garen — Strength 180(140), Agility 180(140), Vitality 180(140), Intelligence 172 with potential 1123%. Soul limit 180.

Six Soul Rings – Five colorless, one red.

Level 8 Draconic Aura. Level 6 Arcanic Art.

Void Original Opus — 70%. Back Limbs — Evil Soldier. Wings — Seven Lives. Tail — Demonic Book.

State —All Attribute Points decreased, Light suppressing curse… (All elemental resistance dropped by a third and easily spotted by Light attribute creatures. Inability to cover tracks)

Overall evaluation — Level twelve. Title — Winter Sigh.”

“The attribute has recovered a lot.”

“The recent Potential Points will all be spent on Intelligence with one more point before it’s full.”

“Now the priority is levelling the Soul Rings.”

Garen reined in his focus and took out the little white bud that the female elf gave him.

Gentling dabbing on it, the bud slowly bloomed.

A slight sound of music lingered from the core, together with a faint floral scent.

Swoosh!

A bleak of white light shot out and hit Garen between the brows.

A heavy clash rammed his head forcefully back.

A dull red ring plunged towards his Soul Ring system in his willpower.

The five Soul Rings circulated in slow motion beneath while the red Soul Ring remained still and afloat above. This was Garen’s current Soul Ring system.

Upon the assault of the red ring, the six Soul Rings trembled, releasing strands of transparent threads, covering the incoming ring from all directions.

The threads snapped one by one by the powerful velocity but as the threads snapped, the speed of the shooting ring swiftly decreased.

Garen expanded his Soul Power to probe within the Soul Ring. He was pleasantly surprised.

“She even helped me wipe out the will imprint.” That female elf must really be thankful for his treatment or else she wouldn’t come to wipe out the will imprint as it would exhaust much Soul Power. If it were Garen, it would require at least a few years of Soul Power to wipe out and assimilate the Soul Ring but now he didn’t need go through the trouble.

He could just merge it.

His Soul Power attracted this new Soul Ring to fly towards his six Soul Rings structure. He was in precision command of the velocity while leaving out a structure space that could be added in his Soul Ring structure.

Click.

A soft noise was heard.

This Soul Ring steadily landed at the top of his entire structure.

“Such a shame. This one Soul Ring isn’t enough to become Orange.”

“I originally thought that with these two Soul Rings, I’ll enter the yellow layer and become top level Demon Lord.”

“I can’t believe what a distance this leap would be…” Garen frowned and immediately felt that for this seventh Soul Ring to become orange, he would require at least another two Soul Rings.

“No wonder that person was generous.”

“In their eyes, even if they lost this red Soul Ring, it wouldn’t hurt them one bit…”

He thought about it before taking out a black and red little pearl.

“Pearl of the Temple…” This pearl with divinity could gift him another Soul Ring but the absorption process was not without its twists and turns.

“I’ll give it a try!”

Garen gritted his teeth and tossed the pearl into his mouth. He then closed his eyes.

Chapter 1347: Confidence 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Pearl of the Temple entered his throat like a scalding glass ball. Garen crushed it with his fangs and it shot out large amounts of thick liquid.

A sort of fishy liquid in oil form flowed in Garen’s mouth. He did not taste it and gulped it down whole.

Within his Spiritual Soul Space, a pitch black ring slowly took shape in the dark shadows. The ring slowly rotated and headed for Garen’s Soul Rings core structure.

Different from the Soul Ring before, the insides of this Soul Ring lingered with streaks of fiery black aura. That was one of the special divinity harbored within. Garen could differentiate with difficulty that this divinity was of the Undead attribute.

In order to completely absorb this Soul Ring, he must first overcome the effect of this divinity.

The divinity at this moment was equivalent to the will of the Soul Ring. Hence, it has to be banished before it could be absorb in full.

Garen shot large amount of transparent threads from the core structure, in attempt to cocoon the black Soul Ring.

But massive amount of corroding gas was released from the Soul Ring and melted away the threads.

“It’s not working.” Garen frowned. If this kept up, he would only exhaust the Pearl of the Temple and the Soul Power of his Soul Rings for nothing.

He thought about it before taking the semi-divine weapon, Despair Skull out.

This gloomy human head-looking skull’s chin was bobbing up and down by itself. Its black eye sockets was burning with hollow blue light.

A faint white thread from the forces of the divine weapons crept in from Garen’s claw into his Soul Space, making a dash towards that Pearl of the Temple Soul Ring.

Unlike from Garen’s earlier thread, this strand easily plunged inside the Pearl of the Temple Soul Ring. The divinity in the Soul Ring and divinity of the divine weapon reached a certain stage of merging.

“Looks like this works.” Garen was relieved from seeing a result from the method he had earlier decided for the Pearl of the Temple.

He started to cautiously control the thread of the divine weapon, tugging the divinity out of the Pearl of the Temple.

This was a painstaking effort as each time the thread would break without reeling in much of a distance. But Garen showed no signs of impatience. He slowly pulled with perseverance.

“Level Seven Arcane Art course analysis complete.”

His willpower mind prompted.

The majority of resources and calculation of Garen’s willpower mind was used to calculate and analyze divinity while the remaining deciphered the next levelling method of Arcane Art. This sort of levelling didn’t just depend on Weave to level but rather ancient knowledge of the non-Weave casting.

The advantage lay on the ability to dispatch elemental energy at will without the restriction of the regulated upper limit for Weave but the disadvantage was the long and delayed release time of a spell. It was far from the Weave spell that was swift and quick.

He was already a level six wizard and after building the wizard tower, his wizardry level was increasing swiftly each day.

Various spell matrix and various Spirit Power construction structure was just child’s play to Garen. It was his basic instinct to him as a secret warrior, as an Endor Demon Lord towards power, any power or energy control.

As for the total capacity of knowledge and Spirit Power, he has quite an abundance of nourishing Soul Power. He just needed to add on Potential Points and his velocity would be multiple fold over a regular Demon Lord. It would be multiple way ahead over a genius wizard.

“Level seven Arcane Art’s done?” Garen was surprised. He had imagined it would have take longer.

His gaze was fixed on his attribute stats. His eyes halted at the column on his Arcane Art level. There was no control nor comprehension difficulty. He knew the next step to increase it.

Such a development to him who has Potential Points, was simply easy.

It was just using a little bit of Potential Points to cut short the accumulation time, that was all.

His sight lingered a few extra seconds and swoosh, the data on his Arcane Art level changed.

The Arcane Art went from level six to level seven and he only used up five Potential Points.

“Establish level eight analysis.” Garen assigned the task and have his willpower mind to work.

He himself continued to close his eyes to the tugging war of his Pearl of the Temple.

“Leave this to me.”

Suddenly, his back limbs transmitted his thoughts. It was Evil Soldier. He who similarly mastered secret techniques, was also the most qualified to replace Garen in executing this job.

“Alright then, you can handle it.” Garen’s body made way of his awareness and allowed Evil Soldier to take over.

They were actually one body. They were only one person with different faces. It was similar to handling multiple tasks at the same time, but it wasn’t harder than handling multiple tasks at the same time though.

“This tugging war would need around ten days. I possibly wouldn’t be able to help you within these ten days,” Evil Soldier said these words before beginning his management task.

“I will be in charge of the training of Draconic Aura.” Demonic Book in form of his tail transmitted his will. He was the embodiment of Holy Phoenix Demonic Book and similar to Evil Soldier, he was of one body with Garen.

“Then I will take over learning the Arcane Art, hastening the research. With the wizard tower, perhaps I could comprehend the relation between space-time plane and elements in no time and seek a faster breakthrough. As for Seven Lives, you should go participate in the Blood Wars and play your potential to the fullest, to snatch us Potential Points and Soul Power the soonest. I’ll leave Despair Skill with you,” Garen’s true form ordered.

“No problem.” Seven Lives walked out and Garen’s pair of wings naturally disappeared.

With the highest rate of survival but one without wits, combat most suited him.

A few of his incarnations and true form has their own assignments.

Once Seven Lives’ identity has been taken care of so that everyone knew he was his incarnation, Garen started to move to a Plane Laboratory one layer beneath the highest layer.

Plane Laboratory.

With the distribution of assignments, there was a huge consumption of Potential Points.

Seven Lives has taken the semi-divine weapon to go out hunting while Garen’s true form took a break and saw the decrease of Potential Points slowing down.

It seemed that Seven Lives has started his highly effective killing spree and has the semi-divine weapon absorbing and converting into potential aura at the same time.

The research on Draconic Aura and Arcane Arts would require the consumption of Potential Points.

Garen did a mock calculation of the required time and progress, hanging the progress of Draconic Aura in the stats column.

“Level 8 Draconic Aura — In midst of upgrading to level nine…” Demonic Book that formed his tail has left the wizard tower to elsewhere to seek for rare environment to upgrade the Draconic Aura. Level nine Draconic Aura was at a critical juncture that required harsh environmental conditions. As a Frost-type giant dragon, Demonic Book needed to find at least an extremely low temperature area.

Regaining his spirits, Garen focused his true form’s attention on the matter at hand.

The Plane Laboratory has numerous rooms used to summon and hold in custody, special creatures of other planes, worlds or dimensions. All the surface on the walls and ground was engraved with rune characters and symbols. Various different space restraining jewels were inlaid in them.

Just the consumption of a layer has occupied half of Cold Winter Tower’s spending. What a terrifying rate.

Garen walked to the summoning formation in a corner. Around the back was a gloomy and empty dimensional prison. Not one creature was captured.

“Research a variety of different plane forces’ effects and changes on creatures and solidify these forces at the same time that a transformation and evolution common law be grasped.”

“This is the crucial point to enter level nine Arcane Art.”

“I specialize in necromancy and I should carry on my level nine Core Spell selection…”

Every level ten powerhouse has to choose their own core abilities, the same for Arcanists as well. Garen too needed to consider the selection of his core spell entering into level nine. It was quite late for him to do so as many wizards would start to strengthen one or a genre of spell by level five or six. Garen upgraded at a rapid speed due to Potential Points and so he hadn’t had the time or energy to think about these things.

He took out a spell book from his space equipment where it was recorded all the basic spell models that he knew. Any deviation or variant would come from basic spells so selecting the core would start from there.

There was not much level nine spell for basic spell models but all represented a different direction in terms of research.

The Succubus’ Wail on pure attack, Energy Draining Spell on negative state or Ultimate Rotting Capsule Spell on biochemical research attack as well as Life Concealing Spell on biochemical research defense, etc.

There were also Undead Disaster on summoning control and Soul Binding Spell on toying with souls.

Garen wasn’t lacking any subordinates, what he needed was the genre he could raise his abilities on.

He originally chosen his core ability to be his Poisonous Eye. He wanted to combine the elevation of Arcane Art with his Poisonous Eye that this ability would be strengthened and elevated too.

As a basic model of a level nine spellcraft, the one that could merge with his Poisonous Eye was Energy Draining Spell.

Energy Draining Spell was a level nine spellcraft that could weaken the enemy by decreasing their levels by two to four levels.

Of course, at the prerequisite that the enemy wasn’t immunized to magic defense.

Once this terrifying level nine spellcraft took effect, if the enemy wasn’t immunized then even at level ten and above, they would be weakened by at least two levels. How terrifying.

But as a wizard, this genre of spellcraft would require to penetrate countless protective forcefields before it could make it to the enemy.

So in actual fact, its function wouldn’t come to full play unless it was against a defenseless enemy.

But if it were blended together with his Poisonous Eye, perhaps he could use the penetrating corrosion of Poisonous Eye to bypass this and then bring Energy Draining Spell to its use. This way, even if the energy was in no state against Poisonous Eye, Energy Draining Spell could also weaken their state at maximum limit.

Garen weighed in his options and mocked an analysis of possible success rate.

Once arcanists reached level nine, they could compress their selected core spell onto themselves or onto an item. Of course, this would require utmost patience and concentration of the spirit, as well as total grasp over this spellcraft.

“Analyze energy Draining Spell, conclude completion time,” Garen ordered.

The remaining willpower mind and calculation ability could manage one task with difficulty. Although the velocity would lessen, but it was still faster than any regular wizard by multiple folds.

“Assignment established, analysis begin. Level nine Energy Draining Spell…”

Responding a feedback, Garen pressed on a summon binding formation button on the wall.

Hiss!

A layer of protective barrier erected onto a formation in the corner.

“Summon selection, Heavenly creature.”

“Summon selection, level five. Random summon.”

The command voice of the wizard tower was heard.

Garen moved his claw and gently poured in a thick and powerful Spirit Power to initiate the positive energy pool stockpile on the peak of the wizard tower.

The formation was like a caged prison and its internal and ground immediately let out a dull white ray of light.

Swoosh!

A grey-feathered angel in white battle armor appeared in the formation. This angel wasn’t a pure form of human appearance. The head was of a roc. The neck was covered up to the upper half of the body with grey feathers.

“Roc-feathered Angel, huh?”

Garen narrowed his eyes and could tell immediately the race of this summoned fella.

Chapter 1348: Confidence 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Roc-feathered Angel was one of the most famous Summoned Creatures in the Heavens. It was known for its power and gentle nature but another key factor of its reputation was its extremely close-knit relationship with upright Wizards. One of the famous spells in low-level Spellcrafting that was called the Roc-feathered Angel’s Eye was researched collaboratively by the Wizards and these creatures.

“Damn Abyss aura! I’ve fallen for it!!”

This Roc-feathered Angel appeared irritated immediately after being summoned out. Although the Abyss aura here was isolated by a Matrix, it could still be detected by his keen senses.

This fellow was holding a silvery white flail in his hands. The wings on his back flapped a few times and made popping noises while he glared ferociously at the White Dragon that had properly released a Matrix already.

“Evil White Dragon…”

Garen ignored his words. He wanted to thoroughly research Energy Draining Spells but its main difficulty was to clarify the concepts of the supposed levels towards living creatures. He needed to know the types of beings that were used as indicators to differentiate between them.

The first part of the Energy Draining Spell’s effects was to decrease its opponent’s level for 24 hours. The toughness of their Vitality would be evaluated once again during the next part before the Energy Draining Spell would erupt in a one-time erosion. If the opponent could not endure it, their level would decrease by one grade permanently.

This was the most terrifying part.

Powerful pursuing and killing abilities were the best match for Energy Draining Spells because it would not spare one’s opponent any time to stop for their wounds to recuperate.

Thus, even if their opponents did not die, their skin would still molt extremely disgustingly.

Garen curled and uncurled his claws while looking at the Roc-feathered Angel inside the Matrix that did not seem afraid of him at all.

“I should dissect it first…” He felt somewhat nostalgic towards his old self from the previous Totem World. This feeling was slightly similar to his past.

He walked towards the Matrix slowly while harboring a tinge of reminiscence.

**********************

Time passed little by little.

More than a decade had passed in the blink of an eye… Major changes had also occurred throughout the entire situation.

The Void Crevices had also increased. It seemed as though the normal masses on the Primary Plane had also discovered their presence and the existence of Void Creatures.

Meanwhile, since the church of the Gods could not be concealed either, they simply proceeded to make it public in an attempt to encourage everyone to participate in the Void Creature hunting movement.

Certain violent Void Creatures engaged in massacres wantonly and slaughtered the regular masses while causing extreme fear among the populace.

However, massacres brought about power throughout both sides. This applied to everyone regardless of whether they were Void Creatures or the common people of this world. This was an internal strife between these two great worlds that left to leeway for compromise.

Several normal Warriors suddenly felt as if various aspects of their bodily strength and physical fitness had rapidly increased after they had killed a Void Creature by a fluke. They were instantly pleasantly surprised.

It would not have been a big deal if these instances had only occurred once. However, it caused a great stir suddenly when this phenomenon happened numerous times.

Large-scale spontaneous Void Creature encircling and suppressing movements were launched.

Both sides were engaged in a mutual massacre where there were no rights or wrongs but only their yearning and greed for power.

As more than a decade of slaughtering and conflict passed, certain forces and beings with powerful abilities gradually became well-known during the battles.

Among the Gods, more than ten Gods died consecutively as if they were meteors that fell from the sky after the first Middle God passed away. These Gods were quickly replaced by powerful and terrifying beings from the Void.

There were three representatives that could move forward in this world and live as comfortably as the Void Creatures as well.

Eye of the Slaughter had divided himself to spread all over the major planes. After the terrifying Demon Master Level creatures that were encircled all along had devoured four Gods consecutively, their powers then swelled to seemingly unstoppable levels. When they had finally personally fought Mother of Nature in a major battle, they were later injured terribly by Fehra. After escaping by the skin of their teeth, they decided to lie low. Nonetheless, they had successfully accomplished extremely terrifying military exploits.

Mother of Nature was also badly injured before she fell into a state of deep slumber. This was simply a situation where both sides suffered!!

This incident greatly shocked all of the Gods in this world. They became even more anxious and cautious while encountering Void Creatures.

Distortion Demon Master.

After leading her pets to cause havoc throughout Meteor City and destroying Fehra’s Divine Statue, she could still escape unscathed. Next, she devoured all of the lives within an entire great empire in the east. The numerous Demon Masters among her subordinates became the nominal leaders of the Mother Stream Alliance. They occupied the domain of that empire directly before repelling the Pantheon’s Holy War army many times. They were currently embroiled in a fierce fight.

This throne had foreshadowed a conclusion that involved a seemingly infinite number of corpses and souls.

There was also the Fallen True Soul in the end. The body of this individual who was the strongest True Soul among the Ancient Endorian True Souls had stretched over several planes. Moreover, there were numerous True Soul powerhouses among her subordinates whose powers were at strong Divine Power grades at least. After ambushing one of the vast mountain ranges in the south with lightning speed, they occupied it as their territory. Their organization was called Void Temple. The formation of their members was extremely complicated but their overall forces were much stronger than that of the Mother Stream Alliance. However, their social order was chaotic and there were no restrictions. Thus, the True Souls started wars unscrupulously on their own.

These three powerhouses were terrifying mainstays that rapidly emerged prominently within a decade of the war. They had opened up numerous Void Crevices and led in an almost inexhaustible amount of Void Creatures that were currently embroiled in a fierce battle with the local original inhabitants of this world.

The powerful beings that had accumulated in the Void after numerous years were seemingly uncountable. Moreover, the strength that was accumulated from their massacres had achieved the peak level of the mortal world whereby they could not advance anymore. They required a greater amount of various types of Inspirations and breakthroughs.

Thus, the high-ranking forces such as the Primary Plane of this local world and the Mountain of Heavens of the Upper Plane had gradually fallen into a declining state.

Their territory gradually fell into their enemy’s hands step by step. The Pantheon forces that were led by Fehra shrunk back at every step.

The situation was momentarily unusually far from good.

Meanwhile, Garen sheltered himself in Vengeance Fortress during this ten-year duration to improve his accumulation slowly but steadily.

His Poisonous Eye had already successfully fused with the Energy Draining Spell while his power had upgraded itself to the next level to reach Level Fourteen.

Meanwhile, Garen had successfully extracted a drop of the Purgatory power’s essence while researching the forces in the Planes. This was a huge advancement in the aspect of biological modifications.

His body had also healed to a completely healthy state as well because Fehra’s previous curse had disappeared fully. Moreover, the Pearl of the Temple’s Soul Ring had also fused into his body’s composition completely too. This allowed Garen’s seventh Soul Ring to turn orange successfully. He had entered the second phase of the Seven Colors Phase. He could advance to the Upper Demon King Level as long as he entered the next stage.

Once his Arcane Technique was upgraded to Level Nine, Garen used his Potential Points, to accumulate an abundance of knowledge and techniques in an extremely short span of time. He made rapid progress in the Space-Time and Plane aspects.

Additionally, his Draconic Aura had achieved Level Ten even quicker due to the Demonic Book’s practices, Level Nine Arcane Technique, and his own powerful Poisonous Eye and terrifying physical fitness.

Without the Space-Time Spell’s restriction shortcomings, Garen integrated powers had already entered Level Fourteen successfully now.

However, he did not reveal them inside Vengeance Fortress. Meanwhile, Seven Lives moving about outside all along during these years. He took the Semi-Divine Weapon Despair Skull and absorbed Potential Points everywhere.

Most of these Potential Points were used to upgrade his Arcane Technique research and Draconic Aura.

The average beings including Upper Level Demon Kings that wanted to increase their Draconic Aura, Arcane Techniques, and physical fitness to this level needed at least a few hundred or even a thousand years to be able to do so if they did not have the help of Potential Points. However, Garen was different… This was his advantage.

Thus, no one knew even until now that Garen had actually successfully entered the level of peak powerhouses in the mortal world already.

Aside from him, the other beings did not seem to be making any progress. It was almost impossible to even dream of obtaining any obvious improvements within such a short time of merely a decade or slightly more.

Andrew was the only one who could barely upgrade to Level Eleven. However, it was obvious that he had become increasingly exhausted as it continued.

Garen gave him another Semi-Divine that he had obtained from trading. Since that Semi-Divine Weapon was basically used for attacking, Garen was not interested in it at all. His strongest asset was his own body and he did not need the support of a Divine Weapon in any way.

After he had achieved Level Fourteen overall, Garen began to set about preparing for his Void Original Opus to be upgraded.

However, several surprises finally appeared in his smooth sailing life at this time.

*********************

“Someone has been spreading rumors that there are Void Creatures among my subordinates?” Garen narrowed his dragon eyes while looking at the other core members below him with a somewhat pondering gaze.

Andrew, the Level Eleven Undead Knight had only been transferred to the position of an Undead recently. This fellow’s pursuit of strength had already reached an insane degree. The Semi-Divine Weapon called Sword of Nuhas that he carried on his back was an overpowered Greatsword that possessed Soul Intimidation abilities. This was also the present that the Black Fish King had given Garen while trading with him.

The General that was successfully promoted by the White Feather Squadron was called Mander but his last name was unknown. Perhaps he had another identity but Garen was unconcerned. This man whose face could not be seen clearly because he was constantly shrouded in a black robe was so mysterious that some people even feared him.

He was currently the captain of the White Feather Squadron.

Next up were the president and vice president of the small-scale association called Cold Winter Claw. This association was established by the two Abominable Snowman ringleaders that had arrived at the fortress initially. Through Garen’s support, these two Level Twelve Abominable Snowmen managed to quickly draw in a large crowd of upscale mercenaries and Abyss Demons including their enemies the Bartoyen Demons. These beings who were their members had one similarity which was their love for slaughtering and their bloodthirsty nature.

Finally, there were the three Chiefs of White Dragon Mountain, the Demon-Hag tribe, and the Corpse Monster Party organizations who were all powerful beings between Level Eleven to Level Fourteen.

These were half of Vengeance Fortress’ forces that Garen was currently controlling.

Aside from Garen, no one knew that the Demon-Hag tribe, Corpse Monster Party, and one of the Abominable Snowmen among the group of powerhouses in front of him were actually Void Creature parasitic bodies.

Despite being a Level Fourteen being, Garen outward manifestations were only at Level Twelve all this while. Although he had the help of the Wizard Tower, his Arcane Technique level was not considered high. Moreover, since he had never revealed his great Spellcrafting powers, he had gradually faded from everyone’s memories.

Cold Winter Tower looked more like an ornamental building instead of a Wizard Tower that was high above the masses.

“There are no Void Creatures among my subordinates. As the head, I would naturally know this matter best…” said Garen flatly. “It’s obvious that someone is trying to give me additional trouble by spreading these rumors at a crucial time like this when Void Creatures are our main enemies…”

“However, people have been spreading information and saying that an extremely powerful Void Creature is hiding inside your Wizard Tower, Commander. Someone personally witnessed her flying inside before disappearing completely…”

The White Dragon Mountain Emissary had an unfriendly look on his face when he spoke. The Void Crevice had caused a large number of deaths in White Dragon Mountain while two of the Elders that they had sent were assassinated at the same time. Moreover, their souls were even offered as sacrifices. Tiamat was so furious that she sent an oracle so that Garen would cooperate with all his might and investigate. However, Garen had declined.

Everyone could see that there was something wrong with Garen because of this as he had the audacity to refuse the Dragon Goddess’ oracle. Any other White Dragon who was in his place would have probably been divinely punished instantly. However, Ann who was behind Garen caused Tiamat to be too afraid to charge into the fortress directly.

Lady Vengeance was overseeing that place. The high-level beings were actually already aware of the relationship between her and Ann.

Almost everyone assumed that Garen was only so confident because he was relying on Ann. However, no one knew that he was actually relying on Deception Demon Master who was hiding in his Wizard Tower.

This woman’s powers were completely indeterminate now. Was she a Demigod? Perhaps a Lower God? Garen could not tell either. He merely knew that another day that Deception Demon Master existed was another day that he could borrow her power.

He was confident enough to face any force as long as he had this relationship.

Moreover, it looked like Deception Demon Master was planning to use him as a form of protection so that she could develop herself in the Abyss for a longer period…

Chapter 1349: Evolution 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It doesn’t necessarily mean anything just because someone witnessed it.” An unenthusiastic expression remained on Garen’s face.

“Are you saying that you aren’t planning to admit it, Commander?” said the White Dragon Mountain Emissary angrily. He had already viewed this mere Level Twelve commander in a bad light long ago. His insignificant forces depended on the strong beings behind him while he used his powerful connections to intimidate others and lead powerhouses that possessed strength that was far greater than his own. This was simply an insult to the honor of strong individuals like himself.

He was a Level Fourteen White Dragon in White Dragon Mountain who knew exactly what was going on!

“What is he not admitting? You can’t just make false accusations like this, Lord Cavenly.” Andrew remained on the side and interrupted fearlessly.

“Andrew you brat, do you have the right to speak when I’m talking to the Commander?” Cavenly of White Dragon Mountain glared at Andrew fiercely.

“Alright, alright, stop fighting. These Void Creatures or whatever are fine on the Primary Plane, so when they’re in our Abyss, who would care about these things?” screeched the representative Elder of the Demon-Hag tribe slowly. “Even if there were Void Creatures, why would it matter? We’ve never concerned ourselves with the origins of any creatures. As long as they’re in the Abyss, they’re one of us.”

“Blasphemer!” Cavenly of White Dragon Mountain’s eyes widened before he glared fiercely at the Demon-Hag Elder.

“Tiamat may be your goddess but she is not ours. You should be more careful when you speak, Cavenly.” The Demon-Hag Elder did not seem afraid of him at all.

“Silence!”

When Garen saw that the people below him were about to quarrel, he simply clapped his hands and made some noise.

“Don’t concern yourselves with the rumors that other people are spreading. Right now, I need you to launch a surprise attack,” instructed Garen.

“Surprise attack?” said the Abominable Snowman Sara. “I’d like that! What kind of opponent are we facing this time, Commander?” He hit both of his fists against each other firmly while itching for a fight.

“Our goal this time…” Garen smiled faintly before continuing, “Is Wanku Fortress…”

“Oh?” The Abominable Snowman was slightly shocked.

Although the relationship between fortresses was not amicable now, they were still in the same alliance nonetheless. If they were to ambush another fortress, this would probably cause the other fortresses to unite and attack him instead.

No one objected. Everyone was considering Garen’s real intentions of bringing up this goal to ambush them.

“Does anyone object?” Garen spoke before them instead.

This plan was not formulated by him. On the contrary, it was simply Deception Demon Master’s demand.

This woman was not very content with only controlling half of the fortress because the laws in the Abyss were not treated as rules anyway. Although they were part of the same clan and alliance in name, no one had ruled that he could not ambush other fortresses. On the other hand, the Abyss would become more joyful because of this. The only issue was that they would have to bear a slightly greater pressure.

Since it happened to be time for them to proceed with an expansion anyway, Garen might as well aim his first goal on Wanku Fortress.

“I object,” said Mander, the Captain of the White Feather Squadron in a low voice. “With our current forces, our probability of successfully ambushing Wanku Fortress would be too low. The success rate of the plan is not great.”

“It doesn’t matter.” Garen raised his hand. “Two of Wanku Fortresses’ Deputy Commanders will dispatch people to be in charge of solving that. Moreover, I believe that their Chief Commander and Fortress Master will have a favorable final destination.” He did not state it clearly even though it appeared that he had other arrangements already.

Fortress Masters needed to be at least Level Fifteen powerhouses while simultaneously having solid backgrounds. It was also possible that they were the incarnations of certain powerful beings. However, Garen actually dared to say these words lightly.

This caused the hearts of everyone on site to tremble slightly at once.

“Since it looks like the Commander has decided already, we should just leave it at that,” said the party leader of the Corpse Monster Party quietly. “We can’t do anything that is out of our abilities but we can still do everything that’s in our power.”

“The massacre will bring even more resources and souls. Moreover, I need all these things,” said Garen, smiling.

The main point was determined then. Another round of war had erupted due to Garen’s few sentences.

Numerous Demon armies and large crowds of mercenaries and slaves charged towards Wanku Fortress that was adjoining to them. While being led by various leaders, more than a million powerful armies rushed rapidly towards Wanku Fortress that was shaped like a human ribcage.

The news traveled throughout the surrounding domains and the other fortresses quickly and immediately provoked the resentment of the Demons. Meanwhile, the Devils did the opposite. They did not actually go and attack the Void’s Vengeance Fortress. On the contrary, they converged with Vengeance Fortress’ army and attacked Wanku from the side.

Hell Army’s fourteenth division commanded over a million Devils and brought thousands of Floating Hell Battleships and various battle fortresses that covered the sky and earth as they rushed towards Wanku and launched their general offensive.

Wanku’s Commander was left with no alternative but to personally put his hand to the task out of fury. Together with his two subordinate Deputy Commanders and three first-rate powerhouses, he brought the Divine Weapon Bow of Extermination officially out to war. He was going to face a powerful opponent who was about to arrive.

Hell Army’s Commander Black Jade Horn brought his Hell Divine Weapon as well to undertake the task and fight Wanku’s Commander directly.

********************

The sky was split into red and blue halves respectively that dyed the Abyss’ dark red deathly still sky into two different colored domains.

Numerous flames were suspended in the red sky while an abundance of blue ice crystals were floating in the blue part of the sky.

Two silhouettes of which one was red while the other was blue were colliding against each other violently now on the boundary in the middle of the two parts of the sky. They were like comets that constantly shot towards each other before turning around. They dragged their long comet tails out behind them again and again while they clashed against each other and released thunderous quaking noises.

The red figure was a Demon in flaming armor who held a double sword in his hand. He was a standard Bartoyen Demon that had a cow’s head, a bear’s body, and the legs of an elephant. Great high-temperature flames would also burn throughout his entire body constantly. He held a flaming Greatsword in one hand and a pitch-black crystal Greatsword in the other. An Energy Field that was made of terrifying temperatures that reached more than ten thousand degrees twisted in his surroundings endlessly and scorched the air until it was completely blurry.

He was the Commander of Wanku Fortress, the Level Fifteen peak Bartoyen Demon– Ron.

The blue figure on the other side wore an armor that was made of ice and a silver crown on his head. He was a muscular Warrior whose lower body was vaporized while his upper body had the same appearance as a human male except that both of his eyes were profoundly dark blue while his hair was burning with fluttering blue flames.

He was the Hell Army’s Commander Behemoth Dark, a peak Level Fifteen existence. He held a gigantic ice hammer in his hand tightly. This was his specialized Divine Weapon, the Ice Warhammer.

The changes that were occurring in both parts of the sky were caused by the terrifying energy radiation that burst forth when the black crystal sword and blue warhammer clashed against each other constantly.

The mere repercussions that erupted from the radiation made the Abyss’ adverse circumstances even more frightening.

There were not many soldiers below who dared to approach this place.

On the other side, numerous Demons and Devils were engaged in a mad slaughter. The light from their energy and their Spells that blasted forth occurred endlessly in waves while arrows, rolling stones, kerosene, corroding poisonous gas bombs, Exploding Corpses, and other various war weapons crisscrossed continuously.

A few of them had rushed too deeply into battle while their eyes were red with bloodlust. They had just chopped off a Devil’s head before they were immediately crushed into minced meat by the other Devils.

The Thorn Archers and Skeleton Archers shot their arrows and caused them to come down in torrents as Magic Arrows that carried various symbols rained down like a storm and caused numerous deaths on the battlefield.

Various large-scale Battle Spells like Meteor Fire Shower and Cold Winter Hail covered the sky and earth while enveloping numerous battle areas.

The entire battlefield was filled with chaos, massacres, and wails.

The Demons attacked the side where Vengeance Fortress’ military base camp was located.

A smaller-sized White Dragon was sitting on a specially-made metal seat while numerous elite first-rate powerhouses were following it from behind and gazing from afar at the Energy Tide that was flaring up in the sky on the faraway battlefield.

The White Dragon was Garen who was currently leading an army forward from Vengeance Fortress.

“The moment has almost arrived now and it’s time to prepare for the great battle that is about to begin,” he said in a low voice. “Your Excellency, are you prepared?”

“Prepared? No no no…” The woman in the black robe behind Garen laughed quietly. She looked like a normal elite woman who was merely standing behind Garen but everyone on site knew that she was the one who had truly initiated the war. She was the supreme and unparalleled being that came from the Void– Deception Demon Master.

“There’s nothing to prepare,” smiled Demon Master while answering.

“My powers can be restored at a rapid pace. As long as I devour most of the souls during this war again, more than half of my powers can probably be restored. Meanwhile, you…”

She looked at Garen who was in front of her.

“The only thing that you need now is the guidance of some qualitative changes… Level Fifteen qualitative changes…”

“Qualitative changes?” Garen’s powers could naturally not be hidden from Deception Demon Master. The disguise on his body was also arranged by Deception Demon Master. As a Demon Master who was named after lies, this individual’s disguises and tricking abilities were second to none among the Demon Masters. The Gods could not even dream of seeing through Garen’s true powers even if they came here.

However, he still remained as a Level Twelve White Dragon in the eyes of the outsiders.

“Yes, qualitative changes… I’ll give you the Wanku Fortress Master’s core as a gift to repay you.” Deception Demon Master spread her hands out before the shrunken Void Shadows of the two Head Commanders who were engaged in battle in the faraway sky appeared on her palm slowly.

The shrunken versions of them seemed to be clashing on her palm endlessly as if they did not realize that anything was wrong.

“Qualitative changes…” Garen had a vague idea in his heart. The core that he had decided on was the Poisonous Eye. However, as its rate of progress increased recently, changes finally appeared throughout the Enneahedron that had not stirred all along. The Enneahedron was the most effective key core that used the accumulated power from slaughtering when Void Creatures entered this world.

Even though Garen had killed so many creatures, he had not seemed to realize the functions of this plaything towards himself.

However, he could suddenly sense on this battlefield now that the faint vibrations had finally appeared throughout the Enneahedron that had blackened already.

Crack…

Subtle, brittle cracking noises echoed from the Enneahedron slowly. Garen focused on it mentally before quickly discovering that an unending stream of various faint split marks had appeared throughout the inside of the Enneahedron.

As the cracks increased, Garen gradually sensed that faint changes were slowly surging upwards from the lowest root level of life. It rushed towards his head steadily after flowing throughout his entire body.

Deception Demon Master glanced at him and smiled but remained silent.

“He’s started evolving. Since the Enneahedron apparently needed to accumulate for such a long time before it could erupt, it looks like his body’s evolution needs even more sources,” said another Void parasitic body powerhouse quietly.

“That’s normal. I’ve never seen the Snakeback White Dragon branch of the White Dragon Race before,” giggled another female Demon charmingly.

More changes occurred throughout Garen’s body as the Enneahedron collapsed.

He regained his initial gigantic physique suddenly and broke the chair instantly. He was about to soar into the sky but Deception Demon Master waved her hand gently before he returned to his previous state immediately.

From an outsider’s view, Garen was still sitting on the chair and speaking to his subordinates happily. However, Garen’s body was already flying in the sky in reality. Large, contoured pieces of muscle appeared throughout his entire body while layers of molted skin began to show up on his skin as well.

Hiss!!

Garen raised his head and roared suddenly. There was a tearing noise before two pairs of fleshy wings that resembled cicada’s wings appeared on his back suddenly. His original dragon wings shrunk gradually and turned into slender fleshy wings that were exactly like the two other pairs. All three pairs of these body parts that totaled into six wings flapped on Garen’s back slowly. These wings did not have scales on the surface and were fully dripping in blood from top to bottom. They looked like wings after they were flayed as damp mucus flowed across their surface.

Shh!

Suddenly, a seemingly infinite and countless amount of densely-packed light green eyes burst open on Garen’s six wings instantly. These little eyes resembled fully-formed blisters that blinked on his wings slowly and looked on with purely evil and greedy gazes.

Hiss!!!

Garen lifted his slender snakelike neck and released an ear-piercing, sharp whistle fiercely.

Chapter 1350: Evolution 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He finally discovered the true function of the Enneahedron now.

It was used to accumulate killing energy to allow one’s body to fully evolve and advance to a higher grade from its foundation after that.

The White Dragon’s initial evolved level was clearly unlike Garen’s own as it would gradually develop by enlarging their physique and hardening their skin. On the contrary, perhaps it was due to Garen’s own exercises or because of certain factors that caused his evolution to fully break away from the initial and normal domain.

He currently had three pairs of wings on his back that flapped slowly and were completely covered in numerous light green eyes. Meanwhile, the numerous poisonous and unimaginably fierce snakes that were initially on his back had currently crowded together closely and were releasing soft hissing noises continuously.

Meanwhile, both of his eyes on the front of his body had enlarged while two slightly smaller eyeballs had apparently grown in the middle of his original ones. It seemed like they were embedded in the center of his pupils. These two smaller eyeballs could even turn and blink on their own in an unimaginably strange manner.

Garen’s entire body felt warm and incomparably comfortable.

Once the evolution was fully completed, Garen glanced at his current state. He saw that various major changes had occurred indeed. It would have been fine if the Enneahedron’s functions did not react at all as the changes that occurred the moment it activated were truly terrifying.

‘Garen— Strength 210, Agility 210, Vitality 210, Intelligence 210. Potential 2829%. Soul Limit 210.

Seven Soul Rings: Five Colorless, Red, Orange.

Level 10 Draconic Aura. Level 9 Arcane Arts.’ 10 Potential Points in one month. 10 Potential Points to upgrade one attribute.

Void Original Opus– 70%. Hind Legs– Evil Soldier, Wings– Seven Lives, Tail– Demonic Book.

Comprehensive evaluation– Level Twelve. Title– Winter Sigh.

These were still considered normal but there were tremendous changes in the sections below.

Core abilities–

Poisonous Eye (Energy Draining Spell effect): Level Fifteen.

Natural Poison Region: Those with Vitalities below 50 will automatically fall into a comatose state and lose their lives while there is a probability that those with Vitalities below 100 will appear weaker (and be demoted by 1 to 4 levels), but those with Vitalities above 130 will be immune to the effects.

Spiritual Poison: There is a certain probability that psychological disorders, weakened curses, amplified negative emotions, and other unfavorable effects will appear in beings that are below Level Fifteen after they are watched attentively by Garen’s Eye of Evil. Positive energy cannot get rid of this but those with Intelligence levels of 100 and above will be automatically immune to these effects.

These were the special abilities that he had obtained. They were simply normal skills that could be activated without needing to consume energy. Thus, they were as easy as eating and drinking to Garen. The Natural Poison Region was basically a toxic Energy Field that was naturally released by his body. It was equivalent to the biological fields that radiated out of human bodies naturally. As long as he was alive, it would release itself endlessly.

Meanwhile, the Spiritual Poison came on its own. Unless Garen suppressed it willingly, any beings that looked at him face to face would not be exempted from receiving the Spiritual Poison’s appraisal.

On the contrary, the other one was truly a great surprise to Garen.

‘Talent of a member of the Dragon Race that has evolved to the Ultimate State– Dragon’s Heart.’

When this ability appeared abruptly, Garen had yet to understand its functions clearly. However, the explanation that appeared after his gaze fell on the top immediately improved his mood tremendously at once.

‘Dragon’s Heart: An evolved ability that naturally appears when an Ultimate State member of the Dragon Race evolves to the peak level. It can only be used once. Those in the Ultimate State can choose to use the Dragon’s Heart to increase one of their body’s abilities such as Vitality, Strength, Speed, or effects of Innate Spells. (Increment effect + 2 Level)’

“An upgrade of two levels… Tch tch.” Garen naturally understood that the two levels that were being referred to here were not as simple as adding two points to his attributes.

If these two levels were differentiated according to the laws of this world instead, that would be terrifying…

His current comprehensive abilities were around Level Fifteen but these were upgraded by relying on his strongest ability, the Poisonous Eye. The Poisonous Eye could be extremely threatening towards Level Fifteen beings and could even affect them by decreasing their levels. This was the factor which had truly allowed Garen’s comprehensive evaluation to reach Level Fifteen.

He was clearly aware that his powers would only peak at Level Twelve or Thirteen if he did not have this Natural Ability.

In comparison to the upgrades of the Dragon’s Heart, the other minor increments towards his average attributes and Soul Limit were insignificant.

Garen did not hesitate at all and immediately drew the faint warm currents of the Dragon’s Heart that was entrenched in his own heart towards the position of his two eyes directly.

Several changes appeared throughout the abilities of both of his eyes quickly.

It changed into a new state immediately from ‘Poisonous Eye (Energy Draining Spell effect): Level Fifteen’.

‘Death Glare (Energy Draining effect): Terrifying poisonous attacks that are slightly bound by laws. It disregards levels but those with 2 or more Divine Personas are immune to the effects.’

“Divine Personas, huh?” Garen knew that the Great Arcanists in this world used Divine Souls to differentiate between levels. There was feeble Divine Power, weak Divine Power, average Divine Power, powerful Divine Power, and supernatural Divine Power. These five stages used minute Divine Persona digits respectively to differentiate them into ranges.

“According to the information in Ann’s book, weak Divine Power requires at least 10 Divine Persona or more while feeble Divine Power only needs 10 of that or below, which refers to the range of anything above 0. In other words, my Innate Core Spell is already sufficient to threaten Gods with feeble Divine Power?”

Garen had a vague idea in his mind.

Demigods did not have Divine Personas but only had Divinity instead. They had to complete their Divinity to form a Divine Domain before they could accumulate a large amount of Worship Power and ignite the Sacred Fire. Only then could they truly fuse their Divinity, Divine Domain, and Divine Power with their own bodies as one to form Divine Personas. They would only truly be considered as Gods then.

Thus, Garen had already obtained powerful abilities that could threaten Demigods now.

Once his evolution was complete, Garen shrunk his body and descended slowly.

It appeared that the gazes of Deception Demon Master and Garen’s two other Demigod subordinates had become exceptionally sensitive at this moment. Initially, Garen could not sense the powerful extents of these three individuals but now that his strength was upgraded to its limit, he could really sense the exact details of the trio’s powers. He met the trio’s gazes before instantly feeling that his scales and skin were scorching hot and aching as if they were being pierced by needles and sliced by knives.

“Your Excellency, thanks to you, I’ve finished evolving successfully,” Garen respectfully thanked Deception Demon Master for her protection. If it was not for her, his exact identity would probably have been fully exposed instantly.

Revealing all of one’s powers in the Abyss was an extremely and undeniably stupid thing to do.

“The Enneahedron can help evolve and upgrade the essence of living creatures. From the looks of it, the various genes and Soul Imprints that you accumulated from the very beginning are very complicated. Their current state has been influenced by your soul and your body’s breakthroughs to a certain degree. Moreover, have you still been analyzing Divinity recently? It should probably be related to the poisonous or corrosive types.”

Deception Demon Master could see through Garen’s current state with one look.

“Your Excellency’s insight is very perceptive,” Garen admitted calmly.

“Your powers are currently already equivalent to a Demigod’s,” said the Demigod Kunder softly.

Garen’s eyebrows knitted together briefly before he said, “But I haven’t analyzed Divinity completely yet?”

“But your essence has already been affected by Divinity…” Kunder was the Demigod who had protected Deception Demon Master in the very beginning and was also Proof of Deception’s Chief Leader. “Otherwise, you wouldn’t have transformed into this state.”

Garen was suddenly speechless. He lowered his head and looked at his own body.

Indeed, the effects of Divinity had silently seeped into every cell of his body already. From the moment when his Poisonous Eye was strengthened, it seemed as though there was a consciousness in his body that developed in the direction towards corrosion and poison.

“Your eye makes me feel threatened. Once you finish analyzing Divinity successfully and fuse it into your body completely, that’ll be the time when you become a Demigod,” explained Kunder.

These people were extremely friendly towards Garen because he had initially helped them shield Deception Demon Master.

“Do you still remember the method that I told you about previously?” Deception Demon Master smiled suddenly.

“I remember.” A faint glimmer flashed across Garen’s eyes.

Deception Demon Master had previously mentioned a way for him to absorb a large number of Fragments of the Inspired Soul during battle so that he could upgrade his Soul Ring.

“Despite being a Deputy Commander, it’s simply embarrassing that you actually only have one Semi-Divine Weapon. I’m giving you this.” Deception Demon Master threw over a jet-black ring that was engraved with countless decorative patterns.

“I’m leaving immediately after this war. This is a reward for that period of time when you protected me,” said Deception Demon Master quietly.

Garen could feel that this black ring contained powerful distorted energy the moment he touched it.

“Divine Weapon!” He could not stop himself from making a noise.

“You may face tremendous trouble once I’m gone so I’d suggest that you shift to another place immediately and leave the Abyss,” advised Deception Demon Master. “I’ve recently encountered numerous fellows that possess great powers in our surroundings. From the looks of it, they came from the Dragons of Disaster that were chasing you from behind. Thus, you should be careful.”

“Is it Ann?” Garen narrowed his eyes. “I understand.” His opponent would clearly be at the God Level at least if Deception Demon Master thought that they had great power. If they were not the Gods of Heavenly Mountain, they would be the Evil Gods from the Abyss itself that were living in other levels instead. However, he did not know why they were troubling Ann.

“Alright, go then. This ring can absorb the resentment, hatred, and other negative energy of the souls within a distance of over ten thousand kilometers around you. It will also transform these things into the purest Soul Fragments simultaneously. You can find the fragments that you require from it. However, it’s slightly troublesome in the end. I seized this thing from the hands of God of Death. Although I’ve changed its appearance slightly, it’s best if you conceal it somewhat when you use it. Don’t let anyone discover your specific location.”

“Understood.” Garen nodded gravely.

Boom!!!

Suddenly, a gigantic shroud of smoke exploded in the faraway sky where the victory and defeat had finally been determined in the battle between the two Head Commanders.

The Fortress Master of Wanku Fortress suffered a painful pounding against the side of his waist by the blue Warhammer Divine Weapon. He raised his head and yelled before swinging his double sword madly towards his opponent and attempting to slice him. However, the Divine Weapon’s tremendous vibration caused him to drop his own weapon immediately.

Hell Army’s Commander sneered fiercely before numerous cold Hell Chills extended towards the Demons’ bodies madly as if they were living creatures.

“If I wasn’t being held back by two other Deputy Commanders, would you really still assume that you were my opponent?” he guffawed loudly in his Hell Language.

“No!!!” Wanku Fortress Master’s entire body exploded violently.

A gigantic terrifying red cloud that extended throughout several kilometers exploded before a delicate Demon Core shot in the direction of Garen’s group.

A popping noise could be heard when Garen caught the Demon Core precisely. He could feel the frightening soul and fiery abilities that were surging inside. It was really Wanku Fortress Master’s Origin Demon Core.

“Keep it.” Deception Demon Master seemed unconcerned. “Moving on, if you want to continue upgrading your Soul Ring through the most primitive route of accumulating True Souls, you won’t need a huge amount of Inspired Fragments. Perhaps you’ll improve faster when you’ve just started but your speed will decrease after that. Meanwhile, another method of this world allows you to thread on the path of condensing your Divine Persona. Recruiting followers will be an extremely slow process in the beginning but will become faster later, especially in a chaotic time period like this when all life forms desire more peaceful lives. It’s most suitable for recruiting disciples.”

“Understood…” Garen nodded. It appeared that the Commander of the Hell Army was one of Deception Demon Master’s people as well. It was no wonder she was so certain.

In the dark, he could sense that more of the Power of Abyss seemed to be converging in his body. His body had also started to receive subtle increments throughout his characteristics.

The Will of the Abyss was clearly proceeding by instinctually rewarding them for their chaotic essence.

Aside from slaughtering his enemies, he had even turned around and gotten rid of a Fortress Master who was actually an ally of his side. These chaotic actions had increased the Abyss’ admiration.

Garen immediately felt that the Power of Abyss in his surroundings had increased by a few times instantly.

Chapter 1351: Entrust 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He did not refuse the Power of Abyss at all but absorbed it fully into his body instead. Since he had already spent so many years in the Abyss, his body had been corroded by the Abyss long ago until it possessed the Vitality of an Abyss Creature. Thus, the Power of Abyss was undeniably the greatest tonic for him.

Garen sniffed lightly and noticed that the smell of sulfur in the air around him had seemed to become much more intense.

The battlefield became clearer. The Demons had retreated once again in defeat. Without the support of their leader, the effectiveness of the high-ranking Professionals massacre was even greater than the cannon balls of earth.

Nonetheless, the Corpse Witches’ Exploding Corpse Spells could cause the deaths of more than ten people each time.

Garen looked over from afar and saw that a seemingly countless amount of densely-packed light green Exploding Corpses were centralized on the battlefield and were bursting forth in a completely soundless manner. There were only light green shrouds of smoke that were permeating outwards and dispersing slowly.

A feeling stirred in his heart suddenly before he noticed that Deception Demon Master and the others had disappeared completely at an unknown moment when he turned his head to look.

“They’ve left, huh?” Garen exhaled.

They had left while Ann’s enemies had found him. It looked like it was necessary for him to find Ann and talk to her now. He could not resist her enemies on his own in the Abyss.

Without a single trace of hesitation, Garen raised his hand and snapped his fingers before a shroud of black smoke that was shaped like a dragon shot out. The black smoke soared into the sky and burst into a gigantic and complicated-looking flower in the air.

Bang!

The flowers released a dull exploding noise that echoed throughout the entire battlefield.

All of the Demons and mercenaries that belonged to Vengeance Fortress retreated suddenly one after another. There were only a few maniacs that continued slaughtering and stabbing insanely because they were blinded by bloodlust and their brains were dominated by the Will of the Abyss.

Large crowds of Demons withdrew rapidly while Battleships, Succubi, Little Demons, and Elder Demons in the sky gradually gathered together in the direction of the base camp in an orderly manner.

“I can’t stay in the Abyss any longer…” Garen looked at his numerous Demon subordinates before him and knew that he did not have much time left in the Abyss.

“The real battlefields are the Primary Plane, Astral Space, and the Heavens. This is not the first battlefield that is vital for us to invade…”

He glanced at the black ring on his hand that had already become slightly translucent without him knowing. These were the traces that were left behind after the Divine Weapon had finished silently absorbing the Soul Fragments in its surroundings.

Garen turned around and did not even turn his head before he walked towards the direction that he came from.

*************

Meanwhile, when Wanku Fortresses was breached by the Devils, Kratos led a group of Demons out and fled through the side door.

“Damn! This damned Garen should be executed and burned at the stake! He actually dared and was apparently brave enough to attack the encampment of another fortress that was part of the same alliance as himself!! Is he mad? Does he not want to get along with the rest of the Abyss or what?!!” Kratos cursed exasperatedly.

However, the expression on his face stiffened immediately.

Two imposing Half Elves with white cloaks draped over their bodies were currently in front of him and blocking his escape path.

“Lord Garen has been waiting for you for a long time, Kratos.” One of the Half Elves was playing with a short dagger that was glimmering with a dim light in his hand. The dagger resembled a fan that was spinning at high-speed while constantly flashing extremely difficult and magnificent slicing patterns.

“Get rid of them!” Kratos roared. His body enlarged suddenly from its shrunken state before he soared into the sky and shot himself into the distance to escape.

However, his subordinate Demons were smart enough to raise their hands and surrender.

They were merely Demons and were not any kind of loyal Slayers. None of them were willing to sacrifice their lives for a person who was doomed to die.

“Cherlyn.” The leading male Half Elf glanced at his companion.

The other one shook her head and took one step forward before taking down the longbow on her back.

She placed the arrow on the bow and pulled the bowstring.

Shh…

The bowstring tightened tautly immediately. It formed a full moon shape before delicate rings of green brilliant ripples were released from the body of the bow.

Hiss!

The arrow disappeared on the longbow instantly before collapsed in the faraway sky and fell downwards right at the sound of it as if it happened simultaneously.

“Let’s go. Take him back.” A look of admiration appeared on the male Half Elf’s face. “You’re becoming more proficient in Soul Intimidation.”

“I have a premonition that the refining in the Abyss this time is about to reach its goal already…” Cherlyn replied quietly.

“Are you going to break through already? Tch tch, you’re worthy of being a first-rate prodigy of the clan. You’re about to enter my realm within a short span of merely two hundred years… Level Thirteen…” The male Half Elf shook his head. “I don’t have anything good to say or to teach you anymore.”

Both of them led a crowd of surrendered Demons and walked towards the fallen Kratos immediately.

************************

Main Substance Plane

Northlands, Ten Thousand Woodlands.

Seemingly countless amounts of various wild animals and natural creatures were hidden all year long in the vast sea of trees in the woods that was located on the left side of Fiery Blaze Mountain Range. These gigantic woods that stretched over a continuous span of over ten thousand kilometers also concealed Half Elves, dwarfs, Dog-Headed Humans, Werewolves, and various other major tribes and races.

When the world’s first ray of sunlight streamed into the woods at daybreak, a gigantic tower that seemed to appear out of thin air was reflected there.

Sunlight cascaded on one side of the tower and reflected blue-gold shades off its blue material. Meanwhile, the other side looked peaceful and tranquil in the shadow of the sunlight.

It seemed that this tower had been standing upright in these woods for an unknown period of time.

A little rabbit with red eyes crawled out of its nest before suddenly sensing that something was blocking its daily warm sunlight.

It raised its head and glanced at the shadowy object before it seemed to turn dull abruptly.

The enormous tower before its eyes had clearly not been here yesterday.

It hopped around a few times and circled here and there while attempting to observe the tower from various angles. However, this colossal object did not change at all despite where the rabbit moved.

Chirp!!

The clear cry of an eagle echoed from the sky.

A little black dot flew towards the top of the tower from afar. It was a Roland Shadow Piercer, a legendary and extremely fast eagle species that could kill shadows.

It moved extremely quickly as if it wanted to fly towards the top of the tower and rest there for some time.

However, it seemed like some slight changes had occurred throughout the tower instantly.

A white ice ball that was suspended at the top of the tower was spinning there slowly.

Crack!!

It seemed like a white flash of lightning had streaked across.

The black eagle fell down at the sound of it.

It seemed as though nothing had happened. The tower was peaceful once again while the black eagle had not flown over at all.

The rabbit shivered fearfully before fleeing frantically.

A blurry large arched door appeared slowly at the bottom of the tower. Next, a young handsome white-haired youth walked out of the large door slowly before the same blurry door disappeared behind him instantly.

The youth was dressed in a white robe that seemed plain and simple while he held a short staff that was embedded with blue gemstones in his hand. A white-gold money bag was attached to his waist. From the looks of it, he did not seem much different from those traveling Wizards except that he was more aristocratic than them.

“The air in the Main Substance Plane…” The youth inhaled deeply before an infatuated look appeared on his face. “It’s truly fresher than the air in the Abyss…”

This youth was actually Garen who had recently grasped the Ultimate Transformation Spell. Many years had passed since he had arrived in this world and transformed into a dragon’s body. This was the first time that he was truly able to change over freely in the presence of any dragons.

After recently achieving Level Nine Arcane Arts, he was immediately able to grasp the spell that he had most desired to comprehend all along. He could perform various activities more freely when he was in his human form. After all, his dragon form was far too eye-catching.

His Wizard Tower had teleported with him and shifted to the Main Substance Plane. A large number of resources needed to be consumed for him to stabilize the space freely but Garen had accumulated a lot of it during these few years. Moreover, Lady Vengeance had also supported him with some strength that allowed him to be teleported back to the Northlands in the Main Substance Plane from the Abyss that was located at a faraway distance.

“Fiery Blaze Mountain Range, huh? It just so happens that I can go and see Snow City. Although they banished me to the Abyss previously, I received a helping hand from them nonetheless…” Thoughts stirred in Garen’s mind as he reconsidered. “However, White Dragon Mountain has been troublesome so I might as well get rid of them together.”

White Dragon Mountain’s headquarters were located on a certain level in the Abyss. They had received the protection of the Abyssal Demon Dragons race while the Evil Gods were overseeing that place. He did not have the skills to proceed with vengeance temporarily but he still possessed the strength to take revenge on the branches in the Main Substance Plane.

“I don’t know what has happened to the Deladia Empire, White Dragon Mountain, and Snow City after all these years.” Garen did not hear about the situation in the Deladia Empire all this while. Now that he had the strength to protect himself when he returned this time, he was gradually not going to restrain himself anymore.

“It just so happens to be near Ann’s location. It’s time for me to see her as well…”

Garen did not bring any of the Abyss’ troops out with him as Vengeance Fortress was the base camp that he was managing. Andrew was temporarily replacing him in power there while holding the position of Deputy Commander. After all, that place was richly endowed in advantages. Thus, merely abandoning it would not be in line with Garen’s interests.

Since Cold Winter Tower had already become Garen’s Wizard Tower fully, it could be used as an armed vehicle to envelop him when he proceeded with shuttling through the Plane. The energy for that was mainly provided by the Elemental Pond.

Garen scanned his surroundings briefly before walking slowly in the direction of the right side of Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

Within the woods, all of the creatures and animals along the way were dodging his aura automatically. Garen’s special Draconic Aura would release itself naturally and cause all of the wild creatures to evade his oncoming path unconsciously.

Despite the deceptive cover-up on his body that was specially added by Deception Demon Master which made it appear as if he only possessed a Level Twelve standard, he was still considered as an ultimate powerhouse in these woods because of this high degree.

Garen found it slightly strange at first before he suddenly recalled that this place was not like the Abyss that was filled with powerhouses. He shook his head and laughed in spite of himself suddenly when he remembered that it was the Main Substance Plane.

Garen hastened his speed. He stopped dragging his feet and charged fearlessly in the direction of Fiery Blaze Mountain Range directly.

Along the way, he encountered a few animals that did not dodge in time such as sika deer, little squirrels, spiders that were the size of washbasins, and white bears that were only as small as little chickens.

The strongest one was a gigantic squirrel with a white bone armor that grew over its entire body. This creature looked extremely fierce. Garen was unsure of this creature’s level but it was suppressed by his Draconic Aura to the point where it did not even dare to move.

Garen passed through a vast expanse of the woods quickly in less than half an hour before he approached the central region of the entire Ten Thousand Woodlands.

“My clan’s station is in front. Stranger, state your intentions for coming here!”

Suddenly, a loud male voice echoed from the front.

Garen’s footsteps stopped suddenly before he stood in the middle of the woods firmly.

Two Elves who wore light green leaf wreaths on their heads walked out of the shrubs in front of him slowly. It seemed as though the shrubs had spread open automatically as if it was a living creature to avoid stabbing or wounding the two Elves that looked unusually harmonious.

Garen’s gaze scanned across both of the Elves’ bodies briefly before he noticed that they were both female Elves. It was a normal phenomenon for there to be more females than males in the Elven race.

“Respected powerhouse, do you have an entry invitation upon coming to our tribe?” one of the Elves asked Garen quietly in a fearful and respectful tone.

They were clearly two interrogators that were sent by the powerhouses of the Elven tribe when they discovered the direction that Garen was traveling in beforehand.

Garen smiled faintly.

“I was just passing through. I had never expected that there would be an Elf tribe here as I was only traveling towards Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.”

“Fiery Blaze Mountain Range… Our tribe’s headquarters are in front and a powerful boundary was arranged there. How did you charge through directly…” said the other Elf softly while an embarrassed expression appeared on her face.

Garen’s nose twitched slightly suddenly before a trace of surprise appeared in his eyes.

“Do you have any connections with the nearby White Dragon Clan?”

“Yes, we have a business relationship with the clan over there. Their Elder often comes to our place here to purchase goods,” answered the Elf frantically.

“Is that so…” Garen’s expression turned milder. “I was also born there as part of the White Dragon Clan. Please help me notify them. I’m sure that you have a Teleportation Array here, right? Since I’ve already encountered them, I might as well return for a visit.”

“Do you have any proof of your identity?” asked the female Elf who did not lower her guard.

“You just need to go back and inform your Elder that I, Garen, have returned.” Garen was confident that the clan had not forgotten him completely in a short duration of a few decades.

This name was unexpectedly effective.

Within less than half a minute, a group of Advanced Elves that looked like Elites rushed out immediately and invited Garen inside.

The inside of the elven village was filled with houses and buildings that were harmoniously built with vines and enormous trees. There were buildings that were over ten stories tall which were supported by giant trees and also little houses that resembled cages which were solely formed by vines that grew naturally. He could not seem to see any signs of anything that was unnatural when he walked inside.

Garen was led into a remote bamboo house where an enormous old man whose hair and beard were completely light green was already waiting for him there.

Chapter 1352: Entrust 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The old man’s body was extremely enormous and he was over five full meters tall. He seemed like a normal old man who was enlarged. He wore a light green long Druid’s robe with the symbols of a golden moon and a silver star on top. He also had a white looped ear of wheat that represented his over Level Ten Great Druid status.

This Druid’s aura was concealed fairly well as Garen could not sense his exact level despite detecting it carefully.

He was at the very least a Level Ten being.

After both of them had sat down facing each other, the old man sized Garen up once before opening his mouth slowly.

“You don’t have to detect it anymore. I’m currently located in the village and all of my strength has fused with the village’s Protection Matrix as one. Thus, I’m the entire Matrix. This Matrix has Level Fifteen peak powers. Although my Spirit Power is insufficient to control such great forces, it can achieve roughly Level Fourteen when I bring it into play.”

He smiled.

“Moreover, are there any mere level differentiations that can clearly describe everything that happens in this world?”

“You have a point.” Garen nodded in admiration. He lifted the cup of dark green tea that was prepared before him and tipped it into his mouth gently before a sweetness and fragrance that resembled honey filled his mouth instantly. It was tinged with the scent of various flowers that made it impossible for people not to relax their bodies completely and be drunk in it.

“This is a rare honey that was made by collecting more than three thousand different types of flowers and pollen. The cup that you drank requires a year to be made,” explained the old Elf. “It just so happened that we could get rid of the intense Abyss aura on your body.”

Garen’s heart trembled.

“You’ve managed to tell.”

Indeed as the other party had said, it was completely impossible to fully distinguish between power levels simply by relying on level partitions. Situations where great reversals occurred at times among opponents with a few levels between them were not nonexistent. After all, forces were merely a form of strength but schemes, strategies, military tactics, pitfalls, and other things were also parts of strength.

“I’ve been good friends with the Third Elder of your clan for many years. Although that fellow is obsessed with ambition and desires to truly become independent and leave White Dragon Mountain so that the White Dragon Clan can develop greatly, your clan has steadily deteriorated these few years, especially after you were banished,” said the Elven Elder quietly.

“Was it due to a type of pressure or an enemy?” asked Garen quietly while raising his eyebrow.

“An enemy.” The Elder shook his head. “That’s right, you can call me Green Beard.”

“You can also simply address me as Garen,” said Garen politely.

“Alright, Garen.” Green Beard continued speaking, “During the Ten Thousand Dragon War five years ago when the Great Decisive Battle between the Deladia Empire and the Black Elves was ongoing, both sides threw in almost all of their own military forces. Numerous young adults who were in the prime of their lives were also thrown in by the White Dragon Clan naturally. The final outcome was…”

“They were defeated?” Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

“Yes, badly defeated.” Green Beard nodded while a hint of melancholy appeared on his face.

“Badly defeated… From what I know, the Empire’s forces should greatly surpass that of the Black Elves right?” said Garen in a puzzled manner.

“That’s a given. Emperor Gus has achieved up to Level Fifteen critical unnatural powers in more than one lifetime. He also brought the Divine Weapon called Reversed Misfortune Dragon Spear that was basically unstoppable,” Green Beard exhaled. “However, an unexpected variable has occurred.”

“Variable?”

“Void Crevices. Numerous Void Crevices have surged out from the rear before an abundance of Void Creatures charged out. The Empire’s troops were caught in the middle of a converging attack on both sides that resulted in a crushing defeat. One of the powerful creatures was even well-versed in our language. He called himself the Enchanted Hunting Demon Master. He was simply not an opponent that Emperor Gus could challenge. During the Ten Thousand Dragon War, he captured numerous members of the dragon race that had taken part in the war and slaughtered, devoured, and even enslaved them. Although it is unknown why he let off the part of the White Dragon Clan, the White Dragons fought fatally against the Black Elves because of the previous Ten Thousand Dragon War and suffered terrible casualties.”

“Demon Master?” Garen laughed bitterly. He had never expected that the White Dragon would be let off after he ran around in circles and returned to his own world. It appeared that this Enchanted Hunting Demon Master was aware of some inside information. Perhaps it was because he knew Deception Demon Master or that Garen’s Therapist reputation had spread far and wide. There could be other reasons behind this but in short, the other party had given him some face.

“It looks like you know some things.” Green Beard could keenly notice Garen’s differences.

“It’s fine. It would be better for me to return personally for a visit and witness it with my own eyes.” Garen stood up.

“That’s good as well. My Teleportation Array here leads directly to your clan. It’ll be good for you to return for a visit and ask them questions personally. Actually…” Green Beard was about to speak but he hesitated and did not open his mouth in the end.

Garen glanced at him.

“Thank you very much.”

“Don’t mention it. I hope that you can unify the current clan properly.” Green Beard shook his head.

Garen left the bamboo house and walked in the direction of the Teleportation Array while being led there by a male Elf.

Along the way, there were numerous Elves around him that ran over to look at him. There were old and young men and women who watched him with friendly gazes. It appeared that the White Dragon Clan had previously left a pretty good impression on them.

Garen had even encountered a little group of human adventurers who were invited inside to drink tea. These people were strictly monitored as if they were prisoners. When they saw that Garen was receiving special treatment that was worlds apart from their own, this group of people clearly thought that it was unfair.

Garen stood on the Teleportation Array before a hazy layer of green light flashed and covered every part of his entire body.

The vast stretch of green flowed before his eyes before the green shades dispersed after sustaining for a few short seconds. A pure white ice wall now appeared before his eyes. He was currently located inside a crevasse that was not very big while an Elder White Dragon that seemed crippled was guarding it on the side. He opened his dragon eyes that were dim-sighted from old age and looked at Garen carefully.

“You are?” Since only the creatures that were approved by the Elven Elder could arrive here through the Teleportation Array, he did not display any malicious intentions.

“The clan has already reached this extent?” Garen did not answer his question but looked at him in a stunned manner instead.

They had actually sent a crippled Elder White Dragon to guard such an important Teleportation Array.

He released a hint of Draconic Aura lightly before that specialized Draconic Aura made the Elder White Dragon’s entire body tremble suddenly.

“I’m Garen.”

Garen’s voice echoed slowly.

The Elder White Dragon had yet to react before he saw Garen disappear instantly. Only a fragmented shadow that vanished slowly remained on the original spot.

****************

The whooshing sound of wind swept past the side of Garen’s ear and reverberated there.

He had transformed into his dragon body already and was looking down at the original White Dragon Clan below him. Numerous weak White Dragons had formed patrol groups that were flying around the snowy peaks while the Dragon Whelps were currently wailing while being trained by their instructors in the middle of the snowy peak.

Several slightly muscular Adult Dragons were about to fly out now. When it seemed as though they had noticed this White Dragon that they had never seen before, they turned around and flew towards him immediately.

“You are…” One White Dragon could vaguely see a blurry but familiar appearance.

“Garen??!!” he yelled suddenly. “You’re Garen?!!”

His voice reverberated throughout the entire White Dragon Snow Peak suddenly before numerous drawn-out echoes surged out.

White Dragon Snow Peak was completely silent at first before it flared up instantly soon after that. A mere duration of a few short decades was not a long time to the White Dragons. Hence, it seemed as though Garen had only left for a short while.

Numerous White Dragons that were still here flew out one after another before encircling Garen’s body in the air.

While he was suspended in mid-air, only ten Adult White Dragons remained among the White Dragons that were circling around him while the rest were all Elder Dragons and Dragon Whelps. Moreover, these Adult Dragons had only recently matured not long ago.

The entire clan had truly weakened to this extent.

“Garen, you’ve finally returned! There’s hope for the clan now!”

“You’re the clan’s last hope! The Elders, all the Elders have…” wept one of the Young Dragons softly who was a Dragon Whelp previously.

After all, the Dragons who had grown up in the clan were still very sentimental towards the clan.

Meanwhile, most of the Adult White Dragons who had formed at the last moment had already died in battle.

Garen scanned his surroundings but did not see many familiar faces unexpectedly.

“Where are Satwo, Sathree, and Safour?” he asked quietly.

“Big Brother Garen!”

Several Dragon Whelps flew over while the surrounding White Dragon left some space for them. It was really Satwo and the others.

They had grown bigger and looked more mature. Perhaps they would become Young Dragons after more time had passed.

“You’ve finally returned.” A feeble voice echoed out of the exterior of the dragon herd suddenly.

The White Dragons become silent suddenly and made way for a passage.

An Elder Dragon whose entire body was wrinkled because of age flew inside slowly.

Although he was so old, Garen was still able to vaguely recognize his identity.

“Third Elder…” He had never thought that this Level Nine powerhouse would age like this within a short span of twenty to thirty years. He could see that Third Elder was not far from death anymore… His lifespan was almost exhausted and he was already walking towards the end.

Third Elder was still holding Tiamat’s staff in his hands. It represented the dignity of the Gods but it was currently dim and lusterless now.

“It’s good that you’ve returned…” Third Elder looked at Garen. He used his gaze to entrust something complicated to him but there was also a deep gladness tinged there.

“My only aspiration, dream, and desire was to establish a clan where White Dragons could live peacefully… They objected in the beginning and imprisoned me but now that my energy is almost exhausted, it’s unfortunate that I may not be able to see this dream anymore…” said Third Elder in a quivering voice. “Since Reyman has defected, our only hope is you…”

He reached his claw out and passed the staff to Garen.

“I was waiting for you all along… The prophecy told me that you would surely return.”

Garen did not take the staff but stared at Third Elder instead. He had already started to release a deathly aura from his soul now. That was the disastrous effect that was caused by exhausting his soul excessively. It appeared that he had released a certain type of great energy that was enough to wreck his soul during the previous war.

Despite everything, he actually had a faint feeling when he was previously in the clan that Reyman was perhaps the Child of the General Trends and the center that all fate revolved around.

He would inevitably leave the clan. However, he did not show any intentions of returning even when the clan was so weak.

“Are you… unwilling?” Third Elder laughed bitterly. “That’s true, it’ll be easy for me once I leave but you’ll be forced to take over this awful mess… I’m asking for too much… I…”

“I’m declining the Divine Staff only to represent that I’m not accepting Tiamat’s faith,” said Garen in a low voice.

He reached his hand out suddenly and grabbed the staff.

Pop!

He squeezed the crystal ball on the top of the staff that represented Tiamat and crushed it.

“I am me and Tiamat is Tiamat.” Garen glanced at Third Elder’s shocked expression and the surrounding crowd of White Dragons that were absolutely silent.

Garen lifted the staff suddenly within the White Dragon Clan that had nowhere to go at this moment.

“From this day onwards, I’m the Leader of the clan. Does anyone have any objections?”

No one made any noise. The White Dragons who were slightly stronger had left and abandoned this clan already.

The sound of the snowstorm was the only thing that could be heard at this time.

**********

In the underground part of a certain abandoned church in the center of a faraway empire at the same time.

A deep black silhouette burrowed out from underground and seeped into Reyman’s mouth, eyes, ears, and nose slowly.

Reyman’s dragon body shook violently while contorted, pained, and resigned looks flashed across his eyes. Nonetheless, he persevered determinedly from beginning to the end.

“Only by complying with the ancient will… can your final wish come true…” Numerous noises narrated in his mind in various languages.

Reyman’s dragon body was currently turning black quickly at a speed that could be seen with the naked eye. It was not the black shade of Black Dragons but another kind of black that did not have a single trace of luster.

The fate of the world gradually induced different trustees.

Meanwhile, several black figures were madly invading the bodies of various beings in more than ten other places.

Similarly, several True Soul Demon Masters were stepping out gradually in various Void Crevices in the world before invisible and transparent Forces of Cause and Effect entangled and gathered around their bodies slowly.

Chapter 1353: Reunion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Reyman’s eyes lost both of its pupils, leaving behind two distant eyes looking like black holes.

A chaotic aura of rage, scheming and bloodlust burst from his body.

In this small underground space, countless blurry spots of black light suddenly appeared, rotating around him like flying insects.

“I… I’m Reyman… Reyman…!!” The White Dragon struggled, trying to bellow out loud.

However, the blurry and distorted silhouette within his consciousness started laughing maniacally.

“No… I am Nimitras… The Child of Hell… Hahaha!!!” Another low voice suddenly burst out from his mouth.

Reyman’s entire dragon body started to exude a strong and evil red halo. His body suddenly expanded a lot as black whips and ropes slowly emerged behind him. These long strip-like items kept fading in and out of existence, almost as if they were snakes weaving and climbing around, burrowing into the darkness, and coming out of the shadows.

“Let’s go, let us punish those invaders of the Void…” Reyman seemed to have finally calmed down, grinning with a sly smile.

Rip.

He tore open a black crevice directly in front of him, revealing a scene from the Shadow Plane. The grayish plane had many Shadow Creatures and alien creatures fighting with each other.

The portal that Reyman opened seemed to coincidentally be in the center of a small battlefield.

He rushed in without any hesitation. Very quickly, screams of pain and sufferings could be heard.

******

It has been five days since he returned to the clan.

Garen was perched atop the new Dragon King Peak. This snowy peak was officially named by him to be Dragon King Peak, blatantly implying that he has no intention of giving in to the White Dragon Mountain.

Garen reviewed the whole situation with the White Dragon Clan.

Fifteen Mature Dragons, more than eighty Dragon Whelps, and more than twenty Elder Dragons, whereas all the Young Dragons fell in battle. Only a handful of them who were living abroad under a Symbiotic Contract managed to survive.

This was the current situation of the clan. As for the Third Elder and the other higher-ups, almost all of them had already exhausted their Life Soul. They had completely used up all they had after transferring all their powers to Garen, naturally dying in their own caves.

The Deladia Empire had already lost. The once glorious and powerful empire had rapidly fallen as Emperor Gus went missing in action in the Ten Thousand Dragon War.

Even the chances of their own survival had come into question, they could not spare any effort taking care of this weak White Dragon Clan.

Snow City had also lost two of their council powerhouses. The remaining wizards also incurred fatal injuries. In this destructive war, the biggest winners were no doubt the Void Creatures. No matter the Black Elf Empire or the Deladia Empire, they had both suffered an unprecedented amount of losses.

Garen did not make any extra arrangements. The clan’s food supply was already running out, he had to transport some of the food over from the Cold Winter Tower. The Cold Winter Tower had food reserves sufficient for the clan to survive for more than ten years, all stored in the space equipment’s vacuum.

Garen initially planned to use the ration in dire situations as emergencies, such as if the Wizard Tower got trapped in a space storm. Little did he expect that he would have to use it now.

No matter what, the Clan did help him back then when he was still weak and small.

Swiftly, he gathered all the White Dragons who could still participate in combat. The Void Original Opus had once again gotten new upgrades. Using the Despair Skull and the Death Bracelet, he absorbed potential aura and souls to further upgrade the Original Opus.

The key to it all, the strongest epitome of all Secret Techniques, had finally returned to him.

Hellfrost Peacock Queen!

It was Garen’s strongest state back when he was in the Mech World.

He had already reached an even stronger degree than the original Hellfrost Peacock Queen.

Furthermore, with the Void Original Opus fully upgraded to 100%, this absurdly strong Secret Technique had finally returned to its original power.

Disregarding the series of frost abilities it gave, the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s Low-Temperature Winter ability had a lot of overlaps with the White Dragon’s traits, so its power was near equal. Thus, it did not increase Garen’s power by a lot, it at most added the Cold Chaos skill, allowing him to cause mental confusion.

However, the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s most important ability was the key factor for Garen’s strength.

Distorted Seed!

Distorted Seed 5 (Creating chaos was one of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s favorite past times. Stat increment raised to 12 times. Aberrations produced a pollution effect, objects that are polluted will automatically aberrate into a next-level distorted object, its stats increasing by 12 times. If the increment reached the upper limit, it would automatically stop.)

This was the key effect Garen would be relying on.

Garen managed to collect a large amount of food and Demon Cores without a hitch. Directly using the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s Devourer ability, he condensed all of it into tiny Distorted Seeds, planting them on the fifteen White Dragons over here.

The effect of the Distorted Seeds had a huge effect on the humans, but that was because a human’s body foundations were too weak. For the White Dragons who were from the Dragon Clan, their actual foundation was very strong, the strengthening effect most likely would not be able to reach a 12-times multiplier.

This was not out of Garen’s calculations, the White Dragons’ with the seeds planted on them had only doubled their overall attributes. However, just with that, it was already absurdly terrifying.

An average mature White Dragon’s attributes would usually range between forty points to thirty points and were classified as a Level Six Creature, However, after the seed was planted, their attributes just skyrocketed, reaching sixty to eighty points.

At the end of the day, the strengthening of the Distorted Seed also had its limit. Otherwise, if it could strengthen beings like deities by over 12 times, then they would be able to easily increase a level of their Divine Persona.

The upper limit of the Distorted Seed used the Hellfrost Peacock Queen as a benchmark, the upper limit of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s strongest physical body would be equivalent to the maximum point the Distorted Seed’s Strengthening could reach. Furthermore, this type of pure strengthening was also limited by the restraints of certain rules. A White Dragon’s blood vessels cannot be upgraded too much before its body evolved, otherwise, their body might not be able to withstand the burden.

That said, however, these fifteen White Dragons were already upgraded to Level Nine creatures. With the entire clan in mind, this was already absurd.

They went from Level Six to Level Nine in just one day.

Garen’s prestige shot up instantly.

There were now fifteen Level Nine White Dragons patrolling the area. Although they were mostly melee-type warriors, with Garen’s personal Arcane Art Protection, Dimensional Confinement and other measures, no matter if it’s a teleportation spell, projection spell, or even a real-life attack, nothing could bother him.

In addition, he was trying his best to use the Divine Weapon of Absorption, the Death Bracelet to absorb the shards of souls.

On the battlefield, there were too many shards that he managed to collect. Even if Garen had the willpower of his mind to help, he could only slowly digest all of it.

However, this peaceful life could not be maintained much longer. In such a chaotic era, Garen still made time to visit the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range. He had to meet Ann one more time.

******

At the bottom of a dark abyss

An average-sized White Dragon slowly headed to the bottom of the abyss. His movements slow but sharp. He was completely surrounded by countless, smoky black, human-faces in the abyss, all rotating around him, but none dared to approach him. It was almost as if this dragon’s body had something that they had feared.

It had been a long time since he was last at this place. But because the necklace that Ann gave him had been destroyed, Garen spent a lot of effort to find that weird snow typhoon and to once again return to this place.

As he nosedived into complete darkness, Garen could soon see a blurry seal at the bottom of the abyss.

Ann was seated at the side of the light ball seal, conversing with a creature completely engulfed in flames.

As if sensing Garen’s, the flame creature looked up at him.

A chill went down Garen’s spine. He felt tremendous stress with just a gaze from the creature.

“Demigod?” He guessed in his head.

“Garen, come down here,” Ann turned her head and waved at Garen.

Suddenly, a huge distorted space enveloped Garen, then immediately teleporting him to Ann’s side and the flame creature.

Ann was still very beautiful. Her black skirt seemed to have a lot of new patterns, he was not sure if it was her old one or did she get a new one. It was still mysterious and flawless.

“He’s the Demigod Lich Gawain. The two of you had some misunderstandings in the past, but it’s still not too late to bury the hatchet,” Ann said briefly.

Demigod Lich?!

Garen immediately became cautious of this fellow. Even an average Lich was troublesome enough to deal with, if you could not find their Phylacteries, they could never be killed.

To make things worse, this was a Demigod Lich. That means that this fellow could easily summon a million-strong undead army at any moment. These types of fearsome fellows were existences that could eradicate an entire nation with a flick of a finger.

Looks like the Void invasion had even caused all the powerhouses in hiding all over the world to come out and take action.

Suddenly a thought crossed his mind. Garen gave a friendly smile to the Lich and turned into his human form.

“His Highness Garen and my student had a scuffle previously due to a misunderstanding. However, since Ann came forward as a mediator between us, I hope we can let bygones be by bygones and create a friendly relationship.” The Lich’s body was still engulfed in flames, his attitude towards Garen seemed very friendly.

“Your student?” Garen said with a slightly confused look.

“Yes, he was living in seclusion back at the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range and had a few Suffering Knights as his underlings,” the Demigod Lich Gawain answered softly.

“Oh, it was him!” Garen suddenly remembered. The Suffering Knights that Garen killed at the beginning was the underling of this fellow’s student.

Seemed like this fellow was convinced by his student to take revenge personally. But after barging in and noticing that Ann was a powerful existence with a Middle-Level Divine Soul, he naturally decided to obediently make peace with Garen.

“A few years ago, I have officially pledged my loyalty to Her Excellency Ann, so I’m on the same side as you now.” The Demigod Lich laughed as he answered. Through the flames, Garen could vaguely make out the appearance of a handsome young man.

“Garen, the timing of your return is perfect. I’m going to need you to help me send a letter.” Ann said softly by the side.

“What letter?”

“How many Demon Lords and True Souls are you able to contact?” Ann bluntly revealed Garen’s background without hesitation.

However, Garen was already at the stage where he did not mind. As long as Ann was still around, he would not have to be afraid of any of the remaining Gods looking for him.

He thought for a while.

“I should be able to contact the three Demon Lords nearby.”

“Alright. I need to settle some slightly troublesome stuff, so the more helpers I can get the better. Of course, you can also participate. I see that your body has been through some sort of unknown change, maybe that might be of help to me,” Ann said solemnly. “You can tell those Demon Lords and True Souls that I’m willing to pay them any reward they deem appropriate, as long as they help me with one task.”

“What task? Count me in if you need my help,” Garen answered seriously. What type of task would require Demon Lord and True Soul Level participants? Demon Lords were already Divine Soul Level, it’s only the difference in strength.

Ann smiled gently. She knew that she was right about Garen back then. For an existence with this type of personality, she was right when she decided to help him back then. To an existence like Garen, as long as someone helped him in the past, he would always remember the gratitude they showed to him. From then on, he would not hesitate when they need his help.

She slowly raised her hands. A blurry black mist suddenly enveloped the three.

“Have you heard of the God of Time and Shadows?”

Chapter 1354: Reunion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s expression tensed.

The God of Time and Shadow. This fellow was an Ancient God. He was not one of the members of the many Pantheons who currently appeared in the eyes of mortals.

This was an existence who could control time, he was one of the most ancient Divine Souls in existence. Even the oldest Earth Mother could only at most level with him.

He was also the most secretive, rarely showing himself. Even when Miss Shar took over the Shadows, a part of his Divine Domain, he did not express any dissatisfaction, freely allowing his followers and priest to slip away.

“The Grey Shadow Society up north is actually the actual location of his church.” Ann continued, “the main goal of him creating the Shadow Council was actually to find my whereabouts.”

“If that’s the case, the rumor is true?” The Demigod Lich Gawain frowned.

“Yes, even though I’m sealed but they still could not find a way to effectively finish me off. Not even the pulling force of the Astral Space could harm me,” Ann explained calmly. “After so many years, The God of Time and Shadow Flame Elemental Thane has been searching for a way to kill me but to no avail. Five hundred years ago, I found an opportunity to directly strip off this entire sealing ground into the crevice with unlimited plane movement, allowing me to flow through the space tunnel. This would completely make them lose my tracks. After so many years of being sealed, it’s time for some payback…”

Gawain’s mouth felt dry. He was engulfed in flames, but he started to feel a slight sense of unease.

“Your goal, it can’t be to…”

“Your guess is correct…” Ann smiled slyly. “It’s time to take back what’s mine… all the Gods now are all in a mess, there’s no better time to strike.”

Garen shivered, Ann’s intentions were clear.

Slaying the Gods!

Slaying Divine Souls with the same Divine Domain as her.

Shadow and Time, Ann’s abilities were also in this aspect. Looks like the other Gods had specifically found a specialist Divine Soul to monitor the seal.

The God of Time and Shadow was someone with an Upper-Middle Level Divine Power. Although Ann had Middle-Level Divine Power, the two operated based on different concepts. After all, Ann had been sealed for so many years, she was excessively weak right now, otherwise, she would not have asked for the aid of the Demon Lords and True Souls.

“I’ll go back and try to get into contact with even more Demon Lords and True Souls,” Garen said after thinking briefly. “Of course, you don’t have to worry, I won’t just leak this plan out to anyone.”

“That’s fine,” Ann nodded satisfactorily. “Garen, you truly have great potential. Within such a short time, your growth rate is so fast that it had even far surpassed that of the Void Creatures. You already have enough power to threaten a Demigod, maybe in a bit more, I wouldn’t even be able to see-through you anymore.”

What she meant by see-through was that if Garen truly entered the Demigod Territory and formed his own territory, although Demigods were still far from achieving the Middle-Level Divine Power, they were still beings on the same level. Thus, she would no longer be able to see-through Garen completely with her natural inspection ability.

After hearing this evaluation, the Demigod Lich at the side looked at Garen intently, reevaluating him again. He was initially friendly to Garen because Ann told him to.

Garen did not care much. If Ann wanted to slay the Gods, this was quite frightening news. He was still a long way from reaching the Divine Soul. Being able to threaten a Demigod does not mean that he could threaten the Divine Souls at the Divine Kingdom. An analogy for this would be that you might be able to stab a person in front of you to death with a knife, but it would not be that easy if your target was a country’s President, even though a President was still an average human…

“Alright, you can leave first.” Ann noticed that Garen looked like he had something to say to her. Hence, she decided to shoo off Gawain for now.

As soon as Gawain’s ball of fire teleported away, Garen heaved a long sigh of relief.

He started to talk about his developments in the Abyss and the problems he faced.

Ann listened to his rants attentively.

“An Evil God?” After Garen finished, she pondered for a moment. “I don’t have a lot of enemies within the Abyss, but Big Mistress is considered one of them. Looks like she’s taking action…well, there’s no rush now after I succeed in my plans, I will personally go talk to her…” Her eyes suddenly filled with a sense of bloodlust.

Casting a glance at Garen, she casually asked.

“You’re also considered one of my pseudo-disciples. The Divine Weapon on hand is something someone else gave you, right? Don’t you need stronger souls? What’s the strongest soul you can absorb right now?”

Garen was at first surprised by her words but then felt delighted. According to his calculations, there was no limit on the number of strongest souls he could absorb right now, but if there were no new inspirations, it would not be able to condense the Soul Seeds and Soul Rings, only turning them into backup Potential Points. He currently already had a lot of Potential Points, there was basically no way for him to use up all of it. What he was lacking right now were Soul Rings that could raise his Soul Limit. No matter if it’s condensing True Souls or increasing the attributes, what he lacked was Soul Rings.

“As long as it’s not a Demigod, I should be able to absorb it!” Garen answered directly. “However, the best-case scenario would be to absorb the soul of a territorial master with special inspirations. The level of power is not that important.”

Excluding Divine Souls, there was no one who could compare to Ann’s kill count.

“Master-level souls with special inspirations?” Ann frowned slightly. “I don’t have too many of these types of souls, Major Gods, and the other Magic Gods and Evil Gosa all like these kinds of souls. These types of souls are Holy Souls and can be transformed into incarnations of Gods, it’s far different from other souls.”

She hesitated briefly before waving her hand.

Suddenly, a puff a grey mist appeared in front of Garen.

“These are two souls from masters of construction. They’re the only ones I’ve preserved, the others I had already used as bartering resources.”

Garen was in joy. He directly accepted the two souls with his Death Bracelet.

“Thank you, teacher!” He was once again reassured of his relationship with Ann.

Truly, without Ann’s help in the beginning, he would have been completely annihilated by the Suffering Knights back when he first set foot here. He also learned countless things from her later on, hence having this sort of relationship with her was nothing much.

Ann also did not reject this sort of relationship. She only casually nodded her head and waved her hand again. Garen immediately disappeared from the bottom of this abyss.

When he reappeared, he was already in the sky of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

“Oh right, I accidentally caught a Void Creature earlier. Her body seemed to somehow have an aura related to you. So, I decided not to eat her. I’ll let you investigate more for now.”

As Garen was preparing to set the transport spell back to the Dragon King Mountain, Ann’s voice suddenly transmitted over.

Without any time for him to react, he saw a black hole appear in the sky. Then, suddenly a small black cage was flung out of the black hole and fell into his hands.

The cage had a few small silhouettes in them.

One of them was a young girl in an earth-style mini-skirt. This girl had a head of waist-length black hair. She wore a super short pleated skirt, her face looked as delicate as a doll. She was sleeping soundly inside the cage.

The other two were a male with blood-red hair, down to even his eyebrows and beard; and a girl with long blue hair, and non-human eyes like embedded gems.

“Na… Nadia?!” Garen involuntarily reminisced of the Nine-Headed Dragon King he encountered back in the Blood Breed World.

After a few more looks at the beautiful young girl in the cage, he confirmed that she gave off the same impression as when he first saw Nadia. If not for him acquiring the Holy Phoenix Scriptures at the end, he most likely would not be able to deal with Nadia’s projection back then.

“Is that a Demon King? A Demon King Level Existence?” The other two were still awake as they seemingly made out Garen’s identity.

“Your Respected Excellency, although we were once pursuers, now that the Void has been unified, there are no longer any factions. We will pledge our lives to serve you, Your Excellency!”

The man loudly begged. He seemed to sense Garen’s identity as a Void Pursuer, his face suddenly revealing a joyous expression.

“Are you guys Void Pursuers?” Garen asked softly in the Ancient Endor language.

“Yes, my name is Rosta, she is my companion Elphis. This one here is one of our targets in the past the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia. However, now…” The man Rosta laughed bitterly. This former great enemy was nothing more than an ant in the hands of the powerful creatures of this world.

They were the last remnants of the Ancient Endorian Civilization. They had always fought at the frontlines to secure and protect Ancient Endor’s legacy. They had almost ended the Warlock’s legacy completely, but they did not expect the Mother Stream’s power to suddenly increase and pulled out a large number of True Soul Imprints that were almost fading away and ejected them with power. Within a brief moment, countless True Souls surged into the Mother Stream, the Warlock’s Civilizations seemed to have returned to its golden era. Their mission had then came to an end.

Originally, they thought that Ancient Endor and the Void would once again have a massive war, but no one expected that both parties united and formed the two organizations, Void Temple and Mother Stream Alliance, joining forces to invade an extremely huge world.

After being captured by a Void Demon King, they were forced to be shot into this world as a test shot, without any hopes of returning alive but miraculously they survived.

“Nadia… She’s actually the Nine-Headed Dragon King, huh?” Garen smiled. After coming to this world for such a long time, he had finally seen someone who had fallen as much as him from the start.

In the beginning, the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia did bully him a lot.

Now, looking at the Nadia inside the cage, Garen could not help but let out a grin filled with bad intentions.

From his point of view, although Nadia’s power was excessively strong, with his current physique she was nothing more than an ant. It was like the difference between an Army Level with a Demon King Level, especially in terms of resistance. A Demon King would be able to resist most special abilities an Army Level threw at him, but an Army Level would not be able to defend against the various special abilities of a Demon King Level. The two also had ordered soul suppression. When facing off, their attributes would be suppressed to a certain level.

With Garen’s current Demon King Level, to defeat Nadia, just the ordered suppression would be enough to suppress most of her abilities to the original degree of the most basic Army Level.

In other words, the Garen now just had to purely rely on the attack based on the natural law of physics to completely crush her like an ant.

“Understood, I didn’t think I would get a bonus reward this time around.” Garen kept the cage and with a slash with both of his arms, he ripped open the space in front of him. Walking in, he arrived inside his Cold Winter Tower.

The Cold Winter Tower had already been transported over to the Dragon King Mountain. This type of top-level Wizard Tower was almost like a battleship fortress, it could move freely through space. However, the number of resources needed was slightly high. But to Garen, there was nothing money could not solve!

Chapter 1355: Tiamat 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After Garen became the Clan Leader of the White Dragon Clan, they officially renamed themselves the Cold Winter Dragon Clan, escaping from the White Dragon Mountain.

The main substance plane of the White Dragon Mountain was enraged as he sent out teams to capture them back. However, Garen was perched within his own territory, easily absorbing the two Master-Level souls. Unsurprisingly, the two Master-Level souls had been turned to shards and eaten as oatmeal by Garen. After absorbing a majority of the memories, within two days, he had condensed two new Soul Seeds.

The eighth Soul Ring had also officially started to condense together.

The more the Soul Ring progressed, its progress rate became increasingly slower. The Despair Skull and the Death Bracelet worked very well together, one absorbing the Potential Points whilst the other managed the discoveries from the shards. Garen started to ponder, should he take the initiative and search for the souls he needed…

After all, he was a Dragon of Disaster and not just a simple White Dragon King.

After hearing that the White Dragon Mountain sent a team, Garen was suddenly more interested.

******

“What? Clan Leader, you’re personally entering the fray?” The newly appointed White Dragon guard leader Annie screamed out loud.

“Why are you so shocked?” Garen lazed on top of the Ice Sculpture throne, looking down at Annie and the group of White Dragons with shocked expressions.

“White Dragon Mountain sent a team here specifically targeting me, so I won’t bother showing them any mercy.”

“But…” Annie wanted to say something, but Garen raised his arm stopping her.

Ever since Garen was able to transform into a human form, he had always stayed as such. Now he sat on top of the throne, surveying the scene below him.

“I’ll leave the clan matters to you guys to deal with. If there are any emergencies, you can break the crystal rock outside my cave, I’ll get notified immediately.” Garen was not one to be tied down in one place by a clan. It was a chaotic period right now, with Void Creatures and various major planes waging war against each other. Just as the world order descended to its most chaotic era, this was the perfect opportunity for him to hunt for more soul shards.

Since he confirmed that souls with high inspiration could help him condense Soul Seeds and Soul Rings, then it looked like the Deception Demon Master’s method was definitely very useful.

Garen shifted his thoughts. He suddenly understood why so many Demon Masters and True Souls started to massacre everyone as soon as they arrived. As it turned out, the Enneahedron was not the sole factor behind it. Since he was already so far behind the other Demon Lords and Demon Masters, it just was not right for him to continue slacking off like this.

“The coverage from the Cold Winter Tower can protect the entire Dragon King Mountain. I had already set up the appropriate spells, temporarily casting Maze on the surrounding areas.” Garen waved his hand and tossed out a few silver-white seeds, dropping them into each one of the present White Dragons’ hands.

“This is my specially made Increment Seeds, you guys can decide whether you want to use it or not. After using it, you will be able to raise your overall physical fitness, but in turn, you’ll never be able to disobey me. The choice is yours.”

Garen looked at the few White Dragons who opened their mouth seemingly wanting to say something. Not wanting to be bothered with it, he used a teleportation spell and immediately disappeared from the throne.

He had already given out more than a hundred of these Distortion Seeds. The first batch was mainly used on the strongest White Dragon Annie and the other demons in the fortress that came from the Abyss. This type of Distorted Seed cannot control their will, but it was enough to force them to never have any ill-intent towards their Parental Garen. It also ensured that their lives were linked to Garen, so if Garen were to die, they would die as well.

After spreading the Distorted Seeds, Garen teleported straight back to the Cold Winter Tower.

Nadia was still unconscious in the tower. On the other hand, Rosta and Elphis had already been released by Garen, but they were restrained within the confines of the tower, not able to leave.

Garen teleported straight to the floor they were at.

The two were eating their lunch. Seeing Garen’s silhouette appearing from the teleportation spell, they immediately stood up.

“Lord Garen,” Rosta was the first to speak.

“What are your plans? Are you two going to leave this place, or stay?” Garen asked casually, sitting down beside the two.

His interest toward these two Void Pursuers was not that big. Their levels were around Level Eight or Nine at best in this world’s standards. He already had a lot of underlings that were at that level.

“We’ve already pledged our allegiance to you, sir, we will not go back on our words,” Rosta answered hurriedly. “Furthermore, since we just came to this world, there is no place we could safely call home, it’s only a matter of time before something happens to us if we leave,” he laughed bitterly.

Elphis who was standing beside him nodded in agreement.

“Originally, we were pursuing the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia, but now… her strength is barely comparable to that of a baby’s, then what’s the meaning behind in pursuing her?” Elphis said calmly, seemingly already seeing past that. “Ancient Endor’s descendants no longer require our protection. With the reappearance of True Souls, our presence is no longer necessary.”

Garen sighed as he tossed out two Distorted Seeds.

“Eat these, it’ll increase your strength. After that, go check out the library on the second floor, it has books on general knowledge. I’ll remove your restraints. As for what comes after, you guys can fight on in this world to grow and evolve. Go ask the snail for more specific details.”

With a wave of his hands, some pen and paper floated over from a short distance away. He picked up the pen and wrote down an address. It was not just any address, but rather a special Dream World address that only Void Creatures and the Ancient Endorians could understand.

“You can contact him through the Dream World, he will tell you guys all about this world and what you need to take note of.”

“Thank you, Lord!”

The two immediately bowed down in gratitude. Garen then vanished, leaving the two in the room looking at the Distorted Seed in their hands, smiling bitterly at each other.

This was obviously something he was using to prevent them from betraying him.

When Garen reappeared, he was now in the isolation room on the fifth floor.

This floor was mainly used for medical purposes. There were countless medical facilities, spells, books, and facilities, neatly placed inside this entire room.

Nadia was sleeping in one of the wards. She seemed to have woken up, staring blankly at the sunlight outside the window.

Click.

Garen opened the door and walked in.

“How’s your recovery going?” Garen grinned from ear to ear as he walked in, looking at the beautiful girl on the ward bed. She had glossy black, waist-length hair and porcelain white fair skin. Nadia was silently leaning back on the ward bed. The moment she turned around and saw Garen, her eyes widened.

“It’s you!!”

She shouted out in shock.

“That’s right, it’s me,” Garen walked over and sat next to her, still grinning.

“Looks like you’re doing well…” He raised his hand and gently caressed Nadia’s cheek.

“What are you doing?!” Nadia suddenly shouted angrily. “Don’t think just because you saved me you can…” She could not think of a word to describe Garen’s action in the heat of the moment.

“Can what?” Garen dodged her slap, his hand almost as if it had not even moved an inch, once again appearing at the same place. He lightly pinched Nadia’s soft cheeks.

“You are now my captive, so how about it? Do you want to beg me to set you free?!” He chuckled haughtily.

“In your dreams!!” Nadia wanted to create a weapon, but she noticed that her entire body was sore and she could barely move a muscle. Her face paled.

“Garen!!!” Her jet black eyes looked as if it was ready to spit fire. “To think that I had admired you a bit back in the day!!”

“Admired?” Garen forcefully pulled her into his arms, the two were now literally inches away from each others’ faces. “You once beat me up multiple times!!”

His burning aura seemed to be hitting Nadia’s face, causing her to turn her head away unnaturally.

“If it was not for that thing, do you think you can manage to suppress me?!!” She shouted loudly, seemingly very flustered. “Then kill me if you can!!”

“Kill you?” Garen seldom had the chance to meet with such a fun old friend, how would he even dream of letting her off so easily. “Why should I kill you? We’re both old companions, I would gain nothing from killing you.” He let go of Nadia, letting her fall back onto the bed.

“You bullied me so much back then, now the tides have turned, so now it’s my turn to bully you,” Garen joked, obviously in a great mood.

“Wait till I recover, then you’ll definitely be dead!!” Nadia’s rage was at her limit. She was grasping the pure white ward bed blanket tightly as she glared at Garen. The aura behind her even started to condense into the black silhouette of the Nine-Headed Dragon, but this type of void aura suppression was nothing but child’s play to Garen’s current physique.

“Alright alright, stop being naughty. Rest your body properly, you can use this entire floor as you please.” Garen came over to tease Nadia to relax his mood. Just as he expected, his mood turned better, and Nadia’s turned worse.

He was building his joy upon other’s sufferings.

Garen suddenly realized how evil he was.

Fondling his chin, he noticed that no matter how he looked at it, Nadia did not seem antagonized in his eyes anymore. Maybe it was because it was such a rare situation for him to meet a familiar enemy in a foreign new world. Although the two had a complicated relationship, where it was hard to even differentiate between friend and foe, at the end of the day, the sense of familiarity still existed.

After leaving the Cold Winter Tower, the plan that he had specifically crafted in the beginning will finally be initiated. Ever since he heard of the Deception Demon Master’s methods, Garen started to have an insane plan. Within the next ten or so years, if he did not manage to get enough power to defend himself in this short period of time, once a huge war broke out, in the war between True Souls and Demon Masters, and Gods, in the midst of all the chaos in the Holy War, those who were not at the level of a God would be no different than ants.

Garen was not overly ambitious and only hoped that he would be able to make it through that huge war in one piece.

However, this was also quite an ambitious dream. Up till now, he had only been in one fatal battle.

After carefully packing up his stuff, Garen pulled out a map of the entire Northern region of the Primary Substance Plane. After looking at it briefly, he left the Dragon King Mountain.

******

On a huge snowy plane, pure white snow continued to rain down from the sky.

In the middle of the sky, a gigantic globe-like sphere was moving at high speed underneath the pale white sun. It had a ring of satellites orbiting it. The entire sphere was completely white, and one could barely see it on a snowy day like this.

The sphere was more than a thousand meters wide, there were multiple intricately carved out ring-shaped spaces. Each space had a person in a white garb with a White Dragon symbol on its chest. These people came in all shapes and sizes, slowly patrolling their respective spaces.

At the upper peak of the structure, the sphere had a small floating platform. A sentinel guard was standing on top of the platform lazily, involuntarily yawning.

“Really, to think they’re sending an entire battle fortress. For a short distance like this, we could’ve just teleported over. Why do we have to fly over so slowly on this thing? I don’t know what’s going on in those Elders’ minds,” the sentinel ranted. Blue sparks flickered from his fingertips, displaying his terrifying spell power. For an average sentinel, to think he had at least a Level Five in Arcane Arts.

“Stop whining, we should almost be there. We don’t get a lot of chances to use the battle fortress anyway. This time, we’re mainly using it to intimidate our opponents, realistically speaking we might not even have to use it in the end.” The sentinel who was taking the next shift walked over while laughing heartily.

“Recently, there’s been a lot more Void Creatures, it might be our turn to head into the battlefield soon, so I guess this can serve as a practice run,” the first sentinel shook his head, saying.

“You sure have set your sights far, but I feel…” Just as the second sentinel was finishing his sentence, a voice cut him off, “there’s a situation!” He immediately tensed up, looking at the snowy skies afar.

Beep beep…

Suddenly, the fortress let out a sharp alarm tone.

“High energy creatures approaching at high speeds!” The supervisor’s Tower Soul sent out an alert, “please report to your stations and await further orders!”

At the center of the fortress, inside a wide control room.

Two Elders with white hair and beards were seated on two armchairs, frowning as they looked at the situation outside the crystal glass.

“What a fast speed!”

“Bordo, it might be someone like you from the Dragon Clan, should we take action?” The other Elder asked the Elder seated right across of him.

Chapter 1356: Tiamat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Elder named Bordo did not reply, his eyes fixated on the crystal glass window.

“It’s a White Dragon’s aura… this timing…”

He was the high-leveled Elder who was sent by the White Dragon Mountain to intimidate Garen of the White Dragon Clan. He was also a member of the Dragon Clan Council. His powers were unfathomable.

“The target this time is to intimidate Garen and subsequently capture him. The advantages of the Cold Winter Tower’s representative cannot fall into the wrong hands. It’s the foundation that belongs to our White Dragon Clan,” the thought flashed in his mind.

“Continue on forward. The Full Moon Fortress does not need to fear anyone from the Dragon Clan. If he’s non-hostile, he will naturally stop. If not, then it’s his suicide,” he sent out the orders.

“True, the White Dragons around this area should all be Garen’s minions. Oh, he’s starting to slow down. Maybe he’s here to surrender?” The other Elder looked out with slight curiosity.

Outside the fortress, a white figure zipped through leaving behind a white line, lunging directly towards the white sphere fortress. His speed was slowly decreasing, and his Dragonic Aura was slowly kept away.

However, just as he was about one kilometer away from the white sphere fortress.

Boom!!

The white line suddenly accelerated, its speed instantly increasing multiple times from its original speed. This White Dragon hidden amidst the snowy skies seemed to have torn open a vacuum-like trail, leaving behind a snowless path in his tracks.

Using this terrifying speed that was unimaginable to a White Dragon, he violently crashed onto the white sphere fortress.

“What is he doing!!”

“Damn it! Is he crazy!?”

“It’s gonna hit!! Brace yourselves!!”

The White Dragons in the fortress were all shell-shocked. They did not expect that there were still creatures who would dare to use their physical bodies to directly slam into a battle fortress!?

He was an absolute madman!

The white line zipped through the air, leaving behind visible transparent ripples. At first, it almost looked as if it stopped in its tracks, but the next instance, it had already collided head-on with the fortress!

Boom!!!

With a huge crash, the fortress shook violently as it collided with the white line in mid-air. Its huge kinetic force was immediately dissipated with the huge collision.

Looking at the scene from below, the white sphere fortress building seemed to be chipped off in a huge area. Large amounts of white debris rained down from the sky.

Sparks of electricity and blue light started enveloping the surface of the white sphere.

After being hit, the white sphere started falling down from the sky at an angle.

“Anti-Magic Energy Fields!! This bastard!!”

The White Dragons on the surface of the fortress immediately transformed and flew out. All the White Dragons here were elites of the elites, every one of them was at the very least a Level Seven in Power. A Level Nine Great Wizard had once used the Ultimate Transformation Spell on them.

The fortress continued to nosedive.

Below, a large number of animal critters on the snow plains were running off in panic.

Boom!

The fortress crashed onto the snow plains below like a gigantic snowball. Powdered snow splashed everywhere like a huge ocean wave. Rings of wave-like snow flung in all directions due to the shock wave. Some of the arctic foxes and polar bears who did not get away in time were instantly decimated into meat paste.

After rolling for a bit, the fortress crashed into a small white pine forest and stopped moving.

Inside the fortress.

In the control room where the two Elders were in, a young man dressed in white was floating silently in mid-air, he was looking at the two Elders who were also floating in the air.

The three’s Cold Regions seemed to be intertwined together, naturally emitting a terrifying energy field, causing the entire control room to be an icy cold space. It was almost as if the air itself has been frozen as well.

“Elder Bordo… I heard that you were coming over, so I just had to personally come to greet you as soon as possible…” The floating young man was Garen who had just left the Dragon King Mountain. After he received the report, he immediately set out to stop the team sent by the White Dragon Mountain.

He neither had his army nor his underlings with him. It was just him alone, a single dragon, directly confronting the team head on.

Bordo’s face was green, standing beside the other Elder.

They completely did not expect Garen to have the guts to directly confront the White Dragon Mountain’s team. After all, they had official positions as the representative of the White Dragons and even had the backing of the great Tiamat.

“Garen!!” He was grinding his teeth as he glared at his opponent. “You are committing a blasphemous sin against the Gods!!”

“Blasphemy?” Garen laughed. “The great Tiamat does not think that way. Why don’t you try asking Lady Evil Dragon Goddess once more and see what they really think of me?”

As he spoke, his face started to transform him a human’s face into a dragon’s head. A pair of evil, powerful, strange but deep mutated dragon eyes appeared in front of the two Elders.

Among the pupils of those dragon eyes, there was even a pair of weird eyeballs.

Just from looking at it, the two Level Nine Elders had chills sent through their entire body.

“You!! …” Bordo’s entire body was shivering. He was pointing his finger at Garen trying to say something, but he noticed that he did not even have the power to open his mouth. His entire body’s power was slowly draining away.

Bzzt bzzt bzzt!

A rune with a high-level protective energy field started flashing up on his body, but it had no effect. That gaze was so evil that even the Semi-Divine Weapon, the Light of Luiz, was destroyed immediately. Bordo’s body started to melt like a lighted candle. His skin, hair, muscles all started to melt dripping in a gooey liquid.

The other Elder was in the same predicament. The two Level Nine Elder Dragons did not even have the basic strength to return to their original forms, all they could do was stare blankly as they melt away, disappearing from this world.

“How weak,” Garen said in a mocking tone. “White Dragon Mountain had long forgotten its former glory. The White Dragon Mountain now is completely rotten… don’t you think so, Your Excellency, the Great Tiamat.”

He turned around and looked at the figure to his left.

A thin plain-looking White Dragon Guard had been standing there since an unknown period of time ago. Hearing the query, this Dragon Guard let out a sharp and ghastly laugh.

“How interesting… from the start, I had already expected that, if it was not that King’s incarnation confronting us, then it would be those invaders from the Void. Looking at this scene now, I guessed I was right…”

“Too bad you came too late,” Garen narrowed his eyes, his tone remained casual.

“Late? No, no, no… it’s not too late,” the Dragon Guard raised his head. He had a human’s body but its face somehow had five different shrunken human faces of different colors on it. With so many tiny faces embedded on his head, it gave off an eerie but holy feeling.

“Even if this is just a temporary projection, if I wanted to defeat a Level Twelve small fry I would still be able to do it.”

“Is that so?” Garen let out a weird grin.

A ring of formless distortion started being emitted from his body naturally, completely enveloping Tiamat within it.

Garen only stared silently at his opponent. His latent ability of Spiritual Poison naturally followed his gaze and slowly moved towards its target.

Whoosh!!

The ten eyes on Tiamat all blinked at once, both their gaze instantly locked onto each other. It seemed like a blurry energy field burst open in the air, a large number of items and rubbish in the middle started being blown in all directions.

The Spiritual Poison and Tiamat’s Evil Eye attack collided with each other. Garen dodged slightly, his latent ability was pushed back. His Spiritual Poison had been canceled, and at the same time, Tiamat’s Evil Eye attack landed on the metal wall behind Garen, burning dozens of small holes onto it.

Tiamat let out an evil laugh, his body lunging towards Garen but briefly staggered.

“Poison?” He was stunned.

His natural Poison Region took effect.

Garen laughed loudly as he charged forward.

‘Natural Poison Territory: Anyone with Vitality Points below 50 will automatically enter an unconscious state, below 100 have a chance to be weakened (Lowered 1 to 4 Levels), Vitality Points above 130 will be immune to this effect.”

Obviously, the projection that Tiamat placed onto a mere Dragon Guard’s body did not have 100 Vitality Points.

His opponent’s aura rapidly fell.

Hmph!

Tiamat tensed his body up, a golden halo started to emit from his body.

‘Warning! Warning! You have entered a Holy Aura Territory. Vitality levels being calibrated… Immunity chance 34%. If you fail to achieve immunity, the negative effects will be that your level is lowered by two levels. Holy Aura Territory is already in effect.”

Garen had not sensed it, but his brain’s willpower had already sent out an alert rapidly.

“Holy Aura?” He suddenly felt his entire body turn heavy, almost as if he was chained with unimaginably heavy shackles. The Draconic Aura and the Arcane Art energy in this body both lowered by two levels and his overall attributes lowered by thirty points on average.

Getting shivers down his spine, Garen could no longer afford to underestimate his opponent.

The heavy Hoy Aura was restraining him, causing his speed to be lowered by a whole lot.

The two did not transform back into their dragon forms but instead charged directly at each other.

Once Garen made contact, he immediately started using all his close-quarter combat moves, various Secret Technique moves, and killing moves. With the support of an immense power, a tremendous might burst out from his body.

As a Five-Headed Dragon, even if Tiamat was using an incarnation, he would still have nearly five times the Stat Points of a dragon of the same level. With the increased power of Garen’s moves, the two clashed head-on.

After a brief exchange, the two got blown back. Garen’s chest seemed to have signs of blood. His Strength Stat seemed to be far behind Tiamat’s projection. His opponent’s Strength seemed to be already near two hundred points!!

After calming down, Garen lenedt power from the fortress walls and kicked hard. With a loud boom, the impact created a huge hole. His entire body started to twist around, the surrounding air immediately had its temperature lowered.

His mouth opened wide.

Whooo! A huge Frost Dragon Breath took shape as a cone and sprayed towards Tiamat.

“Fool!” Before Tiamat even finished, he felt his entire body tensing up. An excessively intense feeling of danger rushed through his body.

Immediately, he leaped away from where he was standing.

Boom!!

A huge metal beam from the fortress was raised up by a figure and violently slammed down onto the position he was standing just moments ago. The fortress behind had a huge hole broken through it, revealing the snowy scenery outside. The metal beam that was dozens of meters long got flung out like a brick, disappearing afar after a moment.

A huge burly man with unmeasurable strength appeared in front of Tiamat.

“Kill him!”

Garen’s voice sounded from nearby.

With a slight smile, the muscles throughout the man’s body started to expand. On his back, seven black-red Death Start Nodes slowly lit up.

Chapter 1357: Release 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Almost as if he sensed something was wrong, all of Tiamat’s eyes narrowed as he slowly jumped backwards.

When compared to the man in front of him, his current body was definitely worse off when it comes to pure Stats. His opponent seemed to have some special Secret Method to enhance his body. His brute force was not as strong as his opponent, and all his other abilities had been temporarily suppressed by Garen. This caused his originally confident self to start wanting to retreat from his hunting mission.

Boom!!

Not even giving him any time to think, the size of the man in front of him had already expanded three times. He went from a normal human’s size to that of half a fully matured White Dragon.

Roar!! The man let out an explosive battle cry as he shoved all ten of his fingers into the ground. Then, with a strong tug, the entire metal flooring had been bent and broken, being tossed straight towards Tamat.

“Evil Dragon’s Sight.” Tiamat’s ten eyes focused onto the metal board at the same time. Suddenly, a strong energy field was unleashed, stopping the metal board.

However, the energy field that was still sufficient last time barely lasted two seconds this time. With the energy field collapsed, the metal board continued to hurl towards him.

Bam!!

Tiamat instantly turned around and left his original position. Looking back, he saw that the position he was standing in had a huge hole in it.

Furthermore, the impact has caused the spherical fortress to roll slightly towards the same direction.

“Meteorology!”

Whoosh… With a strange cold breeze, more than ten translucent ice-crystal spears appeared behind him, silently flying towards his back at high speeds and agility, almost as if they were wielded by invisible creatures.

“Rainbow Jets.” Tiamat’s entire body suddenly emitted an intense and blinding rainbow light. Within the blinding lights, there were five rainbow colored dragon heads created from Divine Power mixed in. They furiously knocked off the spears behind him like a whip.

“Roar!” Out of nowhere, Tiamat opened his mouth and roared in Garen’s direction.

Boom!!

A five-colored Draconic Aura burst out from his mouth. Lightning, flames, cold air, acidity and poison, five fearsomely powerful Draconic Auras mixed together, creating a typhoon-like attack flying towards Garen.

Seven Lives jumped up high and attempted to punch through the Draconic Aura but to no avail. The terrifying Draconic Aura instantly decimated the muscles in his body, Even if he had twice the strength and fitness of Garen’s original body, but when facing an attack infused with Divine Souls, he would still be instantly destroyed.

The only thing Seven Lives could manage to do was to delay the speed of the Draconic Aura ever so slightly, and at the same time mildly weakening the Draconic Aura’s power.

Garen had already sensed it the instance the Draconic Aura was fired. He rapidly changed his position, only to find that this Draconic Aura typhoon seemed to have homing capabilities. At that point, he was completely shocked.

Not having enough time to hide, Garen opened his eyes wide. Two white light rays shot out from his eyes like a streak of lightning, directly flying towards the Draconic Aura Typhoon.

“Elemental Protection!” Using his very short buffer time, he started chanting a high-leveled spell chant.

A rainbow-colored barrier immediately erected in front of him, then a second one, and a third one. This type of adapted Level Nine Spell, Elemental Protection, was something that Garen memorized just to counter Tiamat. With the high calculation and processing power of his brain’s willpower, along with his high level of intelligence, these Level Nine spells would only take him a few days to completely analyze.

Ever since the day he broke Tiamat’s Divine Art crystal, Garen already started making preparations against every probable Divine Soul assaults and attacks. Even if Tiamat was only a God with a weaker Divine Power, even if he’s highly unlikely to personally attack him.

Out of the attacks he prepared for, the most famous of it was precisely the five different Draconic Auras that Tiamat shoots out with his five-colored dragon head.

Now his efforts had finally paid off!

Garen continuously erected five layers of elemental barriers, almost like a stack of rainbow colored glass blocking his front.

Furthermore, once the Poisonous Eye was unleashed, it instantly hit the center of the five-colored Draconic Aura, silently piercing it, shooting towards Tiamat’s projection with absolute precision.

It was an instant counterattack on his part.

The Draconic Aura typhoon finally struck. The five layers of Level Nine protection rapidly got shattered. However, the Draconic Aura also started to weaken, its speed also decreasing.

Taking the opportunity, Garen stomped down. His near two hundred points of agility instantly causing a terrifying explosive effect.

Even if he was being suppressed by the Holy Aura, at that moment he still disappeared like a ray of light, making it seem impossible for anyone to ever catch him.

This was a supernatural phenomenon that occurs when one’s agility reaches a certain degree, Instantaneous Movement.

Garen’s silhouette immediately appeared next to Tiamat, violently grabbing on to his opponents arm. In that instance, he casted a spell.

“Space-Time Anchor!”

A transparent energy wave rippled through Tiamat’s body, making him unable to move.

Bam!

“You!!! …” Tiamat was in shock. He did not expect Garen’s speed to be able to get past his senses, instantaneously moving over.

With a raise of his hand, a bunch of black rays burst out from his hand.

These rays were all Level Nine Wither Rays. These type of rays was strengthened from a medium-level Weakening Ray. Every one of these rays dealt direct damage to the soul. As compared to Disintegrate which focuses on the material decomposition, this focuses directly on one’s soul.

For an average Level Nine Spell, even a top Level Fifteen Wizard could only unleash them one by one. At best, they would implement some unique improvements, and through strong spiritual power and careful magical energy manipulation, to increase the power of their spells slightly.

However, it still could not release a whole bunch like this.

It looks like Tiamat had also made specific countermeasures to defeat Garen.

The bunch of black rays twisted around turning into the shape of a tilde and surrounding Garen from all angles. Due to the short distance and the fact that these rays travel at light speed, there was no way of dodging it.

At the same time, Garen’s hand was also holding Tiamat down in place, not letting him dodge. The rays of the Poisonous Eye pierced through the five-colored Draconic Aura and landed on his body.

Hiss…

A strong sound of corrosion could be heard.

All of Tiamat’s eyes suddenly opened wide.

“This is!! Corrosive Divinity??” A golden Divine Power armor appeared over his body, but the gold color of it was rapidly fading away.

After all, this was only a projection, to be able to bring so much Divine Power with him was already a miracle. He had already exhausted most of it. However, what Tiamat did not expect was Garen’s stellar performance in every aspect. From Supernatural Instantaneous Movement to Poisonous Eye, a powerful incarnation that suddenly appeared, and even his natural latent Poison Region and Spiritual Poison. With all of these abilities added together, he was completely unlike any other Level Twelve existence Tiamat has ever seen. To say that he was a Level Fifteen would even be an underestimation!!!

“Just you wait!!!” He opened his mouth to say one last sentence, before instantly melting away, turning into a grey-white pus.

A golden dot of light flew up from the pus and flew towards the broken area of the fortress.

However, it was immediately caught between Garen’s hands before it could fly off.

His face was in an abnormal shade of red. Although this battle was quite short, he still used up almost all of his trump cards.

The explosive combination of Supernatural Instantaneous Movement and Poisonous Eye was so powerful that even he himself was shocked. However, in order to prevent Tiamat from dodging the Poisonous Eye, he paid a hefty price.

At least more than twenty Withering Rays all landed on him

Even if his vitality was over two hundred, when facing against these types of top Level Nine rays imbued with Divine Power, at that point he felt as if his entire body was dehydrated. His skin, muscles and bones could visibly be seen to be rapidly weakening and withering away.

Quickly stuffing the golden light into his mouth, Garen directly flew off from the hole and disappearing into the snowy sky, completely ignoring the White Dragon Guards who came over to check on the situation.

******

The Divinity was flying around within Garen’s dark soul space.

Within this tiny crystal ball-like golden sphere, a small dragon with five colored dragon heads could be seen. That was Tiamat’s original body’s image. This Evil Dragon Goddess with five dragon heads was repeatedly letting out loud roars.

“It’s useless.”

At the center of the soul space, a huge tower-like pillar transmitted Garen’s voice.

The pillar was made of layers and layers of Soul Rings, at the bottom of it was five colorless transparent Soul Rings, and then above it was red, orange, then red again.

“If it was your incarnation, maybe I would be left with no other choice but to escape. However, that was only a mere projection.” Garen’s fae appeared on the surface of the Soul Ring Pillar.

Countless colorless and transparent tentacles dangled out from the Soul Ring Pillar, furiously grabbing the Divinity with no place to hide. With a tug, the golden sphere Divinity directly flew into the Soul Ring Pillar and immediately got swallowed.

Although Garen was had already used his maximum concentration, but he still underestimated the tremendous amount of messages taken from a Divine Soul’s projections. It was not only just the messages from the Divinity’s original body, but it also carried a lot of information and knowledge that Tiamat had transmitted over to this projection.

This was not just a simple destruction, but Garen was using the Hellfrost Peacock Queen’s strong Devourer ability, directly attempting to devour his opponent.

The tremendous amount of messages started to turn into countless golden light spots in Garen’s Soul Ring Pillar. They gather together and scatter about, sometimes exploding like golden fireworks, and other times looking thin as if they were fading away.

A Void Shadow of a small dragon with five colored dragon heads and a fierce white peacock were fighting inside the Soul Ring Pillar

When they first started, it seemed to be a tie. However, as time passed on, the five-colored dragon did not have any means of replenishing its strength, whereas the Hellfrost Peacock had an unlimited supply of Soul Power. Suddenly, the gap between the two had widened.

After an unknown amount of time, the white peacock finally bit down on the five-colored dragon’s main dragon head’s neck, knocking him to the ground.

Bam!!

Garen slowly opened his eyes, he was lying on an icy white plains.

A thick layer of snow had already gathered on top of his body, almost completely burying him.

He struggled slightly as he stood up. There were no creatures in the surrounding area. When he was groggily flying about just now, he did not pick a direction, but rather he was just headed towards where he felt was the safest.

He did not even remember how far he flew.

His entire body’s skin and muscles felt like a dried up corpse, there was no signs of water. His human form self had already started to turn black all over. With a flick of his finger, he created a water mirror and looked at his appearance.

He literally looked like skin and bones, it was a pitiful sight.

“Looks no different from a mummy…” Garen dispersed the water mirror.

He immediately checked his own status via the Status Pane.

‘Garen – Strength 210(34), Agility 210(22), Vitality 210(57), Intelligence 210(101). Potential 2829%. Soul Limit 210.

Seven Soul Rings: Five colorless, red, orange.

Level 10 Draconic Aura. Level 10 Arcane Arts.

Void Original Opus – 100%. Hind legs – Evil Soldier, Wings – Seven Lives, Tail – Demonic Book.

Combined evaluation – Near Demigod. Title – Winter Sigh.

Status – Extremely weak, Tiamat’s Toxic Woven Flames (Damaged by Tiamat Draconic Goddess’ Divine Power. You will receive a weakened version of the Five-Colored Elemental Draconic Aura Damage once every noon.)’

“How terrible…” Garen self-deprecated, but the next line did change his mood for the better.

On the Skill Pane, a completely new item had emerged.

Right at his original Identity Pane, in front of the “Void Pursuer”, a golden icon appeared.

‘Potential Quality – Divinity Creature, Void Pursuer.’

Garen gazed onto the “Divinity Creature” icon. Suddenly a gigantic flow of messages directly surged into his brain.

‘Devouring Tiamat’s Divinity success, attained special Divinity Creature typing.’

Below it, a list of special traits Divinity Creatures have was shown. All of them were icons for various activated abilities.

Listed first was ‘Frost Immunity’, ‘Enhance Breath’, ‘Elemental Resistance’, and ‘Enhanced Defense’. These four new abilities were the main ones. The remaining abilities were just some simple and practical spells like, summoning an Ice Element every day (Level equivalent to own level minus 2), using Cold Winter Weather three times every day (adapted Meteorology spell), Ice and Snow Hardening, Hail Spell, Eye of Frost, etc.

Chapter 1358: Release 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

However, these types of spells were not as useful as the first four passive abilities.

Frost Immunity: Garen would be immune to all frost type attacks, including a part of Divine Power’s damage.

Enhanced Breath: Breath which was originally peaked at Level Nine, had been enhanced to Level Thirteen due to the Divinity’s modification.

Elemental Resistance: An increase of 10% resistance towards the four elemental attacks, namely Earth, Water, Wind and Fire type. In addition to Garen’s 10% resistance since he was a Dragon, he now had a very impressive twenty percent resistance.

Lastly, the Enhanced Defense was his core skill.

Enhanced Defense: Divine Creatures shall gain 20 points of defense (currently 50). Negate Divine Power damage by 10%.

This was an overpowered effect as it meant that any normal physical attack which had the strength less than fifty points would be nullified by Garen. He, who already had a powerful physical characteristic that could nullify all attacks from low-level weapons had this ability further enhanced.

Warriors with fifty points of strength were equivalent to the human’s high-ranking Knights. This meant that no one would be able to damage Garen’s scale without a weapon with a unique attribute, regardless if it was the sharpest weapon in the world. This had yet to consider injuring the dragon body under its scales.

In simple terms, Garen was completely immune towards a forefront attack.

Furthermore, with Divine Power being nullified by 10%, it meant that Garen would be able to reduce an incoming Divine Power attack by 10%.

This was the power and special characteristic of being a Divine Creature.

Garen had officially entered the realm of Demigod.

The key difference between a Demigod and a typical living being was the immunity, resistance and the level of defense they possessed.

In overall comparison to a Human Warrior, he who was in a Demigod state would obtain a bunch of spells, a variety of resistances and unique enhancement in his attacks at the same time.

Although there was not much of an improvement in terms of his attributes and Life Force, his lifespan had increased tremendously.

Garen stood on the snowy ground as he reached out his hand. He felt that he could freely control the flow of the heavy snowstorm as if he had total control of the weather with this spell.

This spell would not exhaust his Spell Slot. He did not use a lot of his Spell Slots to begin with as he relied on his melee attacks to kill his enemies.

It was very important for weak beings to save up these Spell Slots but it did not matter to Garen at all as he was a powerful Dragon.

Perhaps he would be able to escape from the grasp of the Spider Web Spell by just wiggling his toenail. The Lower to Middle-Level Spell Slot was meaningless to him other than making his life a little bit more convenient.

“I need to recover my physical condition quickly…” Garen frowned. It was extremely dangerous for a Dragon to not have the power to protect itself in this chaotic era. Furthermore, Tiamat would be able to locate him at any given moment via the Prophecy Spell.

Garen guessed that the reason he was able to devour the Divinity this fast was not because he was decrypting the Divinity but to devour it completely with his Devour Ability. Naturally, the efficiency of the process was much better. Analogically speaking, it was just like using a handphone or taking it apart and researching it thoroughly. There was a difference between the two.

Most of the creatures were the user who used the phone directly whereas Garen was the other type. It played the main role as he had finished analyzing it thoroughly, he would be able to determine more similar Divinity characteristics from a Divinity. As long as he had enough computing power and storage space, he would eventually have the full picture of the Divinity Persona’s structure.

In other words, if Garen were to study the Corrosive Divinity, he would be able to branch out and discover the Death Corrosive Divine Persona and even the Decaying Divine Persona. If he were to analyze the Time Divinity, he would be able to structure the Aging Divine Persona and so on.

The nature of Divinity was ultimately the realization of the universal law from a living creature. It was the natural evolution of the living flesh and the cells’ will to understand the law of nature.

“The fastest way to recover my body is obviously devouring more stuff…” Garen looked around. In theory, the Devouring Ability from the Hellfrost Peacock Queen could convert anything into energy resources. However, items such as snowy water and normal stones would not be able to recover one percent of his body strength even if he were to devour a hundred million tons of them. After all, their characteristics were different and it would require a long time to digest them as well. Furthermore, these substances required less energy to devour as well.

Naturally, the best way to replenish his life force was to devour things which had a Life Force as well.

Garen set his sight onto a snowy hill nearby.

He then walked towards the snowy hill.

He soon arrived in a forest and a few Snow Wolves ran far away as they sensed his presence.

Garen ignored them as he reached out his hand and placed them onto a huge tree.

The tree which was covered in the white snow could be seen wilting with the naked eye. The snow started dropping down to the ground as the big tree which was as thick as a human’s hug quickly arched down. Like an old human, it turned pale as its bark which was rich in water instantly turned rough and wilted as it became a black old tree bark.

On the other hand, Garen’s complexion seemed to have improved slightly.

“It’s unfortunate that I’ve only devoured a small amount of pure Divinity. Perhaps the effect will be much better if it were the Divinity with quality.”

Garen quickly continued to the next tree as he finished absorbing the first tree.

As time passed, Garen soon finished absorbing the entire snowy forest. The skin and muscles on his body started to fill up and he at least did not look wilted anymore.

Garen moved both of his hands.

“This is too slow… Demonic Book!”

The space behind him distorted slightly as a fully black demon with a small violin in his hand appeared.

The man looked cold and handsome as his eyes gave off a faint gold luster.

“Master, what’s your order?”

He bowed down elegantly.

“I want to recover as fast as possible and I need to at least devour a huge amount of living beings. Since my strength is not up to par yet, I’ll let you handle this,” said Garen with a stern face.

“No problem…” The Demonic Book smiled as he gently picked up the small violin in his hand and placed the bow onto the string.

He slowly shut his eyes as if he was engrossed into the environment.

Sizzle…!

Suddenly, a huge and sharp soundwave spread across the snowy land with him as the epicenter.

A powerful and seductive melody spread across the land along with the snowy wind. There were distorted faces flowing together with the wind as they spread in all directions.

The Holy Phoenix Demonic Book’s expertise was not in killing but an unparalleled seduction and hypnotism.

Soon, the living beings around the snowy land which heard the melody had their eyes turned red. They then walked towards the source of the melody as if their consciousness were completely buried.

As they walked slowly towards the source of the melody, Garen could feel hundreds of Life Force approaching him which were linked like a spider web. There were even dozens of humans, elves and dwarfs among them.

It felt incredibly intriguing as if he was at the center of all lives. These Life Forces kept approaching him without any sign of stopping soon.

Garen could not help but to give off an ecstatic cry.

**********

Far away at the east of the Primary Plane.

At the sky above the mountain range filled with yellow rocks.

Two golden doors slowly appeared. The doors opened up and two Majestic Gods glowing in bright gold came out from them. One of them had a pair of wings, clad in armor and had a long sword in his hand whereas the other had a Crystal Crown on his head and white fiery fire burning at the bottom of his feet.

During the evening hours, the blood red sun gradually set below the horizon as the yellow mountain range started to tremble.

“Fire of the Elves? You dare to come again even though I didn’t eat you up last time?” A humongous snake head slowly appeared between the mountain range. It spitted out the rocks out of its mouth as it stared ill-intently at the God who had fires at the bottom of his feet.

“Leaving the Heavens shall be your greatest remorse.” The Huge Rock Snake started smiling like a villain.

“Greatest remorse?” The Fire of the Elves rubbed the crack on the Crystal Crown as his gaze was filled with killing intent.

“King of the Rocks, today is the day you die!”

A white gold wave-shaped dagger appeared in his hand out of the blue as he gently threw the dagger to the front. Suddenly, the sky turned dimmed as the sun was distorted, releasing a minute amount of gold fire from its center as it flew towards their direction at incredible speed.

“The Sun God’s Light!!” The Huge Rock Snake’s expression turned for the worse as it tried to dig beneath the ground to escape. However, it was too late.

A thin layer of Golden Light had blocked his path, preventing him from drilling further in. It was a Divine Power Barrier unique only to the Higher God, God of the Sun. The Fire of the Elves had even taken out the God of the Sun’s Divine Weapon. Was not he just a Middle God!!?

“To cause chaos upon the True Soul. Today is the day the war among the Gods starts!!” The Fire of the Elves looked like a savage as he nodded towards another God before both of them flew down.

In an instant, the golden light crashed onto the rocks, turning them into dusts. The dusts had covered the entire sky within tens of kilometers in diameter around the area.

**********

In the Void Temple.

“The King of the Rocks has fallen?!!”

The Void Temple was a huge metal vortex and was located at the center of a galaxy. There were countless of metallic rings structured similar to of a galaxy as it rotated slowly. Among them were hundreds of billions of metallic planets rotating slowly, forming into solar system of different sizes.

There was a pond the size of a planet at the core of the metallic galaxy and the source of the voice was the pond.

The pond was filled with silver liquid and ripples were constantly generated due to its viscosity.

“The opponent has started to make their moves… It’s the God of the Sun that had attacked but that’s fine.” Another female voice could be heard. “This will happen sooner or later.”

“Although the beings who had entered the region would improve greatly within a short amount of time, it bears a very huge risk as well. The risks and gains balance up very well.” A voice of an old man chimed in.

“We can’t just do nothing since they’ve already initiated,” said the man who started the conversation coldly.

“The Mother Stream Alliance had already sent their Eye of the Slaughter. We should officially make our move as well…”

A man that was covered in silver metal slowly came out from the silver pond. His body was stabbed with dozens of weapons. These weapons were either rusted or glowing with silver and gold light. There was also a white, slanted bone dagger pierced through the top of his skull. As the sharp dagger was pulled out from his head, the white brain plasma solidified onto the sharp dagger.

This man was already considered dead and yet it flew out of the pond as if he was alive.

He opened up his hand as a small solar system started rotating on his palm.

“Lost. Are you trying to release that thing?!” The woman’s tone from one side sounded rather uncomfortable.

“In this destructive war without compromise where there is no right or wrong. Is there anything more terrifying than this?” The Fallen True Soul started smiling gently.

The remaining True Souls and Demon Lords remained silent.

“God Fehra is nothing. The real trouble right now is the Abyss. That place is hell,” said the Fallen True Soul calmly. “The Child of Hell has appeared. Soon he shall incarnate into a being that could eliminate all beings. I’ve attempted to get in touch with the Abyss but I was rejected. This made me feel extremely uneasy.”

“The Abyss is trying to consume our souls. He’s trying to understand the secret rules of our world. I wasn’t able to stop it but nothing will not come out without paying a price for messing me around…!” The Fallen True Soul’s eyes turned black as he stared at the solar system in his hand.

Chapter 1359: Massacre and Divinity 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At the northern region of the Deladia Empire, Corolla City.

Ding Dang Ding Ding Dang Dang~

The Red Horse Carriage rang its bell as it moved forward on the main street at the city center. The driver was an old man with a white beard and had a black captain’s hat on his head. He dressed up like a like a pirate and laughed like one as he looked at the excited crowd of kids on both sides of his carriage.

He received a lot of hustles and bustles from both sides as there were people shouting out to buy their snacks, cheering from the people and even the music playing from the poets. The crowds squirmed among themselves on the busy street, hence his carriage had no choice but to slow down to prevent himself from crashing into the passersby.

Boom boom boom!

Colorful streamers were shot up into the sky. Among the streamers, colorful powders were mixed among them and they dyed the whole area in colors as it rained down.

The mistresses were holding their children by their hand as they stood beside the clown who was selling candies.

The magicians and acrobatic gnomes stood high up at both sides of the street as they performed their beautiful arts. The youngsters who were out shopping by the streets applauded as they watched their performance.

The morning sunlight showered the entire city, painting it with a layer of faint gold.

The Guardians would occasionally patrol on the streets and one could vaguely see the Wizard from the northern region in their cloaks among them. These people were wearing a full body grey robe. They were either seen lowering their heads and kept quiet most of the time or speaking to their acquaintances softly, giving off a rather quiet and mysterious vibe.

The people around them would stare them in awe whenever they passed by them.

“There has been an increased amount of Void Creatures lately…” The Wizard in the patrolling team sighed.

“Right. I’ve received three reports just two days ago and all of them were reports of Void Creatures. None of them has yet to be solved and the unease within the city has started to spread.” The captain of the guardian’s expression was helpless. “The head captain has received an order from his superior that we need to fortify our defenses. However, how are we supposed to do that with the amount of manpower we have right now? It’s the Usha Festival right now. It’s an annual carnival festival enjoyed by all and we’re lacking the manpower to begin with.”

“Afterall, we don’t really belong to the authentic Deladia Empire where the higher management belongs to the White Dragon Mountain. The issues regarding the Void Creatures have been reported to them but we have yet to receive a response from them. It’s obvious that they are lacking manpower,” responded the Wizard softly.

“Hey, there’s someone performing a violin solo over there.” The female guardian seemed interested as she rushed towards the tall stage nearby.

The remaining patrol members had no choice but to follow along as well.

Far away above the stage, they could vaguely see a poet in a black cloak with a small violin. He was just about to place his bow onto the string and seemed to have just about to start his performance.

“For thousands of years, Corolla has been the border city under the direct order of the White Dragon Mountain. We have all of the White Dragon’s history as they developed until this very day. This city is the city of culture and art of Deladia,” narrated the man in black cloak softly with a metallic voice.

“It’s very fortunate for me to arrive here as I am able to see the peace and prosperity in this city. I wish to give you a melody, my own piece of melody with my utmost sincerity…”

“Dream… This melody’s name is called dream…” The black cloak started to pull his bow slowly.

The beautiful, slender, silk-like melody from the violin spread across the busy street. The melody was not overwhelmed by the other noise as it was extremely clear.

There was not much of a crowd below the stage before he started. However once he did, people started to gather to listen to and enjoy his performance.

As time slowly passed, the melody became clearer and louder. The crowd started to flood in and even a few patrols were firmly mesmerized by the beautiful and peaceful melody.

Then, the Wizard jolted as he came back to his senses.

“What happened? Did I just get pulled in by the melody?” He did not even like music and yet he became cold and quiet as if the melody had used the most beautiful moonlight and bathed him equally on his body, causing him to quietly calm down.

He looked around and realized that something was off. It was not just him as even the team captain, Aswan who was a Level Three had turned quiet as well. He was a rough man who hated music and he had become quiet because of this melody.

“That’s not right! There’s something off about this music!” The Wizard was alerted as he pinched his members who were beside him. However, there was no reaction at all. What was supposed to cause a hugely painful and screaming reaction did not occur at this very moment. They did not even frown when they were pinched.

The melody spread further and wider…

The black cloak on the stage started to levitate. He flew higher and higher as he gently landed on the highest bell tower nearby.

He remained quiet as he played his violin, as if nothing could disrupt his performance in any way.

The Wizard tried to scream at the top of his lungs to disrupt this performance but he quickly realized that he could not emit any sound at all.

He then adjusted his throat in an attempt to fix it but to no avail.

He was not able to make a single sound at all. In fact, he realized that the background noises that could disrupt the melody had gradually toned down to the point where it could not be heard.

Then, the performer in black cloak’s eyes gave off a red glow as he started to speed up the rhythm of his melody.

However, there was not a single sign of spell being activated at all.

It was just a normal melody and pure music.

Cling!

Suddenly, a soft and gentle voice could be heard among the densely packed crowd. A bald middle-aged man had used the cake knife in his hand and stabbed it into his own throat. He looked at the sky, revealing a mournful expression.

The blood flowed along his palm down to his arms as it dripped to the floor. However, the people around him did not seem to realize what had happened at all. Perhaps it would be more accurate to say that none of them cared.

The melody started to turn sorrowful.

Cling cling!

Another two gentle noises could be heard as two people in the crowd used their fruit knives and stabbed it into their throats. They cried as they laid onto their own puddle of blood and yet no one cared.

The number of people committing suicide gradually increased as they picked up all sorts of sharp objects and stabbed them into their throats. None of them made even a cry before their deaths as they laid quietly on the streets.

Ten people… Twenty… Fifty… A hundred…

More and more people started to spill their blood as they ended their lves. The streets were then dyed completely in red.

The Wizard stood among the crowd as he tried his best to not listen to the strange melody. He was born with a lack of concentration, which meant that it was extremely hard for him to focus when he performed a specific task. This was also the reason why he was still a Level Two Wizard. However, this lack of concentration had become the reason why he was still alive.

Chills were sent down his spine as he looked at his own team captain Aswan unsheathing his sword and cut his own throat. He was still smiling as tears filled up his eyes even as he laid on the ground.

He tried to stop it but he could not control his body, as if his body was not under his control.

“What is going on!!??” He screamed within himself and yet he could still not change the current situation where his body was paralyzed.

The number of people committing suicide increased as the blood on the ground merged into a river. A flock of pigeons and other unknown small birds and insects started to revolve around the black cloak performers. Occasionally, they would crash onto the walls and buildings nearby and die from the impact. However, they were not awakened when their own kind passed away as they remained dancing around the performer at high speed.

“This is the music of death…” The Wizard could only think of such a sorrowful thought. It was also his last and only thought before he blacked out and became unconscious as he fell onto the ground.

Within half an hour, the busy Corolla City had turned into a dead city. Fresh blood had covered every corner of the city. All lives, regardless if it was an animal or human had ended their lives by this strange melody.

Those Void Creatures that had hidden among the crowds did not survive through this disaster as well.

Cling!

Finally, the Level Seven City Master took up his own blade and ended his life inside the main office.

Then, the melody from the Black Cloak had slowly reached to an end.

He gently played the final note as he put down his small violin. He then looked at the city with ten thousands of population turning into a lifeless city filled with fresh blood.

“What a beautiful melody…” A lively young man with his crystal gem-like skin appeared behind the performer.

He was in a white cloak and his eyes were mysteriously black. The white pupil could be seen in his black pupil and it looked extremely strange.

“Master, are you satisfied with your meal?” The Demonic Book turned around elegantly as he bowed.

“I’ve fully recovered.” Garen nodded satisfactorily. “Fifteen thousand people’s worth of life force. Fifteen thousand souls… The Despair Skull has been fully filled as well.”

He raised his left hand and a few colorful jewels had appeared on the black bracelet on his wrist. They were yellow and red in color and there were a total of five of them.

“I guess it is faster if we perform a massacre…” Garen was extremely satisfied as a jewel on the Death Bracelet represented a Soul Seed. Since he had five of these jewels, it meant that these tens of thousands of people’s souls had provided him a total of five Soul Seeds. This was completely different from secretly absorbing the souls in the Abyss.

He slightly opened his mouth and the five jewels on the bracelet instantly turned into five streams of light as they were absorbed into his mouth.

Garen then shut his mouth satisfactorily and closed his eyes as he enjoyed his gains.

Inside the dark Soul Space, he had finally filled up the eight Soul Ring. As he fused in the five Soul Seeds, the Soul Ring was instantly upgraded into a faint red Soul Ring. Then, all there’s left was to increase it to orange color and finally yellow color before he arrived at the Upper-Level Demon Lord Class.

An Upper-Level Demon Lord at its peak would be able to fight against a Lower God. It was not just an embodiment but an actual God descending to the mortal world.

Garen gathered the remaining transparent energy in his body on his chest inside of the Enneahedron. A bloodbath worth tens of thousands of lives had allowed Garen to form a grey-black Enneahedron.

Roar!!!

An angry dragon roar could be heard far away in the sky.

“Oh… It’s Tiamat’s power.” Garen raised his head and looked up as he revealed a smile. “Unfortunately, she’s one step behind…”

Pew!

Garen and Demonic Book disappeared at the top of the bell tower.

******

The Corolla City, the ancient city under the direct command of the White Dragon Mountain had been massacred. The life of fifteen thousand people including their souls had vanished. They did not enter the Abyss nor hell and not even the Styx or Tiamat Divine Kingdom. All of them had mysteriously vanished.

As Tiamat did not have any church but a few worshippers and evil priests, practically no one was able to obtain any more clues from her side.

There were only a few lucky survivors that could describe what had happened then.

An evil and mysterious performer had hypnotized the entire city. He did not kill any of them. Instead, all of them had committed suicide! Corpses filled all the streets, small and big. Even the Level Seven City master had committed suicide in his own room.

However, this was a news that was worth paying attention to. The White Dragon Mountain was angered as they sent a huge amount of members to capture a genius White Dragon named Garen. However, all of them were killed by Garen when they engaged in a battle.

Within half a month, Garen had killed at least thirty Adult White Dragons, Elder Dragons, and Ancient Dragons combined.

For the next half month, it was not just Corolla City that had suffered as the Rosan City which was seven hundred kilometers away had suffered the same fate.

This city was not a city under the direct command of the White Dragon Mountain. It was a city belonging to the Black Streak Empire and at the border of the Black Elf Empire. The majority of the city consisted of soldiers and there were twenty-five thousand people died in this massacre.

The Music of Death had spread across the entire northern region.

As two big cities were massacred in a row, a huge amount of members from the church gathered together in an attempt to investigate the situation. However, all evidence had without a doubt pointed towards the new Dragon of Disaster, the White Dragon Garen.

Chapter 1360: Massacre and Divinity 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The White Dragon Mountain had requested a hunting order towards the Dragon Clan Alliance as the major churches had sent out their elite forces to work together.

There was evidence stating that Garen had achieved the peak of mortals, which was Level Fifteen. In fact, Tiamat’s oracle might have suggested that Garen had already obtained the Demigod’s Divinity.

A Level Fifteen Demigod Powerhouse would be impossible to be chained or killed without a Clone of God or three similarly powerful powerhouses surrounding him.

However, as the Gods were being suppressed by the Void in the overall situation, the Pantheons were still facing the constant destruction imposed by the three major Void beings. The Eye of the Slaughter seemed to have been revived as he was spreading the Evil Eye Church within the inner region of the Element Plane and he had also swallowed the Big Mistress’ Church in the Abyss.

The Fallen True Soul seemed to have acted on his own as well as he started to spread something across the Primary Plane.

The Distortion Demon Master who was the only who knew his place had even started to gather and invading the lands. He had already occupied more than half of the lands in the eastern empires.

The Pantheons had formed an alliance and sent out a united group of incarnated armies to retaliate against the Distortion Demon Master. Ultimately, the battle reached a stalemate and they had barely stopped the Demon Master’s Void Armies from advancing their invasion.

Under these circumstances, the Church Pantheon basically did not have the power to deal with Garen. They had no choice but to let the Dragon Clan Alliance to handle the situation.

The death from the war spread across the world as it covered the sky.

The True Souls and Demon Masters started to come out from the Distorted Void Crevice. The majority of the True Souls and Demon Masters did not belong to any organization. They were merely here to kill and increase their own strengths.

These monsters were even more terrifying than the Disaster of Dragons. They killed everything wherever they went as they did not want any witnesses to tell the tale. These massacres were similar to swallowing everything up as even their souls were not spared during the massacres.

Hence, these had caused a huge discontent from the Abyss and Hell.

The rumors of the Child of Hell has started to spread across the globe as a solid line of defense that spanned hundreds of kilometers was swiftly formed. This divine defensive line was very effective in preventing the advancement of the Void Creatures. As the Gods joined forces to cast an extremely huge Void Detection Spell and an actual Higher Divine Soul had descended into the mortal realm.

The God of the Sun, Osiris had brought his Blazing Legion from the Heavens. His Divine Kingdom could be seen through a portal which appeared just behind the divine defensive line. A swarm of Blazing Angels flew out of the entrance as they joined in the intense battle against the Void Creatures.

Garen, on the other hand, was currently in a district just outside of the divine defensive line, which was located within the swarm of Void Creatures.

The battle became more chaotic as death and blood spread about. The majority of the people in many cities started to flee. The number of people fleeing from the city grew further as the size of the city increased.

Many Teleportation Portals appeared on the Primary Plane as the Gods opened up the channels connecting the Upper Inner Plane to the Primary Plane. Countless of Elemental Armies, a variety of legions from different factions, Heavenly Creatures, Hell Creatures, Abyss Armies, and so on gushed out from the portals.

All of them had joined in the battle against the Void Creatures.

As Garen was wreaking havoc and searching for the Fragments of the Inspired Soul, the local forces had gained a slight advantage in the battlefield. However, a huge number of lower level citizens were massacred by the Void Creatures, causing a reduction in production as many cultivated lands were left unmanned. Hence, this had caused the gradual disappearance in logistics as well.

The number of humans was drastically reduced in this chaos and what had replaced them were the main clans from the higher plane. One of them that had become the majority was the armies of different layers from the Abyss and Hell.

The reincarnation of the Gods, Demon Masters, True Souls, Thane of Hell, and the Thane of Abyss. All of them whose existence only seen in the form of names in the ancient records had started appearing. They appeared in the Primary Plane as they killed each other in the sky, throwing the entire Primary Plane into blood and fire.

*************

An incredible huge grey snake’s corpse was floating in the evening sky.

The snake covered half of the sky. Two bloody sockets were left behind as the eyes had been taken out. Its body was filled with densely packed white thorns and some of these thorns had already snapped in half.

It was still oozing out black gas around its body and this had frightened other living beings from getting near to its corpse.

Garen lowered his head as he looked away.

He quietly avoided the forces that way after him as he arrived at an inconspicuous area.

It was a coastline by the south.

A huge battle had just occurred here recently and that huge snake corpse which had covered half of the entire sky was the corpse of the True Soul which had fallen here. Its corpse was still oozing out a horrifying deadly aura even though it was dead for dozens of days. Any living being which had been infected by it would immediately grow old and die.

Garen strolled about alone by the port of the completely silent Crystal City.

This city was already dead as it was covered by the auras of True Souls and Gods during their battles here. All beings of Level Eight and below were instantly killed.

“Two Demon Masters and one True Soul had fallen here. Naturally, our battle result is glorious as well since we’ve managed to kill five Divine Souls and one of them was a Middle God.” A voice of a young woman appeared beside Garen’s ears. “We’re responsible in cleaning up the aftermath. The Soul Fragments you’re searching fall does not lie here and even if it does, it has already been taken as well. However, this is the best place to obtain the inspiration of the Death and Decaying Divinity as the Divine Souls, True Souls, and Demon Masters who had fallen here are related to the two Divinities.”

“Thanks.” Garen nodded. The one who spoke to him was one of the Demon Masters of the Mother Stream Alliance responsible in this region. He found out about this place and purposely came here in hope to obtain some gains as he had received intel from the Snake Princess.

He had massacred over fifty thousand lives. Garen’s reputation had spread across the entire northern region as he became one of the strongest Demon Masters. Although he was still not the strongest, he was the most discreet when it came to killing. His melody of massacre did not contain any signs of spell as he would be able to force countless of people to commit suicide purely by sound hypnosis.

This was the main reason he became notorious.

“Alright. I’ll mind my own business and you should as well,” Garen replied softly.

“It’s nothing. I should be thanking you for giving me more work.” The woman started to laugh softly as her voice gradually faded.

At the port of the Crystal City, the most famous landmark building was the gigantic glass tower located at the center of the port.

It was the Wizard Tower that controlled the entire city’s central region, the Crystal Tower. It was managed by the City Master who was a Level Fifteen Great Arcanist.

Garen looked over at the Crystal Tower which looked like a broken wooden stick as the top half had already fallen onto the abandoned buildings beside it.

It looked like it was broken beyond repair.

It was also the place where the presence of Divinity was the strongest.

He blinked his eyes.

“Let’s do it.”

‘Beginning to scan for traces of Divine Power…” His consciousness had finally able to create an effect towards the external surrounding.

Its sensation surpassed Garen’s by dozens of magnitude as it utilized Garen’s current sensation and response towards the traces of spells.

It was able to quickly find any clues no matter how subtle it was.

Garen walked slowly towards the Crystal Tower in this ruins.

Both sides were filled with the lifeless white buildings which the majority of them had spired at the very top. The body of the buildings was filled with dome-shaped windows and the streets beside them were filled with the wilted corpses, shirts, broken stone or copper sculptures and so on.

As he walked past a pond, he could see it was polluted with black and rancid fluid. The birds which had died and floated in the pond did not have any maggots or flies feasting on their carcasses.

‘Traces of Death Divinity has been detected… Divinity Radiation Level 11%… 15%…’

Garen stopped moving as he pondered for a while before moving on.

‘Radiation is increasing… 21%… 27%… 30%.”

Garen halted once more. He raised his hands and he could see traces of his skin wilting. What was originally a well-stacked skin had started to wrinkle.

“What powerful energy… To be able to affect me in such a huge manner even when the battle has ended long ago. It is truly a battle of the True Soul Level.” Garen gasped.

“This place should be able to increase my deconstruction of the Decaying Divinity.” Garen sat on his knees.

He sat quietly as he felt the remaining residue of the energy and its aura.

His brain then started to compute at high speed.

Garen’s Soul Limit had already reached two hundred and sixty points. The Despair Skull had given him Potential Points as it absorbed the souls whereas the Death Bracelet had absorbed the fragments while providing him Soul Seeds and Soul Energy.

Both were able to bring out the best in each other.

The first thing Garen increased was his Intelligence as it was the key in his brain’s computing power. Two hundred and sixty points worth of Intelligence would provide him an incredible fast computing power.

The deconstruction of the Decaying Divinity had reached the critical stage. If he were to succeed, he would be able to fully understand the root of decomposition and construct a Divine Persona based on the decomposition.

“Perhaps the other Demon Masters have their ways in dissecting this issue, they definitely don’t have the computing ability that is as advanced as mine. My computing power is countless times faster than theirs and even I need such a long time to barely able to deconstruct a rather reclusive Divinity. If it were them…” Garen’s method was completely unique and inimitable.

He loosened up and emptied his mind as he focused his energy on his computing power.

“What a chaotic era…”

Garen gave off a gentle sigh as the Enneahedron in front of his chest shattered, forming into pure energy that had entered his brain.

It was one of the ways to use the Enneahedron. This pure energy could be used to evolve or increase any aspect of his body, including computing power.

The energy of fifty thousand living beings that were massacred instantly nourished Garen’s brain to the point where veins started popping up on his face.

Buzz!

A black halo slowly appeared behind Garen’s head. The halo contained countless algorithms that were densely packed together as it started to spin slowly.

‘Obtained an unknown source of energy, computing power is now greatly enhanced…” A message appeared in his mind and it was immediately dismissed.

The black halo behind Garen’s head started to spin faster over time.

Pew pew pew!!

Suddenly, the halo gave off a big amount of black rays as they spread across all directions. These streaks of light were like iron as it penetrated through the grounds and Voids.

It then started to absorb the surrounding nutrients like a giant tree’s root.

As Garen saw this, his slightly surprised and pondering expressions were written all over his face.

He then shut his eyes and immersed himself into computing once more.

As he took his posture, he had sat down for ten days.

Chapter 1361: Collaboration 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the pitch-black Abyss

“Ann, everything’s been properly arranged,” said a blonde-haired woman dressed in red softly, floating in front of Ann.

“Are all the fifteen nodes we set up in the north complete?” Ann’s back was facing the woman as she played with a dagger with a black handle that glowed with a faint silver light. An indiscernible red light flashed across the dagger occasionally.

“It’s complete. Each of the fifteen nodes will be guarded by a Demigod,” the woman replied hurriedly.

Ann turned around, frowning.

“It’s too bad that you’re the only one under my wing that I can use, Mura and the others left too soon… They couldn’t even wait for my reappearance.”

“Even with your mighty abilities, milady, there’s no way you could have saved them. That’s the inevitability of time…” The woman’s expression had a hint of melancholy as well.

Ann was the leader of the strongest Dragons of Disaster, the Three Monarchs, so she would naturally have extremely powerful forces under her command. At first, she had five Dragons of Disaster with the power of Lower Gods as her generals, but now this woman was the only one left. The incomparably powerful and glorious sect from back then was now reduced to slightly over twenty Demigod-level powerhouses. As for those below Demigod-level, they were practically negligible.

“I’ve contacted some people, it all depends on how the general situation goes. Even if I don’t have many people, I still need to make my move. This is the best time right now,” said Ann calmly.

“The time?”

“One week from now…” Ann raised her head and looked at a certain direction. Her gaze seemed to penetrate countless barriers, finding a powerful being hiding in the darkness. “He can’t escape…”

******************

Garen woke from his immersion.

He glanced at the time, and the timekeeper in his Willpower Neuroprocessor told him that it had been more than ten days since he began his immersion.

Without knowing it, he had noticed that black circle of light that grew ever more complicated and sophisticated at the back of his mind. It was something like a ring of light, and inside it, there was a large amount of data and many runes, flowing, moving, and computing. The carving of most of the patterns and runes around the ring of light had been completed, but there was still a small section that had yet to be done.

“A Decay Divine Persona, is it?” Garen reached his senses toward the thing his Willpower Neuroprocessor had created using that wisp of Divinity. He had never seen a Divine Persona before, but that did not mean he could not find out what ring of light actually was.

He used more than twenty years and most of the computing power in his Neuroprocessor, and now that he had finally gotten this thing as a result, it had to be related to a Divine Persona somehow.

“A Divine Persona is the final product of Divinity lit up with sacred fire, and it can use the Divine Domain to convert Divine Power. It requires the input of everything, the soul and the Willpower. Right now, I’m still a single independent unit, so I clearly don’t count as a Divine Persona. In that case, what is this thing?” Garen observed the black circle of light behind him, somewhat confused.

This thing was emitting many black silk threads, absorbing a special something that felt like Soul Energy from the Void surrounding him, as though they were so many tree roots.

The thing that was being absorbed came with hints of terror, fear, hatred, antagonism and other similar emotions. Clearly, this was the power of fear and respect unique to Dragons of Disaster.

“What do I represent?”

Garen frowned slightly.

“What do those who treat me as their enemy see me as?”

As soon as that question rose from his heart, it was as though he could instantly hear a great many different voices.

“Cold Winter Dragon, I curse you! May you be confined and tortured forever in the bottomless Abyss.”

“The Lord of Hell will someday tear off your skin and flesh, drying them out the gates of hell!!”

“I will get my revenge! Someday, I’ll kill you!!”

“Cold Winter Dragon, I want your life in exchange for my son’s!!!”

Countless voices surged up from the bottom of his heart.

Garen watched these voices quietly. It was strange, to be hated by so many survivors. It was his first time feeling something like this.

Other than that, there was also the power of worship from those who feared him. These beliefs were much simpler, mostly they just involved praying that he would not appear and spread the Wintry Death.

“Looks like this thing truly is a semi-completed product. It’s just that I’ve yet to properly decide what I represent.” Garen understood now.

Ann represented time and shadow, so her Divine Persona will convert all the power of fear and worship into Divine Power of time and shadow, or rather, the power of Disaster.

“The Divinity and Divine Persona I have constructed are based mainly on Decay, so I’ll temporarily set my position as Decay for now.” Garen mused over it for a while, and directly decided on this rarer Divine Doman.

‘Confirming the Divine Domain… Initial determination — Decay. Includes rotting, wasting away, and can extend to aging and death as a result of the passage of time.’

The Willpower Neuroprocessor instantly gave him a response.

The instant he decided on his Divine Domain, Garen abruptly felt his body shudder. The ring of black light behind his back began to tremor abruptly, rapidly finishing up the remaining incomplete patterns and runes. Within a few dozen seconds, the whole circle was utterly complete.

Once the ring was complete, it looked just like a wheel of burning flames wrapped around a large ring. Many dots of black light spread and scattered from the edges of the ring. It looked eerie and creepy.

Mysteriously, Garen could vaguely feel a powerful gaze staring at him from across the endless distance.

That gaze was icy cold and emotionless, and carried with it the aura of death. Even the faraway distance could not hinder its penetrating stare.

“The God of Death… Did the overlap in our Divine Domains result in a conflict over the worship power?” Garen’s heart gave a jolt. He knew that the Divine Domain he had settled on probably overlapped with that of the God of Death, and in that case, there would surely be a divine battle to fight over that Divine Domain.

“I just only determined my Divine Domain and I haven’t accumulated enough Divine Power yet. Looks like I’d better stay out of the way for now…” An intense wariness rose in Garen’s heart.

The God of Death was a true Higher God, in name and in power, and was one of the more formidable presences even among the Divine Systems. Going head-on against him would not end well at all.

When that thought occurred to him, the ring of black flames behind him automatically hid itself, but he could still feel those many root-like black threads connecting him to those lives and souls that feared or hated him. They were still providing him with an endless supply of that immense worship power.

And this power of worship was also flowing like a stream into his Divine Persona, before it was converted into wisps of energy like black threads, merging into his Soul Ring structure.

‘Now condensing tragedy power, please select: One, store and increase your Divine Persona. Two: use immediately to power up yourself.’ A message came from the Willpower Neuroprocessor.

Garen glanced at his current level.

‘Divine Persona: 1.’ It was standard, weak Divine Power.

“I can even use it to strengthen myself directly?” He had not expected it to have this ability. Usually, Divine Power was mainly used for consumption, as well as to accumulate and increase the level of one’s Divine Persona. The stronger the Divine Persona level, the more Divine Arts one would be able to use to respond to one’s worshippers, and the more power and authority one would have.

Garen carefully looked through his current status.

‘Garen — Strength 260, Agility 260, Vitality 260, Intelligence 260. Potential 12829%. Soul Limit 000.

8 Soul Rings: Five Colorless, Red, Orange, Red.

Level 10 Draconic Aura. Level 10 Arcane Art.

‘Potential Quality — Divine Creature, Void Pursuer’

Void Original Opus — 70%. Hind leg — Evil Soldier, wings — Seven Lives, tail — Demonic Book.

Overall comments — God of Decay: Divine Persona 1. Title — Winter Sigh.’

“My Soul Limit has turned to 0?” Garen was slightly taken aback and then overjoyed.

He sensed his current condition carefully, and felt as though the converted Decay Divine Power had directly turned into a thin membrane that covered the surface of his body. This membrane was even growing ever stronger as more Divine Power was converted.

“This should be the so-called Divine Power Shield, looks like most Gods rely on their Divine Power as a protective force field. To them, Divine Power was more like a layer of natural armor, armor that could withstand attack. It only needed to consume a certain amount of their Divine Power.

Garen quickly came to a mental conclusion.

“As for the strengthening and leveling up of the Gods’ own true bodies, almost no books mention it at all. I couldn’t even find any mention of Gods powering up their own bodies and 神体 Divine Bodies in Ann’s books. Mostly, they just assimilated and evolved gradually alongside their Divine Power, until they finally become one with their Divine Power, their bodies turning into the incarnation of their ocean of Divine Power.”

“On the other hand, True Soul Demon Masters simply use all their power to strengthen their own bodies. Looks like the two options the Willpower Neuroprocessor gave me act as the boundary line between True Souls and Gods…”

Garen’s heart instantly became clear.

“If I choose to accumulate, the Divine Power will automatically turn into a Divine Power Shield, that’s the God Route. If I choose to strengthen, then that’s the True Soul Route.”

Naturally, there was no hesitation at all here.

Garen went straight for strengthening. Although the Gods were strong, they were also extremely limited by their own worship power. It was fine when they had plenty of worship power, but if ever that was reduced, their Divine Persona’s level would drop, and they would be affected instead. On the other hand, the True Souls just used all their power to strengthen their own Elements. There was no chance of outside interference.

It was clear at a glance, which one was better.

This was also the crucial reason why the Gods in this world grew weaker as they fought more wars, because the regular civilians and worshippers were being massacred in large numbers. This was the source of their Divine Power.

‘Select Strengthening.’

As soon as Garen decided on an answer.

Instantly, that thin layer of Divine Power began to be slowly absorbed by Garen’s Instinct.

Garen’s current body had the terrifying Devouring Instinct of the Hellfrost Peacock Queen, so unless he purposely held back from devouring something, any energy that got too close to him would all be absorbed and devoured by that Instinct.

“The Gods don’t have a Soul Limit, probably as a result of the unique nature of their souls. I have the characteristics of both a God and a True Soul, so I might probably be an extreme minority in this world…” Garen guessed.

From now on, he was also a God with a little Divine Power, albeit an extremely weak one.

But without the restriction of a Soul Limit, he could practically increase his own attributes endlessly.

He gave his Semi-Divine Weapon, the Despair Skull, a quick glance and made some rough calculations. He still had a couple thousand Potential Points left.

Without a shred of hesitation, he activated the Devouring Instinct directly, beginning to absorb the Potential Points inside freely. At the same time, his Willpower Neuroprocessor automatically converted them into Intelligence.

That was right, he did not increase any other attribute first, but went straight for Intelligence, the one that he had increased first earlier.

Without the attribute limit, he immediately increased his Intelligence first, as it was the most crucial to his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

His Intelligence decided how fast his Willpower Neuroprocessor could analyze divinity, and it also decided the speed of his Divine Power conversion via his Divine Persona.

Divine Power had to be accumulated across time, from the creatures who worshipped him, so it could only be gathered through plundering. Soon enough, he was going to join Ann’s raid operation, so Garen was already planning to make the biggest preparation in anticipation of this operation.

“Now, it’s about time I got started on Ann’s matters.” Garen organized the information he had about the True Soul Demon Masters.

He got up and instantly vanished from the spot.

*******************

“A raid?” The Deception Demon Master looked at Garen in the Water Mirror lazily. She was lying on her side in a black palace, surrounded by pools of blood, corpses, and skeletons everywhere. It was clear that she was slaughtering some God’s temple.

“The God of Time and Shadow, that fellow’s not easy to deal with…” The Deception Demon Master frowned. “The point is, what do I get in return?”

“Ann just wants the Time Divine Persona, and we can split the remaining Divine Personas, according to how much power we contribute,” Garen explained. The first one he went to was the Deception Demon Master, because she was the closest to him, after all.

“You just entered the God level and already you dare to participate in a raid of this level? Casavon’s Divine Kingdom is no joke, y’know? After that Divine Kingdom was increased, a ton of Holy Spirits reached Demigod Level, they could crush you just by piling on top of you,” said the Deception Demon Master, confused.

Chapter 1362: Collaboration 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Naturally, I have my own plans.” Garen did not explain. The truth was he never wanted most of the Divine Persona, he just wanted to obtain a wisp of the Death divinity. Just a wisp of divinity, and his Willpower Processor would be able to make that into a complete Divine Persona. That was why his needs did not conflict with Ann and the others, who were fighting, at all.

At the most, he would ask for a few Divine Crystals. Those were made by condensing pure Divine Power, and that just happened to be what he needed right now.

“Okay, it just so happens that we need an overwhelming victory to settle the score over here as well. The way the Sun God killed the King of Enzo gave us quite the blow…” said the Deception Demon Master with a cold laugh. “I hear that they’re raising some Child of Radiance, hehe. They’re gathering all of their divine authority and power into one Incarnation in the hopes of fighting against our rapid approach.”

“The Child of Radiance, the Child of Hell, they’re all just their means of fighting back,” said Garen offhandedly. “Alright, then, I’ll go contact the other Demon Masters and True Souls. Of course, if you could contact some other helpers as well, it would be better if we had more assurance of safety.”

“Mm.” The Deception Demon Master’s attitude toward Garen had changed as well. Although Garen was still very weak, he was already a God in every way and form. He was, in essence, the same as level as her, so her manner of speed was much more equal now.

The Water Mirror vanished, and the Deception Demon Master touched her chin.

“I wonder how this guy leveled up. It’s not been that long since we last met, and he’s already on his way to becoming a God?”

“I’ve been a Demigod for so many years, and yet I still lack that most crucial step,” said Kunder with a sigh, walking out of the darkness. “After deciding on a Divine Domain, you’d still need to accumulate worship power, gathering it up to light up the sacred fire before you can build your own Divine Kingdom. He’s already halfway through that…”

“Yeah… Although it’s not complete by any means, he already has worship power. Now all he has to do is withstand the killer pursuit of any Gods whose Divine Domain overlaps with his, and he’ll be able to light up his sacred fire steadily, forming his very own Divine God. He has to use the energy provided by the illumination of the sacred fire to support the operations of his Divine Kingdom. This’s an inevitable process.”

The Deception Demon Master’s expression was one of admiration.

“The Divine Soul System of this world is just a shortcut that speeds up the strengthening speed by gathering the power of all creatures. It’s much, much faster than how we had to bust our backs and gather every ounce of power ourselves from the bottom up. In just a moment, he’s finished walking the path we took several millennia to cross.”

“But there’s a huge flaw as well, taking a shortcut means paying a price.” Kunder shook his head.

“That’s right…” The Deception Demon Master did not say any more. “A price…”

***********************

The Earth Demon Palace

There were countless black smoke figures floating everywhere, crowding in every inch of the ancient and evil grand hall. They danced, baring their fangs and claws like evil ghosts and demons, some notes of an eerie and cruel music slowly spreading from the Void in accompaniment with the dance of the black smoke figures.

Above the grand hall, a man with a strong body and a scorpion head sat crookedly on a tall and large throne. He tapped the armrest lightly in time with the music, seemingly rather engrossed in it.

After Garen powered up, this was the nearest Demon Master’s Demon Palace — the Earth Demon Palace.

Its owner was a powerful Demon Master from the Void, the Scorpion-Headed Human, Jirhas. He was in charge of the cleanliness and security of this area, and operated under the name of the Distortion Demon Master.

“What an impressive song and dance.” Garen clapped his hands lightly, sitting at the VIP seat on Jirhas’ right. Although he had no idea what was so attractive about this ghostly song and dance number, he still knew how to say a few praises to fulfill the most basic manners.

“Does Her Highness Ann have such performances at her place as well?” Jirhas asked with a laugh, looking at Garen sideways.

“Naturally, my master has no such thing. Perhaps only your place would have such a unique song and dance, Demon Master Jir,” said Garen respectfully.

“Of course.” Jir nodded. “I understand what you mean, we have always communicated and cared about Her Highness Ann to a certain degree. Since she’s one of the few powerful existences in this world with the same needs and interests as us, we’ve always placed much importance in Her Highness Ann’s potential.”

He stretched out his hand, and a black wine glass appeared, floating above his palm. He sipped some wine from it lightly.

“Regarding this matter, it’s a rare moment when we all share a common goal and interest, so cooperation would not be a problem. However…”

He paused.

“However, what?” Garen’s expression did not change as he waited for Jirhas to continue.

“However, Her Highness Ann still belongs to a different camp, after all. My master’s always wary of outsiders to a certain extent.” The Scorpion-Headed Man gave an eerie smile. “If the one we’re working with is you, however, perhaps that will put our hearts at more ease…”

They had done their research on Garen’s roots, he was a textbook example of a Void being with a proper background and a bright future ahead. Each trace of the Secret Techniques on his body was an extremely pure example of a Void Demon Lord’s foundations. Besides, his progress speed was much faster than most Demon Lords, he had only taken a few years to go from a middle-level Demon Lord to almost becoming a God. After all, the God level was a peak-level existence, just like Demon Masters and True Souls. At this point, he was basically at the pinnacle of two worlds now.

The only difference in strength now was the comparison within the same level.

Garen frowned slightly and did not continue that thought.

The Scorpion-Headed Man, Jir, did not seem particularly bothered.

“As long as you’re willing, we can make all the proper arrangements. You just have to coordinate with us from the inside, and it won’t be that hard at all to take down the entire Dragons of Disaster party.”

Garen understood what he was getting at now. They were actually dissatisfied with Ann and were looking for another being that they could support as her replacement.

“Sorry, I…”

“There’s no rush. Take your time and think it over. Her Highness just rendezvoused with us recently, but we were very disappointed in her performance. She’s already lost the necessary will to push forward. Instead, she actually said that she wanted to retire to another plane once she was free of the seal…” Jir shook his head, his expression slightly taunting.

“She actually wants to retire in the middle of an era as great as this?”

Garen’s heart gave a jolt. Clearly, the situation right now was that the Void Creatures were unhappy with Ann’s pacifist attitude. For all he knew, they were already secretly supporting another existence, hoping to replace her.

Now, they wanted him to cooperate with them, probably to increase their chances of success and reduce the degree of uncertainty.

He did not doubt the power of the Void at all. The Distortion Demon Master was a peak-level Demon Master that could fight even Fehra head-on, so in this world, the Demon Master was considered as powerful as the strongest powerhouses among those with the truly powerful Divine Power.

“No need to worry, our Mother Stream Alliance has a few Gods as well, their Divine Personas were all formed by killing and devouring middle-level Divine Souls in the middle of the wars. They’re powerful enough, but without a Dragon of Disaster, there’s no way to lead this group. Her Highness Ann can mobilize many Dragons of Disaster and have them fight in a group, so she’s a partner that we really need to work with,” consoled Jir.

“No matter what, this raid is a compulsory chance for our camp to fight back, so we hope you can participate in it.” Garen stayed silent for a while and then stood up.

“As for my Master’s matters, I hope you guys can continue observing for a while longer. Perhaps you will notice some other changes.”

“I’ll join the raid, but as for changes… Here’s to hoping.” Jir waved his hand nonchalantly. “In that case, goodbye.”

“Goodbye.” Garen’s figure disappeared abruptly.

Jir was not worried that Garen would tell Ann at all. From what he could see, Garen and Ann were not all that close, and besides, Ann probably had an idea about what they were thinking to some extent. It did not matter whether she knew or not, now that Ann was being repelled by the Gods, even if she wanted to hide and avoid them, where could she run to?

**************

Garen’s figure appeared on some black plains. There was not a blade of grass growing anywhere around him, but instead, there were black stone shards everywhere, evenly spread out on the ground.

This was the teleportation point marker he had left here in advance. It was less a thousand kilometers away from the clan he was returning to.

The sky was covered in dark clouds, as though it was going to rain soon. Occasionally, he could hear the rumbling of thunder coming from the clouds.

After he received that information from the Demon Master Jir, Garen’s feelings were rather complicated as well. It seemed that there was a huge rift and conflict between Ann and the Void.

He was stuck in the middle and it made things very awkward for him.

He wanted to reduce and resolve this problem, but it was slightly frustrating. He could not change Ann’s decisions, and the will of the representative from the Mother Stream Alliance was also unacceptably strong.

“In the end, my power still isn’t enough!” Garen frowned slightly. Ann saved his life before, so no matter what, he could not let the Mother Stream Alliance use him to take her down. On the other hand, he would definitely offend the incomparably powerful Mother Stream Alliance. In that case, be it himself or Ann, they would probably face an even more troublesome ending if they went against the Demon Masters from the Mother Stream Alliance, resulting in the Demon Masters’ embarrassment turning to fury.

“How do I find a middle point…” For a moment, Garen was frustrated as well.

Whoosh…

Suddenly, a mysterious cold breeze blew past him. Garen vaguely sensed something strange.

All of a sudden, the alarm bells in his heart went off, and he immediately moved, disappearing from the spot and reappearing somewhere nearby, several hundred meters away.

Barroom!!

The place he was just standing at had abruptly turned into a sea of ice crystals. The surface of the plains within several dozen meters had completely frozen over.

A large White Dragon, more than twenty meters long, rose gradually from the surface of the ice. It was as though he had crawled out of a deep well, his claws digging into the ground and forcefully pulling out the lower half of his body.

The dragon scales all over this White Dragon’s body glowed with a hint of platinum, and he had a crystal-clear diamond-shaped crystal embedded into his brow. On his head, he wore a platinum crown, and it was as though the stars and the clouds were constantly reflected, rippling in his gaze. It was a scene as beautiful as the Milky Way.

Roar!!

The White Dragon roared madly at Garen’s direction, an immense and powerful energy force spreading around.

“Garen! You killed the Elders, resisted against Her Highness Tiamat’s Incarnation, and killed your innocent relatives from the White Dragon Mountain. Today, all of your crimes will be completely judged and concluded right here!!”

“White Dragon King, rather than staying in the Abyss, you actually dare to run out here in pursuit of me?” Garen’s expression was dark. “Aren’t you afraid of dying outside, resulting in the White Dragon Mountain losing even a land for them to rest?”

“With your powers?” The White Dragon King laughed wildly. “Upon mine body, God descends!!”

He spread open his wings, and his entire body abruptly emitted an intense white light.

‘Warning, warning, you have entered the vicinity of a Holy Aura. Beginning identification of Tiamat’s Holy Aura, Divine Creatures cannot be identified, identification failed… Vitality Identification passed, removes effect of the Holy Aura.’

A large amount of information instantly came from his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

Garen frowned. This time, Tiamat had clearly descended here using her own Incarnation. Even with his divinity and Divine Persona, his Divine Power was still weak, and it actually could not make him immune to the effects. Thankfully his Vitality was too powerful, the slaughtering over the past period of time had accumulated and resulted in up to 260 points in his terrifying Vitality stat. Almost no creature in this world could surpass him now. It was the perfect chance to see how much more powerful he was after condensing his Divine Persona!

“The last time I was completely suppressed by you, but let’s see who suppresses whom this time.” Garen’s expression did not change as he pounced forward, his entire body instantly ballooning into a giant White Dragon.

The three pairs of wings on his back unfurled slowly, the countless green eyes covering every inch of his six wings opening with an aura of unbelievable evil. As though to accompany those eerie compound eyes, an overwhelming and decaying aura began to permeate through the air.

Boom!!

The White Dragon King abruptly sprayed five-colored Dragon Breath out of his mouth, crashing hard into Garen’s body as the latter was shooting through the air toward him.

Chapter 1363: Incarnation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Burning heat, chilling cold, powerful poison, numbing itchiness, and lightning. Different types of Dragon Breath energy crashed into Garen’s body hard with a huge momentum.

Along with the Dragon Breath, the White Dragon King, Tiamat’s Incarnation, pounced mercilessly, pressing down on Garen and trying to use his immense power to suppress him.

The dragon scales all over Garen’s body began to melt, but he paid them no heed. He rushed straight through the Dragon Breath, taking it head-on, and all the powerful Five-colored Dragon Breath could do was force him to close his eyes, lest they were burned.

He also had a Divine Persona now, so his resistance to Divine Power attacks had risen again. Besides, his Vitality was also much stronger now than it had been before, and the stacking of these effects had finally triggered a fundamental change. The damage the Five-colored Dragon Breath did to him was almost negligible.

“Imprisonment Spell.” Tiamat’s voice gave a screech, and suddenly a pitch-black cage enveloped Garen, who was still rushing forward. It became a black square cage.

He opened his mouth wide and bit at the cage.

Bam!!

The cage instantly shattered, and a giant dragon’s tail from within whipped Tiamat’s face hard. It sounded like a bolt of dull thunder, the giant impact creating faint space ripples in the air.

“Dragon Race Control!” Tiamat was forced to stagger by that whip, and there was instantly a large flash of golden light from his body. The Level Nine Holy Spell was cast almost instantaneously and released directly.

At his level, all Holy Spells were practically as fast as a change of his will. The only thing was that there was a limit to how many casts he had daily.

Unfortunately, while the Level Nine Dragon Race Control was a Holy Spell unique to him as the Dragon God, it still had barely any effect on Garen, whose Vitality was terrifyingly high.

He had been immune to Level Nine Spells a long time ago. It went without saying that they would not work on him now.

The misty glow formed by that golden light landed on Garen’s body and then vanished without a trace, having no effect whatsoever.

“Pollution Meteor…” Before Tiamat could finish saying the name of the spell, Garen instantly appeared before him, crashing his claws into his chest with a bam.

Bong!

Tiamat took several steps back, and his spell was also interrupted. He shook his head but was not injured at all.

A thin golden membrane had blocked off Garen’s attack, rendering Tiamat completely unharmed.

“The Divine Power Shield?” Garen raised an eyebrow and activated all of his 260-point Speed.

Swoosh!

He instantly appeared behind Tiamat’s back and whipped down hard with his tail.

The attributes of Tiamat’s Incarnation were also clearly over two hundred. He turned around immediately with decent reflexes, and four other dragon heads appeared beside his, all biting at Garen harshly.

Psst!

Garen suddenly felt an intense pain in his tail, and he moved aside, instantly and hurriedly.

Only then did he realize that his opponent had taken a small bite out of his tail. His heart turned cold, but before he could react, Tiamat moved instantaneously beside him as well, biting down hard once more.

“Since the Holy Spells don’t work on you, I’ll just use my sharpest teeth to swallow you directly!” Tiamat said, screeching with laughter.

The two giant White Dragons had practically become two balls of shadows, moving and wrestling at high speeds on the plains. Occasionally they would fly into the air, or crash down hard into the ground. Anything that would touch them now and then would instantly explode into dust, just like an illusion.

Garen could move instantaneously because of his high speed and agility, and Tiamat could perform instantaneous movements too, but he was one step faster than Garen in terms of reflexes. This was the difference in their Agility attribute.

As an Incarnation of God, only then did Garen get a deep understanding of why only Incarnations could fight Incarnations most of the time. The strength of the True Soul and God Levels lay in their bodies that had been powered up to the limit over an infinitely long period of time. Just this one Incarnation had more than two hundred points in Speed and Strength. Add that to the solid Divine Power Shield that was extremely hard to pierce through, and this was practically a fearsome, indestructible war fortress.

But the difference between them and the True Souls was that the Gods’ own increases in attributes were based on the Divine Power enveloping their bodies, whereas the True Soul Demon Lords simply relied on their own bodies.

“As I expected, you really are a Void Creature!” Tiamat sped up, chasing after Garen and laughing coldly.

“Saber of Domination!!”

Suddenly, an expanding ball of darkness exploded before him and enveloped Garen in an instant.

The giant black saber within the ball slashed at Garen soundlessly, its blade carrying a faint layer of a purple glow.

It was as though the giant saber instantly became enormous before Garen’s eyes, smashing down on him like a mountain range. It was so powerful that even Garen, with more than 260 points in Strength, felt suffocated and unable to fight back.

“Divine Persona Evolution!” Garen was shocked. Tiamat’s Persona had domination in its definition, and this ability was clearly his using the Divine Persona to mobilize the most Divine Power he could.

When he was going through Ann’s books, he had read somewhere that the Divine Persona represented Authority, and this Authority was the embodiment of the rules. Going against the Authority was going against the rules, and this was not something normal power could resist. Only Authority could resist Authority.

“Corrode!!” he roared deeply, his entire body emanating with large clouds of purple-black fog. That wheel of black light appeared behind his head directly.

The purple-black fog came into contact with the black saber head-on, and instantly, the black fog fell apart and scattered. It was because the difference between their Authorities was too large.

Disregarding the Black Fog completely, the black saber slashed onto Garen’s body mercilessly.

Rawr!!!

Amidst the howl of pain, a deep cut appeared on Garen’s body. The black saber disintegrated, and the black fog enveloping him dissipated completely as well.

“What a powerful body you have, to think you went straight up against my authority and still managed to survive!!” Smiling evilly, Tiamat began to condense the black ball of Authority once more. “How about another go, then?”

“Poisonous Eye!”

Suddenly, two dark-green rays smashed into Tiamat’s dragon head.

The speed of these rays was so fast that even he could not dodge them, despite his two hundred points in Agility. They hit him straight between his brows.

The rays actually carried the faint Authority of the Decay Divine Persona. Although Garen’s Divine Power was very weak, and the destructive power he obtained from activating his Authority was not quite enough, it was still far stronger than the previous Poisonous Eye, that had only been Level Fifteen.

As a grandmaster-level powerhouse in terms of combat and killing, Garen just had to see the way Tiamat used his power once with his Willpower Neuroprocessor, and he already understood the best way to use Divine Power to the strongest effects.

Divine Power Authority, and the Divine Power Shield, these were the Gods’ strongest spear and shield!

Tiamat was the Evil Dragon God in charge of Domination and Evil Dragons, so if the one fighting here was simply a pure-breed Evil Dragon, his power would naturally be suppressed by four or five levels. Since Garen was actually a Void Creature, he managed to avoid this form of suppression.

So the only thing that had an effect on him was the Domination aspect.

Tiamat had been just slightly careless. He did not expect Garen to learn so quickly, so he was instantly hit by the Poisonous Eye with the Decay Authority. A large hole was formed in the Divine Power Shield around the middle of his brows as a result of the corrosion, and the golden Divine Power all over his body instantly reached over to fill the gap, quickly mending the hole.

If Garen could not instantly break through the Divine Power Shield and kill the one inside, an attack of this extent on a God would only produce one result.

As long as they still had Divine Power, Gods would not fall.

“The difference in the Divine Power we’ve accumulated is too large!” Garen was shocked, and he rapidly retreated backward.

He barely avoided the Authority that fell down like a blanket. Half of his upper body was still flowing with platinum-colored blood. That terrifying cut stretched from his neck all the way to his chest, and had nearly cut a third of his body off.

“Retreat!” The idea flashed past Garen’s heart. The power of Tiamat’s Incarnation was not something he could hope to fight against right now.

Without a shred of hesitation, he turned around and teleported again, appearing immediately in the sky several hundred meters away.

“Tryna run, huh!!” Tiamat smiled sinisterly, and gave chase with his entire dragon body. To his surprise, however, Garen’s speed was actually a notch faster than his.

He could not really sense it when they were fighting in close quarters, but as soon as there was a distance between them and Garen started running, the minute difference in this attribute of theirs instantly became clear.

The two Colossal White Dragons began a high-speed chase, flashing across the sky above the black plains more than ten times within an instant, traversing several kilometers in distance.

“Poisonous Eye!”

There were two hisses through the air. Garen turned around suddenly and shot out two rays of green light from his eyes, the rays landing on Tiamat’s body as he was caught unprepared.

His Divine Power Shield gave a jolt, and another large hole was instantly torn through it, but it quickly recovered again.

Tiamat was quite shocked at first, and he paused. Immediately after, he realized that he was uninjured, and he continued to go after Garen in a rage.

The two White Dragons ran away and gave chase respectively, all the way from day to night. Time passed by slowly, and this lasted a whole six days.

They crossed the black plains, flew across vast golden deserts, and entered the sky above the massively wide ocean.

Every time his Poisonous Eyes healed, Garen would turn around and hit Tiamat with them without fail. At first, Tiamat did not even intend to chase him any longer, but Garen’s actions provoked him into continuing with the chase relentlessly and furiously.

Throughout these six days, Garen continuously used the Poisonous Eye countless times. Tiamat was just an Incarnation, after all, and he was possessing the White Dragon King’s body. Although the White Dragon King’s body was powerful, it still could not take the long-term invasion of a Divine Power that was not his own, and he finally buckled under the pressure.

**************

Above the bright blue ocean and the roiling waves, two Colossal Dragons shining with a white glow flew past the ocean at high speeds.

Psst.

Suddenly, a large crack opened up in Tiamat’s chest, spewing out white dragon blood.

“What’s this? The Incarnation of the Dragon God can’t even apprehend me, a normal White Dragon?” On cue, Garen turned around and taunted him.

“You’re asking for it!!” Tiamat raged and continued to give chase once more.

Psst psst psst!!

In an instant, several arrows of blood exploded from his body and fell into the seawater beneath him. The water instantly turned platinum in color, as did the seawater around that spot.

In front of him, Garen turned around instantly, the countless green eyes on his six wings winking deviously.

“After being chased for so long, it’s my turn now…”

He flapped his wings abruptly and actually stopped dodging, rushing straight toward Tiamat.

“Saber of Domination!!” Tiamat condensed the power from all over his body and created another black ball that enveloped Garen.

The black ball scattered, and Garen continued to rush at him, his body all covered in blood.

“Saber of…!!” Tiamat attempted to gather his Authority again, but suddenly he spewed out a mouthful of platinum-colored dragon blood.

“You’re done for!!” Garen laughed heartily as he teleported to Tiamat, his dragon claws turning into two shadows that smashed into Tiamat’s body mercilessly.

At the same time, Tiamat’s body had stiffened as a result of the backlash from the way his Authority had been interrupted, and he could not move, so this hit landed squarely on his body.

Boom!!!

A cloud of white smoke burst in the sky over the ocean, and the golden Divine Power Shield appeared once more, blocking Garen’s dragon claw.

But the immense power also caused the Shield to ripple distortedly.

Chapter 1364: Incarnation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen used all four of his limbs, all the joints all over his body instantly turning into a storm of attacks. That formidable power and speed burst forth, and he used the shock technique from the Secret Technique users to continuously emit bursts of penetration power in an attempt to destroy the insides of Tiamat’s body.

The Divine Power Shield grew gradually fainter and more distorted. Clear cracks began to appear on it.

Tiamat had been forced back several times now, and when all was said and done, this was still merely an Incarnation of his, so it was incomparable to the strength of his own true Godhead. The White Dragon King’s body was slowly growing unable to keep up, such that he did not even have the power to whip his tail in self-defense. All he could do was take one hit after another, as Garen continuously sent him flying backward over and over again.

“Poisonous Eye!!”

Two more green rays hit the front of Tiamat’s body.

Bam!!

There was an enormous sound, like glass shattering. Tiamat’s body finally collapsed under the pressure, falling apart and exploded instantly.

The limitless golden Divine Power gathered up once more, forming a golden illusion of a dragon.

“Cunning fellow! Don’t think you can get away so easily!!” Tiamat roared furiously.

“Escape?” Garen laughed coldly. “I didn’t keep you busy for so long just to escape in the end!”

Before he even finished speaking, he rushed forward, opening his dragon jaws wide.

Hiss!!

Amidst the loud devouring sounds, he swallowed all that golden Divine Power, completely unafraid of Tiamat’s possible retaliation.

“Without a body as a vessel, even Divine Power can be interrupted by the lowest level Blasphemy Priest.” Garen’s gaze grew colder. His mouth kept on swallowing the large amounts of golden Divine Power.

Tiamat knew that he was at a disadvantage now, and he struggled in frustration and anger, but it was useless. Without a body as a vessel, his Divine Power was as floaty as a lily pad without roots, unable to produce any powerful effects. It just kept being absorbed by Garen at high speeds.

As the devouring continued, his voice became smaller and dimmer.

Garen could sense limitless power coming from the devouring. His body kept expanding and growing like a balloon being inflated, and there was even a faint layer of gold forming on the surface of his body.

‘Devouring Divine Power… Devouring Divine Power… Beginning the strengthening…’

Waves of golden Divine Power were rapidly converted into pure Soul Energy, sinking into Garen’s Soul Ring structure. None of the Divine Power was stored up in order to increase his Divine Persona. Instead, Garen just used all of it to strengthen himself directly.

The texture of the Divine Power was unexpectedly strong, one wisp of the Divine Power, equal in volume, could somehow be converted into two wisps of Soul Energy.

Garen took one last merciless gulp and swallowed the illusory golden dragon before him completely. Without a hint of hesitation, he teleported away from the area, afraid to linger for even a second.

He had devoured all the Divine Power from an entire Incarnation, but Divine Power was not the only thing included in there, there was also something extremely troublesome—a part of the God’s divinity!

Tiamat’s divinity of Domination and Evil Dragons!!

It was only when Garen took that last bite and swallowed the entire Incarnation that he knew just how much he had lucked out this time. This divinity was as complete as roughly one-third of the true divinity, so he just to derive some things slightly and complete it, then he would able to form a complete Divine Persona of Evil Dragons and Domination in no time at all!

*****************

In the battlefields of the Eastern Empire

Countless flaming meteors fell from the sky, dying the sky a shade of blood-red.

Eerily, the earth beneath the flaming meteors was a sea of frozen ice. Countless blocks of ice rapidly formed Ice Elemental Giants that stood up from the ground and roared angrily into the sky.

Waves chock full of countless Void Creatures kept surging out of the many distorted purple Void Crevices. From a distance, it looked like a chute channeling rubbish as Void Creatures of all colors, creatures that could not be named, surged madly into the battlefield. They were completely unafraid of death, and under the leadership of the Demon Kings, they rushed towards the Ice Element as well as the landing spot of the flaming meteors.

On one end of the battlefield, there was a tower covered with white bone spikes. At the top of this tower, a rich-looking wife dressed in a pitch-black long dress and wearing crescent-shaped dangling earrings was looking down calmly at the battlefield where almost a million lives were killing each other.

Three large and strange monsters floated in the air behind her.

The first was a giant Three-Headed Wild Boar, the second was a white sphere that looked like a circle, but also had a clear human face on its surface.

The third was a platinum-colored metallic spraying machine, but its top half was a cow whereas its bottom half was styled after a robot. It seemed to be a powerful existence from a technological civilization.

These three powerful presences floated behind her back, watching the enormous battlefield below as well.

“Have you found him?” asked the rich lady, frowning.

“No,” said the Three-Headed Wild Boar in a deep and low voice, shaking his head. “There were no traces of the Child of Hell’s aura, it looks like he’s pretty darn good at hiding…”

“You must look beyond the surface,” said the Balloon Man with a smile.

“Do you mean you got a lead?” said the Wild Boar unhappily.

“Of course I don’t, but we have Kar, don’t we?” The White Balloon looked at the last member, the Bull-Headed Robot.

“I’ve scanned the whole area and found 132 suspicious points. Three of them may be searched,” said the Bull-Headed Robot in a low voice.

“Do it.” The rich lady glanced at him. “You’re the expert at this.”

“Understood.” The Bull-Headed Robot nodded and took one step forward.

Psst!

His arm actually pierced right through the space in front of him, wriggling into a crevice that had opened up vertically. There was a hissing sound as he pulled a blood-red figure from within, with one yank.

“The first.” The Bull-Headed Robot stuffed the blood-red figure straight into his mouth, chewing roughly a few times and swallowing.

“It’s not…”

He repeated this process a few more times. They saw him pull out a pale-red snake shadow from the Crevice and stuff it into his mouth once more.

“This isn’t the one either.”

“The third one.”

He reached out his hand again, tearing apart the Void and sticking his claw inside.

Ahhh!!!!

An abrupt, piercing, and terrifying scream came from inside, and a red figure dashed past at lightning speed, trying to escape by flying outside.

The Bull-Headed Man gave it a glance and opened his mouth slightly.

Barroom!

There was a huge sound, and it was as though his mouth had expanded several times in an instant, covering this entire piece of space completely.

That darting red figure also finally screamed out before it was swallowed up.

“This is the one…” The Bull-Headed Man began to chew roughly. “The Child of Hell…”

“How’s the taste?” asked the Balloon Man, fascinated.

“Not very good. Tastes like Purgatory, so the taste of sulfur is very strong. It’s not nice at all…” replied the Bull-Headed Man honestly.

“How disappointing…”

The Three-Headed Wild Boar let out a sharp breath.

“Let’s go.” The rich lady turned around and vanished instantly. The three Demon Lords also made their figures fade and vanish, as though they had never been there.

Nobody noticed that in a certain corner of the battlefield, a dragon shaped like a black shadow was emerging from the dark shadows.

It was quietly devouring the corpses nearby, and the aura it emitted also continued to increase slowly without stopping as it devoured more.

A flaming meteor fell from the sky and landed nearby, just enough to illuminate this small area for an instant.

The black dragon figure raised its head slightly, revealing a face Garen had once been familiar with – Reyman.

****************

Astral Space

In the Astral Space with its glorious colors that went around emanating terrifying radiation everywhere, many spheres formed from countless pieces of trash, bodies, and other miscellaneous items.

The powerful attraction and radiation filled this entire space that was in danger.

A silver-white line gradually appeared in an empty corner of the Astral Space.

The silver thread flowed down slowly, and almost seemed to print out the eerie body shape of a man. He was covered from head to toe with wounds that looked as though he had been pierced through with weapons, and some of the weapons still linger on his body. He just looked like a corpse that could not be any more dead.

The man opened his eyes and held open his palm. In the middle of his palm, there was a condensed item made from countless pitch-black mosquitos and insects. It was as though all the countless insects had gathered together to form a sphere made of insects.

“It’s about time you came in handy…” he sighed softly, lightly tossing the insect ball in his hand toward the front.

The insect ball exploded tracelessly, and now it turned into countless insects flying all over the place and scattering everywhere. It seemed that the radiation and gravity here were practically ineffective on them.

The man watched this scene quietly, until all of the bugs had flown away from the corner he was occupying.

******************

Dragon King Peak

Garen was all curled up his own dragon cave. All this golden Divine Power just kept beating, the Divine Power that had come from Tiamat was still struggling inside his body. But he had already converted most of it into Soul Energy.

Since he had the Divine Persona now, he no longer had a Soul Limit. That was why he just decided to use all the Divine Power he had just obtained from the fight against the Incarnation in order to increase his stats.

The wisps of divinity were converted into Soul Energy and then turned into Potential Points. Garen kept adding them onto his dragon body.

Right now his Soul Ring structure could not level up because he lacked inspiration, and it just so happened that out of Tiamat’s divinity that Garen had obtained that day, one part was unneeded.

He did not need the Evil Dragon divinity at all, so he just converted it into his Soul Ring.

The divinity in an Incarnation was more than he had found in the Pearl of the Temple back then. According to Garen’s initial estimates, a completed divinity could be converted into four red Soul Rings. That was quite the haul!

However, completing the divinity required some time…

“The operation has begun.”

Suddenly, Ann’s voice echoed around his dragon’s cave.

Garen opened his eerie dragon eyes with double pupils. “Understood. I’ll be there immediately.”

There was an instant flash of bright yellow across his pupils.

After he absorbed three Red Soul Rings that were converted from the completed divinity, he finally managed to condense a Level Yellow Soul Ring as well.

There was another Red Soul Ring on top of his Yellow Ring, too. That made nine Soul Rings in total, standing in the Soul Space like a tall tower.

Garen could clearly feel changes happening in his body, but he could not tell exactly what these changes were. It was a strange, imperceptible feeling.

Even so, it was obvious that he had an instinct. He felt as though he could enter Dream Space directly with his body, as though his body could shift and weave through the semi-dreams and semi-reality.

This was a very strange ability.

He did not know what this ability was actually useful for, but clearly its most basic function was to avoid attacks.

He could use his actual body to leap into the Dreamland and then instantly jump out again. With this method, he could avoid any would-be fatal hits. He also vaguely sensed that this ability seemed to have something to do with the rules of conversion between the material and the spiritual. After all, the Dreamland was purely a Spiritual Space.

As he got up from the ground, the golden Divine Power all over Garen’s body retreated rapidly, as though he had gone back to being the normal White Dragon he used to be.

When he walked out of the dragon cave, two Adult White Dragon guards who were standing at the entrance bowed at him slightly.

“I’m going out for a bit. If anything happens, get Annie to solve it.” Annie was the White Dragon who had protected him way back when he headed for the Snow City. Although her personal life was a mess, she was very powerful.

“Yes.”

“If anyone comes from the White Dragon Mountain, tell them to wait for me to come back.” Garen left those last words and then flapped his wings, instantly vanishing from the spot.

Chapter 1365: Hunt 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Standing at the peak of the snowy mountain, Garen pulled back his wings and looked at the lake on top of an extinct volcano in the distance. Over there, he could vaguely see three figures standing there, all of different colors.

The woman surrounded in black was Ann, the woman in purple was the Deception Demon Master, and there was a Scorpion-Headed Man there as well, the Earth Demon Master.

All three of them were surrounded by a naturally-occurring yet terrifying glow of energy. That was the Radiance of God that they made absolutely no effort to hide, a phenomenon naturally derived from their essence as a result of their bodies reaching the True Soul Level.

This was a battle between True Souls. As of right now, Garen did not yet have the right to participate in a battle of this level.

After all, even Tiamat was just a Lower God, and this time, he might very likely have to face multiple Gods with Middle-Level Divine Power. Although it was only a one-level difference, such a distance still meant that even two Lower Gods may not be able to defeat one Middle God. Gods such as the God of Time and Shadow were also particularly adept at battle, so there was an extra multiplier there as well.

That was why Garen had been arranged to watch from the distant sidelines, and placed in charge of sweeping other Demigods or Holy Spirits.

That suited Garen just well, since he was not particularly interested in a complete divinity. He just needed one wisp of divinity, and then he could perfect himself, eventually absorbing it and converting it into his Soul Ring. If he had enough Divine Power, then all he needed was to determine his Divine Domain, and he would be able to condense a Divine Persona. To Garen as he was now, that was not particularly difficult.

“Still not here yet?” Garen frowned slightly. They had been waiting in this state for three days now, but Casavon, the God of Time and Shadow whom they were expecting had yet to make an appearance.

Garen came here in order to steal many different types of divinities. As long as he had enough divinity, he just had to use a little more time and he would soon have even more Soul Rings.

Garen waited patiently and glanced at the color of the sky.

The sky was slightly grey and dreary, the heavy layer of clouds threatening to pour at any moment.

Occasionally, a herd of black migratory birds would fly here from the distance, flitting past volcano the lake. They did not notice the three terrifying presences beneath them at all.

“He’s here.”

Suddenly, Ann’s voice spoke by his ear.

Garen’s entire body stiffened, and he hurriedly pulled back his aura.

He looked into the distant sky beside him. A Three-Eyed Grey Dragon with golden wings had appeared there. It had a large stomach, and like a snake, its tongue was extremely long and red. However, its skin was stone-grey.

“Golden-Winged Dragon Mother, get ready.” Garen recognized her, this grey-colored three-eyed Colossal Dragon was Ann’s other student, so she was Garen’s senior sister in a sense. She had been following Ann for a long, long time before Garen was.

“I’ll take left and you go right. There are others in charge of the other two sides.”

The Golden-Winged Dragon Mother spoke in a quiet voice.

“Understood.”

Garen nodded and instantly flashed a few times with her, until both appeared in the sky above the volcano lake, taking left and right respectively.

At the same time, two others appeared in front of and behind the volcano lake, dressed in black clothes, their faces hidden.

The four of them promptly formed a square formation, surrounding the volcano lake.

Red light glowed from all four of their bodies at the same time.

The red light grew more and more intense, shining wider and wider, until they rapidly spread and wove together, forming a large and dense red net in the sky above the volcano lake.

The large net was several dozen kilometers in width, enveloping all the space around them completely and resulting in a blood-colored web ball.

“Maintain for ten minutes,” said the Deception Demon Master’s voice.

Barroom!

The corner of the blood-colored web that Garen grabbed with both claws abruptly gave a huge jolt, as though something had happened inside. He applied some force mercilessly, steadying the net he held in his claws.

The other three probably did the same as well.

The ball of net shook for a while and then rapidly fell silent as well.

But Garen was astute enough to notice that large flocks of Colossal Fire Birds were slowly appearing behind him.

These Colossal Birds were burning completely from head to toe. Their eyes were like emeralds as they all rushed toward his back.

Caw caw caw…!!

Amidst the sharp cries of the birds, Garen flapped his wings once. An invisible circular territory of intense poison spread out wide. His unique Natural Poison Region was like a membrane of transparent fog that could not be seen with the naked eye, slowly reaching out.

The fog of the Poison Region enveloped the flocks of Fire Birds, and instantly, the flames burning all over bodies of the many Fire Birds became fainter and smaller.

Their cries became hoarse, their flames growing smaller and dimmer, until finally they fell from the sky like so many dumplings.

“Ann!! How dare you…” Suddenly, a menacing man’s voice came from within the ball of net, sounding blurry and hoarse, as though it came from an extremely long distance away.

The ball of net began to shake violently, as though there was something inside trying to fight its way out.

Garen grabbed the corner of the ball of net even harder, turning aside slightly. Behind him, the countless Fire Birds gathered together, forming a figure of fire.

It wore black armor, and the body inside the armor basically had the same dark-red texture of lava. It was basically an Elemental.

Garen narrowed his eyes. Casavon had three powerful Gods under his command, and one of them seemed to match this person before him perfectly in terms of their physical appearance.

“The Elemental Thane… Aer.” If the one he faced before was an Incarnation of Tiamat, the one he was about to face this time was the true Godhead of a Lower God.

“A mere Dragon of Disaster..” Scorching hot flames erupted from underneath this Fire Elemental Thane’s helmet, and his body kept emitting large gusts of black smoke and high-temperature heat waves from all over his body.

“How dare you offend His Highness Casavon!”

He raised his scimitar and pointed it at Garen.

“To thy soul, I shall…” Bam!!

All of a sudden, a giant black beast pounced at him from the side.

The beast grabbed him tightly in mid-air, and the two of them wrestled and rolled. In mid-air, the beast suddenly sprouted a pair of large black bat wings.

Rainbow-colored circles of light burst forth as a result of the clash between the waves of energy and Divine Power, exploding between the two of them.

Garen watched this scene quietly. Since Ann had arranged so many things, it was only natural that she would not have forgotten to consider the manpower Casavon had under his command.

The two Lower-God-Level Thanes fought each other madly. One was the Earth Elemental Thane, the beast arranged by Ann, and the other was the Flame Thane.

The mountains and river beneath them rose, and crevices appeared between the giant boulders, revealing the lava that flowed beneath.

The powers of the Earth and the Flames tangled and wrestled with each other. It was a natural phenomenon as a result of a leakage of the two Thanes’ power.

Amidst the loud rumbling, several black shadows began to appear slowly on the ground beneath them. The black shadows contracted abruptly, turning into several purple-black metallic giants that were each more than ten meters tall.

These Giants wore sharp triangular masks, and they held long black swords in their hands, their entire bodies covered in many mysterious carvings.

They leaped, their movements nimble, and all pounced toward the four people holding up the net in mid-air.

“Shadow Masks. They’re from the Grey Shadow Parliament.” Golden-Winged Dragon Mother snorted coldly. “Careful, each of these Giants is a Level Fifteen Sword Master from the Giant Clan.”

“Leave this to me!”

A woman in black slowly appeared in mid-air beside them. The woman had dark golden curved horns on top of her head, and she wore a black suit of armor that covered her entire body. In her hands, she held two long and thin swords. Her long purple-red hair flew in the wind.

“Chaotic Space-Time!”

She abruptly raised her swords high, and a piercing sound immediately echoed through the entire vicinity.

Psst!!

A ray of purple-red light abruptly shot out of her blade, shooting straight into the air where it turned into a long thin line of purple-red, piercing through the clouds.

“Come, my most loyal clansmen!!” The woman screeched with strange and eerie laughter.

Buzz… Suddenly, a large current of purple-red clouds swirled in mid-air, turning into an enormous tornado that spun slowly in the sky.

With a crackle, a bolt of purple lightning shot past, and the entire sky dimmed.

Immediately, countless purple-red moth-like insects flew out of the tornado. These insects seemed to be several dozen times the regular moths, and each of them had eyes that glowed with a faint neon red light. Their vicious-looking mouthparts opened and closed constantly, as though they were trying to chew something greedily.

The insects pounced down from the sky like raindrops, flitting past the woman and leaping downward.

Roar!!

A Giant roared furiously, waving its Greatsword rapidly until it looked like a wheel as it moved into a sword dance. But even so, it was blocked by the many purple-red moths.

The moths’ bodies were extremely hard. Even if they took a hit from the Greatsword, they would only sustain a tiny bit of damage. Then, they would shake their heads slightly and go charging forth once more.

Beneath them, the several dozen Giant were instantly surrounded by the countless moths, intercepted in mid-air.

On the ground, a Giant Sword Master wearing a black cape with golden trimmings looked up at the woman who had summoned the moths.

Without wasting any breath on small talk, the Giant Sword Master created an Excalibur in his hand, condensing it out of blue electricity. He took a few quick steps forth, borrowed that momentum, and stomped down hard.

Boom!!

The blue light shot into the air, the Giant Sword Master and the woman crashing into each other in mid-air. Black and blue Holy Aura Territories rose around the two of them, cutting off all the gazes from the outside world completely.

Garen pulled back his gaze.

The battle between the two sides was growing larger.

A few grey-robed old Wizards gradually appeared in the distant sky. There were still the faint vestiges of the forces from when they leaped through space, so it was clear that they had leaped here using a matrix.

As soon as these people appeared, they lowered their heads and began to chant a spell quickly, their hands scattering countless crystalline powders into the air.

“The leaders of the Grey Shadow Parliament!” Garen recognized these five old Wizards, they were all peak-level Great Arcanists from the Northlands. Even the weakest one was at Level Eleven. The highest-leveled one, on the other hand, was a Level Fourteen Great Arcanist.

Each of them had the faint image of a tall tower floating behind them, symbolizing the fact that they each had a huge Wizard Tower and Elemental Pond supporting them.

Garen glanced at Golden-Winged Dragon Mother’s direction. She was already exchanging blows with a yellow shadow, and bolts of gold-colored Divine Power sprayed out of their battle. Clearly, her opponent was also a Lower God.

“Looks like I’ll have to handle this on my own.” Garen did not think that this was the extent of the Grey Shadow Parliament’s firepower this time.

Just then, the chanting stopped abruptly.

The bodies of the five old Wizards suddenly gathered together, and actually molded into one clump like mud. Then, they quickly turned into a Warrior dressed in a huge white suit of armor and wielding two sabers.

“Emperor!!” the Warrior roared in a low voice. A white star suddenly lit up in the sky, and the white starlight pierced through the clouds and the tornado, shining down directly on his body.

In an instant, countless magnificent and holy patterns continuously appeared all over the Warrior’s body.

He took one step forward, and his body disappeared abruptly, reappearing behind Garen.

He swung his saber!!

A diamond-shaped crystal appeared in front of the saber and was instantly shattered by the blade.

Bam! The countless crystal shards shot toward the back of Garen’s head, hiding the trajectory of the saber’s tip.

“Decay,” said Garen in a low voice.

A cloud of black fog erupted from his body, covering everything within a several-dozen-meter radius. It covered the Warrior as well.

This was his Divine Persona’s Authority. He could use his Divine Power to activate a powerful ability, as an embodiment of the laws. Everything trapped in the fog was limited by the laws of this place, and so began to decay slowly.

Be it their stamina, strength, speed, or essence, these would all fade quickly with the passage of time.

Pfft pfft pfft!

Countless crystal shards all landed on Garen’s body.

However, it was as though they were crashing into wood. They left no trace whatsoever.

The tip of the blade also pierced into Garen’s scales mercilessly, and the thin golden layer of the Divine Membrane was instantly broken through. The tip of the blade tapped directly against the dragon scale, emitting a piercing screech of friction.

“Dragon Light Slash!!” The Warrior used all the power in his body once more, and an arc of golden electricity burst forth from his hand, extending along the blade and instantly reaching the top. It became a huge force that propelled the blade forward viciously.

Pfft!

The arc of lightning shot out of the blade tip and struck into Garen’s scales.

The Warrior’s other hand abruptly turned into a blood-red tentacle of pure energy which wound itself around one of Garen’s wings fiercely, with a smack.

“A Divine Weapon?” Garen raised an eyebrow. That blood-red energy tentacle meant that the opponent was clearly using a Divine Weapon to temporarily block of his Decay Authority.

This was also because he had too little Divine Power. If his Divine Persona was not limited to such weak Divine Power, if he had the Divine Power of a Lower God, then unless it was a Middle- or Upper-Level Divine Weapon, it would have been impossible to go against the power of Divine Authority.

But Garen was not surprised in the very least. If the opponent did not have at least this much power, how would they dare to participate in a battle of this level?

“Saber of Domination!” With a shake of his hand, he emitted a pitch-black ball that instantly enveloped the Warrior before him. It also swallowed up the red tentacles.

This was Tiamat’s ultimate move, but since it was part of the Domination Divine Persona’s Authority, Garen managed to absorb it into his Authority as well after a period of analysis.

This was the benefit of concentrating all his potential into his increasing his Intelligence. Within a few short days, he had completely digested Tiamat’s Authority.

“Unfortunately, since it’s the natural ability of the Divine Persona, I can only use the Lower-Level Authority once without a cost. If I wanted to use it a second time, I’ll have to add on some extra Divine Power as a starter. Garen calculated how much Divine Power he had saved. He left just a wisp to allow the Divine Shield’s protective mechanism to run and operate automatically, and converted all the remaining Divine Power into Potential so that he could strengthen himself.

The Divine Power he obtained from devouring Tiamat pushed his Intelligence all the way up to 400 points. Unlike before, he now needed twenty Potential Points to increase his attributes by one point, so it was quite the cost.

400 points in Intelligence caused the computing speeds of the Willpower Neuroprocessor to increase to an unbelievable level. The computing tasks that required several days, and took Gods several months, now only took him several hours.

Chapter 1366: Hunt 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black ball slowly dissipated, and on the body of the white-armored soldier who reappeared, was a horrific saber mark. The saber mark had almost slashed his body into two pieces, and a great number of red blood vessels wormed out from the gap of the wounds, waving madly like a dancing snake.

At this moment, a faint feeling of pain was spreading at the body part where Garen had used to forcefully resist the opponent’s attack.

His brows knitted together, but such an attack could only make him feel pain. Some of the scales’ surfaces were ruined, nothing more.

Boom!

His tail twined round the Warrior in front of him and entangled him tightly.

Sizz…

The powerful might was not something even the Incarnation of a Lower God could compare with. Garen’s 260-points of Strength was fierce, tightening the Warrior more and more…

He raised the other party up high over his head. Lifting his face, Garen opened his dragon mouth, and a large amount of blood was squeezed out, dripping into his mouth.

His snake-like tongue flickered continuously, licking the blood that spilled over his mouth.

“Sure enough, it’s the Incarnation condensed from Faith… hahahaha, such a pure blood of worship… what a free delivery of Divine Power!!”

Garen’s eyes gleamed ferociously as he laughed out loud. He casually flung away the Warrior at his tail, and the gigantic bloody colored ball of net behind him finally began to fade.

At this moment, three golden lights shot up into the sky and fled in three different directions.

“The Wheel of Time!”

Ann’s voice echoed throughout the space around.

In that instance, everything stood still.

Only the three flying golden lights were still flitting away, but their speed had slowed down by a great deal. It was only then that Garen could clearly see that the three golden lights were actually three panicking golden Gods.

“Turn.”

The Deception Demon Master’s sound rang out.

In a trice, the heads of the three golden Gods fell right away, as if they were sliced off by a sharp weapon.

“Go!” Ann said nothing more, raised her hands to release four golden lights, which fell onto Garen and the Golden-Winged Dragon Mother, the four net-weavers.

In a cloud of distortion, all the combatants on the scene who were from Ann’s side disappeared at the same time.

Just at this moment.

Bang!!

An incomparably enormous golden beam descended from the sky.

A golden angel flew out from the golden light. She had six pairs of wings, her entire body was like a gold sculpture. Holding a short-handled flail, her eyes coldly scanned below.

“Shadow Dragon King…”

************************

When Garen opened his eyes again, he was already in the Abyss at the place where Ann was sealed at.

Ann was exhausted, her entire body was constantly swallowing and spitting out a large amount of golden Divine Power, which was a sign that the Divine Power had not been completely digested.

“Casavon is dead. I didn’t expect another two Middle Gods to be there. This time we almost failed!”

“The God of Knowledge and the God of Raging Wind. Both were of middle Divine Power and had vanished without a trace a long time ago. No one expected them to be hiding in that place, waiting for us.” The black-armored woman spoke in a low voice.

“I’ll take my remuneration with me. The impact this time is too great. Fortunately, we moved quickly.” The Deception Demon Master came out of the darkness from one side.

“What I want is the God of Raging Wind’s Divine Persona. The Divine Crystal doesn’t matter to me.” No one knew where the Earth Demon Master Scorpion-Headed Human was hiding, and they could only hear the voice.

“The one that came later was the Higher Divine Power Lord of the Golden Angel, Fehra’s strongest right-hand man; also a pure God with a holy nature who is in charge of purification! Fortunately, we left fast. This fellow is not much inferior to Fehra’s Incarnation!” He said gladly.

“The three Divine Personas will be equally divided, while the divinity will be given to the other existences who had given assistance. More than two thousand Divine Crystals were extracted, and it can raise 20 points of Divine Persona. Are you sure you don’t want it?” Ann looked at the Earth Demon Master.

“No,” the Scorpion-Headed Human said casually, “what we lack isn’t the Divine Crystals… to convert the Divine Power into the energy that could enhance ourselves takes too long. What we lack is divinity. Complete divinity. Unfortunately, they’re all too fragmentized by you in the battle.”

“Divinity?” Ann pondered.

Garen and the Golden-Winged Dragon Mother quietly listened to the distribution of spoils at the side.

Hearing the words of the Earth Demon Master, he also instantly understood.

Other Demon Masters could not perfect the divinity as fast as him. His horrific computing power could even extend the perfected divinity into the existence of a Divine Persona.

It seemed that although other Demon Masters could also perfect the divinity and convert it into a Soul Ring, obviously it would cost a lot of time and effort, so they were not interested in the over-fragmented divinities.

“Fragmented divinities? I’d like to be allocated some of each. I don’t need too many in quantity, just want more types. Is that feasible?” Garen thought about it and took the initiative to go forward to speak.

“Some of each?” The Earth Demon Master frowned slightly and thought of something. “Are you…?”

“I want to try perfecting the divinities,” Garen nodded and frankly admitted.

“Alright. Divine Power isn’t of much use to us unless you want to focus on the path of the Gods. Otherwise, the Divine Power could only be used as a consumable item for the means of attacking.” The Deception Demon Master nodded on the side.

“The Divine Crystals… since you guys don’t need it, I wonder if you could sell some of them to me?” Ann suddenly said.

“How many do you want?”

“We’ll talk outside,” Ann said lowly.

The three Middle-God powerhouses disappeared at the bottom of the Abyss.

Some sundries-like objects were instantly scattered from mid-air and divided into four parts as they flew into the hands of Garen and the net-weavers.

There were still two combatants who were empty-handed. But no dissatisfaction was shown on their faces. Obviously, there had been other arrangements beforehand.

Garen collected his own share. It was more than a dozen little balls that looked like lustrious balls of yarn.

He had now transformed into a human figure, and he reached out his index finger to gently touch a small red ball.

‘Divinity discovered, category: storm. 1% completeness.’

Then he touched another silver one.

‘Divinity discovered, category: literature.’

‘Divinity discovered, category: poetry.’

Garen touched all the divinities one by one.

These dozens of divinities came from the God of Time and Shadow, the God of Knowledge, and the God of Raging Wind respectively. They were threads of divinity from the different Divine Domains that the three Middle Gods were in charge of.

“If I can perfect these divinities…” Garen’s heart was slightly looking forward to it. Some of the Divine Domain divinities could enhance the computing power of his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

For example, one of the God of Knowledge’s divinity that was called Logic could completely enhance the computing speed of his Willpower Neuroprocessor.

“Well, we can now leave. Be careful, I smell the aura of the God of Death on you,” the Golden-Winged Dragon Mother on the side reminded gently. “Maybe it won’t take for the God of Death to pay close attention to you. Once you utilize the divinity that overlaps with his to form the Divine Domain and attempt to condense the Divine Persona, it will trigger a Holy War.”

Garen was astounded.

“Understood. That is to say, he’s just taking note of me now, right?”

“Yes, just taking note. He pays attention to all the existence who have grasped the divinity of Death.”

Garen nodded silently.

But being amid the whirlpool of the war between two big Worlds, he had no reason to give up the capital that was in his hands to enhance his strength.

“If nothing unexpected happens, Ann should be able to reap a major gain this time. Forming an alliance with you guys, the Void, can help her to ascend to a new level.” The Golden-Winged Dragon Mother sighed slightly.

“Ann is already at the peak of the Middle Divine Power. A new level… is it…” The black-armored woman’s voice faltered, but she still could not suppress her shock. “She had just broken out, and already she had accumulated such a foundation?”

“She did not just break out…” The Golden-Winged Dragon Mother spoke with another deeper meaning to it.

“Isn’t this better? Hehehe…” The black beast fanned his wings and laughed deeply. It was him who had helped Garen to block the first wave of enemies.

“Only in this way can we protect ourselves in this chaotic era…” the black-armored woman said solemnly.

Garen stood by the side and did not speak.

Just for… self-protection?

He suddenly recalled what the Earth Demon Master had said to him.

No one was a fool. Regarding his ability in which he could quietly perfect the divinity into a Soul Ring, perhaps the Deception Demon Master had been aware of it. After all, she had been together with him for so many years.

Perhaps this was also the reason why the Distortion Demon Master thought that he had the most potential.

Although it was still too early for him to replace Ann, it had not been a long time until now, and already he had reached the combat power of a Lower Divine Power. Becoming a Middle God soon would not be difficult.

He recalled the Earth Demon Master’s last meaningful gaze, and there was a hunch in his heart.

“Alright then, I’m heading back first,” he said plainly. “This is the way to contact my Tower. You are all welcome to come and visit.”

He shot out a white cold light, which separated and landed before the other three.

“If there’s a chance, I’ll certainly come to visit. This is the coordinates of my deep pool.”

The other three tyrannical existence also exchanged information with one another. In this chaotic era, more friendships represented more security. No one would reject befriending a Lower God powerhouse.

Garen nodded and vanished instantly.

The remaining three were silent for a moment.

“Garen, there shouldn’t be anyone else who’s more talented than him in the White Dragon Clan…” The Golden-Winged Dragon Mother sighed.

“How many years did it take for him to reach this level? I feel that his bone age is too young…” the black beast remarked in a low voice.

“Less than fifty years,” the Golden-Winged Dragon Mother answered.

There was a moment of silence.

The other two clearly showed an astounded expression.

“That’s really… indescribable.” The black-armored woman smiled bitterly. “Compared with him, what have we been really doing all these years…”

“No… it’s different.” The Golden-Winged Dragon Mother shook her head. “Ann once told me that Garen had the inheritance of the God of Pharmacy of the previous generation. He’s different.”

“No wonder.”

The God of Pharmacy was the most mysterious God in this big world, and it had created countless mysteries and weirdness. Even the most powerful major Gods could not tell what his true form was. In the end, it was due to the rise of another God of Pharmacy that the Divine Domain was discovered to not have been occupied. Only then it was known that the God of Pharmacy had fallen.

That was to say, until the fall, no one was still able to know what his true identity was, and who the Godhead was.

Chapter 1367: The Onset of Doomsday 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Cold Winter Tower

Garen’s figure instantly appeared on the Transportation Formation at the bottom floor.

He looked around, and a metal Golem came over and bowed slightly at him.

“Where’s Nadia?”

“At the third floor. Seems to be reading a book?” The Golem replied in a low voice. These Golems had a certain intelligence. They were high-performance Golems created by Garen using the technology of the Mech World, which could be considered the integration of Arcane Technique and technology, and they were extremely horrific, as they already had a standard capability of Level Six once they came out of the experimental platform. Moreover, they could even continue to grow.

Garen had built a total of three of them; one to manage the Cold Winter Tower, one in the Abyss, and one in the production logistics.

“What about Koala?” Garen asked. “How’s the progress? Ask him to come see me.”

“Yes.”

The gigantic body of the Golem bowed his head in reply.

Garen strolled to the Transportation Formation that led to the third floor. The Cold Winter Tower did not have stairs for each level. Instead, they were each an independent space and could only rely on the Formation to travel to and fro.

After a burst of white light, the second floor of the Cold Winter Tower was a place like a strategic research room, and at the center was a large universe Plane simulation scene.

On the khaki colored Main Substance Plane ball, the space of the upper-level Heavenly Mountain and other Upper Planes was a huge white disc, while the bottom also had a large disc, but it was black, which was the space of the Lower Planes; some were also named the Inner-Level Planes. On the side of it was a large cloud of colorful misty things floating over there; it was the Astral Space.

The Astral Space extended numerous tentacles, linking the Upper, Middle, and Lower Planes. Some blood-like objects could be clearly seen flowing from the Planes into the Astral Space, and from the Astral Space, they would flow back into the Planes along the tentacles, forming a large cycle.

Around the whole model was a vast Dark Void, and there were huge colorful plates faraway in the Void. They were the Divine Kingdom of each major Higher Gods. There was also a huge black hole in the middle, which was the node connecting the Void and this World.

Garen walked up to the simulation scene and swept his eyes across the situation shown on it.

‘According to the latest data collected, the scene authenticity is estimated at 67%.’ The Tower Soul, which was also Garen’s Willpower Neuroprocessor, gave a feedback.

“67%? That’s not low…” Garen nodded with satisfaction. “What is the general situation at the moment?”

‘The Void has completely suppressed the local Pantheons and has dominated nearly 50% of the local territories. Besides the big seas and the ocean, there had been major massacres at many places at the Main Substance Plane. The situation is very good. However, there are some tricky characters that can’t be detected even by the levels of the Distortion Demon Master; for example, the Child of Hell and the Child of Radiance.’

‘The Child of Hell. It’s estimated that there are dozens of them, each of whom is of different race, and their form is uncertain. The Child of Radiance is one person, and his identity is unknown. Their location is uncertain.’ The computing power of the Willpower Neuroprocessor was now far beyond than that of the average top-level Energy Machinists. In the Mech World, the Gods would also be considered an incomparable existence.

“How’s the Biochemical Pool?” Garen turned around, and a semi-transparent micro-black, thin little Golem suddenly appeared behind him. This Golem was only the height of a person, and the figure was slender and thin, looking like it could be easily fractured. However, there were sharp and pointed protrusions and spiked blades everywhere on it, giving a feeling of fragility and danger at the same time.

“Reporting to Master. The embryos bred in the Biochemical Pool has reached a thousand in numbers. All are placed in the soil under the Cold Winter Tower, and the Protection Matrix has been activated to safeguard them. We can stimulate their hatching at any time to join the battle.” Koala the Golem answered sharply.

“Types?”

“There are ten Razor Wolves Type 1, and they’re estimated to be at this world’s Level Five. The remaining basic units are Berserk Werewolves, which have flying and drilling functions, and their strength is evaluated at Level Three. The stock of Abyss resources that were recently shipped here have been exhausted,” Koala replied quickly.

“It’s fine,” Garen was not very satisfied. “Release all the Razor Wolves and collect the needed data in time to prepare for Type 2.”

“Understood,” Koala hesitated. “Master, do we need a Willpower Connection?” he asked cautiously.

Although it was hatched and produced from Garen’s Biochemical Pool, without the execution of the Soul Connection, these bio-weapons could not enjoy a mighty augmentation from Garen’s Willpower. In addition, because Garen was a Demon Lord, there would also be a natural strengthening to his subordinates.

This Demon Lord’s strengthening ability was acquired when one reached the Army Level. All the soldiers would be strengthened following the enhancement of the Demon Lord at the same time.

“No rush…” Garen blinked. “I’m going to have a big enhancement soon. The enhancement needs a better Type 2.”

“Understood…” Koala nodded and instantly faded into the darkness. He was basically an assassin-type Golem.

Garen had a final look at the simulation scene. The black representing the Void and the white representing the locals were constantly twisting and slaughtering at each major Planes. Through the information from the Abyss, he was able to gather a lot of information from the innumerable Planes that were linked to the Abyss. He then in turn simulated this huge scene.

After watching the simulation scene for a while, Garen turned around and walked to the darkness on the side. A black crystal stone pillar automatically raised from the ground, and a large amount of information from the Vengeance Fortress was displayed on it like it was a screen.

After he had left the Abyss, the powerful Evil Gods around the Vengeance Fortress did not have any other targets, so they ceased all activities and left. Instead, the forces of the White Dragon Mountain had entered the fortress, changed their previous rampant behavior, and quietly waited for his return.

“The White Dragon King is dead. Looks like the White Dragon Clan will have to find a new reliance,” Garen snickered. He had a terrible intuition for the White Dragon Mountain. The representing Elder from the White Dragon Mountain now appeared in the frame and was exhibiting a peaceful and submission deportment, clearly being oppressed by the other forces so that they had no choice but to seek other assistance from the outside.

“Andrew.” Garen gently tapped the picture.

“Master.” A commander in black armor appeared on the crystal stone screen. “What are your orders?”

“How’s the current situation at White Dragon Mountain?”

Andrew had unwittingly broken through to Level Twelve, but his aura was close to saturation. Obviously, his soul had reached the upper limit. Many creatures had their own limits, whether it was the soul or the flesh, and only very few powerful inheritance could help the creatures to break through this limit. This World had a lot of top-level life energy cultivation methods, while the Worlds Garen had previously transmigrated to mainly focus on the Void’s various Secret Technique inheritance.

What Andrew had been practicing was the powerful inherited secret method of his own household, which was the Knight’s Technique that many knights studied. However, he could only reach Level Twelve in the end, and that was already considered very terrific. After all, he was only from a duke family of a small empire; how strong could the inheritance of a duke household from a remote small empire be?

“White Dragon Mountain is under the coercion of the Abyssal Demon Dragon Clan, so they’re now stuck in a difficult position and are seeking foreign aid everywhere,” Andrew quickly replied. “There was a time when they sent someone to try to bribe me, but I refused.”

“How ’bout Tiamat? How come she didn’t care for them?” Garen sneered.

“Tiamat seems to have disappeared without a trace. Even the Evil Dragon Priests had also vanished. The White Dragon Clan have lost their refuge and are faced with the duress of being swallowed up by the Abyssal Demon Dragons. That’s probably the key reason why they come to ask for your help,” Andrew said plainly.

“Disappeared?” Garen gave it a thought. “How much accumulated resources are left?”

“The consumption was not huge. Recently, we organized another Blood War and have reaped abundantly. There’re a hundred units of Abyssal supplies that could be given out.” Andrew simply summed it up. The Abyssal supplies was a unit determined by the internal department of the Cold Winter Tower. One unit of Abyssal supply could support the functioning of the Cold Winter Tower for a month. It could also produce a hundred Berserk Wolves, so it was a very large unit.

“Sent them all over. I need to open up a new territory here,” Garen ordered.

“Yes.”

Switching off the communication, Garen went directly to the Transportation Formation and entered the third floor.

The third floor was temporarily refurbished into a medical and reading floor, and a lot of data were placed here on the rows of bookshelves at a side.

Nadia was wearing a black blouse, a mini-skirt from Earth period, and long black socks. Her slender and symmetrical figure leaned against the seat, as her dark long hair draped down the back of the chair, straight and smooth.

Rosta and Elphis, the two Void Pursuers, also sat opposite her, quietly reading their books and counting something with a pen.

Seeing Garen appeared, all three tensed up slightly

“His strength is stronger…” Rosta was stunned as he felt an endless horrific aura spread over. Glancing at Elphis, both of them saw from each other’s eyes a sense of impotence as they smiled bitterly.

Nadia also felt the enhancement of this aura, and there was another layer of coldness on her face.

The human-form Garen was dressed in a white aristocratic outfit with a silver edge. He had white gloves on, and his figure was slender, giving others a cultured and elegant temperament.

“How’s things? I’m sure you three are doing fine in the Cold Winter Tower?”

He went to the table.

“Come and sit. I’m here to tell you all something.”

He swept his eyes across Rosta and Elphis. Both their aura was obviously enhanced a great deal due to the Distorted Seed, probably reaching the standard of Level Ten. Although they were still fragile like a child in front of him, but they could already manage to gain a foothold in this world. This was the power of the Distorted Seed.

“The two of you, what’s holding you back from advancing is that you have to find a point of convergence that you want, condense all your strength, purify it, and focus on that point as the core. Only then can you further enhance.” Garen gave some pointers to the two subordinates. Elphis and Rosta were also Void Pursuers, so he naturally had some sense of identity with them.

Then there was Nadia.

He turned his head around and looked at this old acquaintance.

“What about you? Almost comprehend it all? Regarding the situation of this World.”

Nadia closed her eyes and was silent for a moment. She then opened her eyes, and her pupils were filled with an unruly luster.

“What about that? What do you want to say?! Want me to succumb to you?” She taunted. “Even though I’m very grateful to you for saving me, but don’t think that I will succumb to any existence!”

“I don’t intend to oppress you,” Garen smiled. “I just feel that by leaving you here, any time when I’m in a bad mood, I can come to you to vent it all out. And after that, my mood will be fine,” he joked.

“You!” Nadia was ignited, and her eyes began to blaze with fury.

“Forget it. Master Garen is just joking with you…” Rosta, who was a kind old man, quickly began to soothe and smooth things over. Judging by his proficiency, this was clearly not his first time doing this.

Garen shook his head and stopped teasing her.

“Alright, back to business. Nadia, I can let you go, but with your current strength of less than Level Nine, and now is the time of great war between the Void and the Pantheons, if you don’t group together but choose to act alone, I suppose you won’t even make it for a week. Do you believe me?”

He did not lie to her anymore. This was the truth.

Now, whether it was the Void or the Pantheon, even the Lower Gods were afraid to act alone, for fear of being pursued and assassinated by the other powerhouse group. Not to mention her, a mere Level Eight-existence.

Nadia was silent, biting her lower lip slowly. She wanted to find a reason to refute, but she was not one with a silver tongue, and she herself was well-aware of the facts.

“So, seeing that you are an old friend, I’ll give you two choices,” Garen extended two fingers.

“One, join me. I’ll give you a Distorted Seed so that you can advance to around Level Ten, which will be sufficient for you to protect yourself. At the same time, like Rosta, you’ll be a small commander in my Cold Winter Tower.”

“I refuse! I don’t like to command whatsoever!” Nadia refused flatly.

“Then it’s the second one,” Garen smiled. “Be my personal bodyguard. I’ll grant you the Soul Connection. As long as I advance, you can also benefit and advance. I’ll be having a major leap soon, you can also seize this opportunity. But as an Army Level, you should be aware of the disadvantages and advantages in this respect.”

Nadia did not say anything.

The Soul Connection was actually the means by which the Army Level or Demon Lord-Level established its own army. After the establishment of the connection was successful, whenever the Demon Lord or Army Level advanced their strength, they would also simultaneously spur their subordinates to advance together.

The advantage of this was that one could progress quickly with a genius. The downside was that you must absolutely obey the Demon Lord or Army Level regardless of any order; even if they want you to go take your life.

Such a connection was almost impossible to be rid of, and no one had ever heard of anyone who could be released from it. It was said that only when the strength of the subordinates exceeded that of the Chief of Army or the Demon Lord by a great deal that it was possible to break off the connection at that time.

However, such a result had never appeared.

“Do you still actually want to enslave me?!” Nadia fixed her gaze coldly on Garen.

Chapter 1368: The Onset of Doomsday 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I don’t have such a thought,” Garen smiled. “I have countless powerful subordinates in the Abyss. To be honest, I don’t lack you guys. But since our relationship is rather different, as Rosta and Elphis are the only Void Pursuers left, while you’re my old friend, naturally it’s necessary to take care of my acquaintances first. Am I right?”

Nadia bit her lips, and her eyes revealed a mixed feeling. She also remembered the tragic experience of just entering the world and being simply caught like a chick or rubbish.

“Let me consider it.”

She originally wanted to immediately refuse in rage, but when the words reached the tip of her tongue, they unconsciously came out with another meaning.

“Give it a good thought.” Garen was not in a hurry. His plan would not be delayed due to Nadia.

“Rosta, you guys come with me.”

“Yes.” Rosta and Elphis instantly responded.

The two stood up and followed Garen to the Transportation Formation. With a whoosh and a flash of light, they disappeared directly from this floor.

Nadia quietly watched the few people left, and her heart was wavering more and more.

She had already reached the upper limit of strength enhancement, and she could not advance anymore as she was at the Army Level. Although she could advance herself in this World through slaughtering, but just like what Garen had said, it was too dangerous.

“Perhaps… I should really consider it.”

*****************

Garen the trio appeared directly in the center of the Elemental Pond at the top floor.

The six Elemental Ponds around were still emitting horrific energy fluctuations. Upon just entering here, Rosta and Elphis were entirely stiff and were directly impacted by the violent elements. They could only freeze on the spot and could not move at all. The enormous energy pressure made them, the Gods, felt sore and painful in their skin.

Snap.

Garen made a bright snapping sound, only then did the energy concentration around the two returned to normal.

“This is the core of the Cold Winter Tower, the source of all power. I’ll cultivate here, while you’ll connect with my soul first. After the imprint is marked, you’ll be able to advance along with me.”

“Thank you for going through the trouble for us, Master.” The two quickly thanked.

“In the future, you guys will be responsible for the troops that manage the Cold Winter Tower at the Main Substance Plane together with Koala and the rest,” Garen casually said. “I have other things to deal with. The lesser the Soul Connection of the army, the greater the enhancement that will be equally shared. I plan to look for only ten existence to be enhanced.”

Rosta and Elphis were stupefied. With an army of only ten people, this meant that so as long as Garen advanced, the help for them would be a terrifying qualitative change. This would be almost like a skyrocketing leap in strength.

Garen was not bothered, because what he needed now were powerhouses; enough powerhouses to assist him; not cannon fodders, since he already had lots of those. Whether it was the Abyss or the Biochemical Pool, he could create sufficient powerful cannon fodders. However, he was lacking those who could really become his right-hand man.

“If there’s no other opinion, then let’s get started,” Garen said plainly.

“Yes.” X2.

As soon as the voices fell, Garen flicked his fingers and shot out two reddish translucent rays, precisely piercing the center of the two persons’ eyebrows.

The impact hit them hard to the point their heads were raised, and instantly fell into a coma.

The reddish light continued slowly, and Garen stopped looking at the two but walked to the Biochemical Pool to observe the latest changes. What was needed next was just the passing of time.

Initially, he had determined the places for Andrew and the other senior subordinates, coupled with Rosta the trio from this side as well as the few whom he had selected from the White Dragon Clan, Satwo and so on. There were only ten places in total. All of them were to command the enormous army under him.

After streamlining the Abyss’ army, now it was close to eight hundred thousand, all of which the lowest level were Level Three-cannon fodders, while the highest was Leve Six junior captains.

Garen planned to have this force stay in the Abyss and strengthen them.

He intended to build another large army at the Main Substance Plane and to mainly construct with the Biochemical Pool and experimental platform.

“Next, it’s time to study the divinities…” Garen looked at the more than a dozen little divinity balls in his Soul Space. “I wonder, how much will I achieve after I have completely constructed and absorbed them? I really look forward to it…”

He simply chose to sit on the edge of the Biochemical Pool and quietly closed his eyes.

******************

Behind the Alliance of the Gods.

Holy Light City.

This was the famous city Fehra was born in, and it was rumored that here was the origin of all light.

At the center of the city, a long string of bell chimes continued to ring out.

Numerous airships floated in the air and scattered down countless white petals as countless believers and people prayed piously.

Because of the Void Creatures’ wanton slaughter, the population had been greatly reduced, but at the same time, it had also led the existing people’s belief in the Divine Souls to reach an extremely pious level. This was because only the Divine Souls could kill the Void Creatures to eliminate all disasters and persecution.

Inside a huge cathedral in the center of the city.

The Holy Light Cathedral was the miraculous cathedral that was the core of the entire Holy Light City. It was where the Divine Souls had personally demonstrated their Divine Power.

Dozens of Gods had appeared before, of whom the most number of times was naturally Fehra the Major God.

At this time, all the top Cathedral leaders were gathered here on the inside, and Demigod-level powerhouses were seen everywhere. Even some former Popes who had reached the Lower God-level but still stayed in the mortal world and had not established the Divine Kingdom had appeared here.

“Praise the Gods!!” The current pope, Pope Chius, hailed loudly.

“Praise the Gods.”

Everyone called out in response at the same time.

“Evil stirs up the World, but Light will come,” The holy chief judge came forward and exhorted loudly. “Heroes will naturally emerge in troubled times. The oracle has been revealed, and I will now confer Bishop Anselon Kyrgyz with the position of the Chief Knight of the highest order, commanding one thousand and twenty-eight Knights of the highest order.”

A handsome young man with a faint golden light all over him and a gentle smile on his face slowly walked up to the center of the Cathedral, escorted by a group of Golden Knights.

He had on him a dark golden armor, was carrying a helmet in one hand, and his long blond hair wavered as his paced forward.

The sacred and grand music began to sound, and as the young Knight continued to advance, golden holy lights were ignited on the bodies of the Cathedral leaders on both sides, showing their respect.

Rays of holy light illuminated continually from both sides consecutively, turning into golden beams of light.

Everyone began to pray in a low voice.

The Pope got up and personally handed him a platinum long sword, which represented the command of the Knights, with both hands.

“Anselon, the Lord has been watching you all the time.” The Pope smiled mildly at him.

“His subordinate understands.” Anselon bowed his head and respectfully reached for the sword.

Just when his hand touched the sword.

Whish whish whish!!

Countless white golden rays burst out from the long sword.

Boom!!!

The Divine Statues of Fehra and the other dozen of Gods in the Cathedral all lit up at the same time, and countless white golden rays descended from the Divine Statues and converged on the Pope.

“It’s an Incarnation!!”

“It’s the Incarnation of the great Fehra!!”

“Oh my God! The Major God actually chose to come down!”

The surrounding Cathedral leaders were surprised. At the power transfer conferring ceremony of the highest armed forces, the new commander actually received the glory of the Major God’s personal arrival!

This was simply a miracle of all miracles and a glory that had never been seen before!

The countless holy light converged on the Pope, transforming him into a Light-man.

His body seemed to have gotten taller, and twelve pairs of white wings spread out from his back. An intense and mighty-to-the-extreme Holy Aura pressure naturally spread out.

“Anselon, I will personally grant you a completely new authority and identity,” Fehra’s majestic voice sounded from the light.

Anselon could not resist the shock, and he quickly bowed his head even more respectfully, facing Fehra’s Incarnation.

“Praise my Lord! The Light of my Lord shines through thousands of Planes,” his voice was quivering.

“Your feats will be turned into a Holy Sword; your kindness will be turned into the Holy Light Shield; your justice will be integrated into the countless hearts of justice; your anger will be turned into a boundless iron!” Fehra the Incarnation sang loudly in a poetic tone.

He made a grabbing action with one hand, and countless golden light gathered into a delicate and gorgeous armlet. It flew to Anselon’s right arm and was automatically attached there.

“I will confer on you the highest title, the Light of the World. Your mandate: Anti-Void’s Crusader! May your feats be worthy of our trust toward you.”

Anselon’s face was clearly excited.

“The body and the soul of your subordinate will perish together! I vow to give everything for the annihilation of the Void!”

Fehra’s Incarnation nodded with satisfaction and gently passed over the sword in his hand.

Anselon caught it gently and kept it, a deep piety and sacredness on his face.

Numerous rays and flames erupted on him as if he had turned into a white golden humanoid torch for a moment.

Clang!

He pulled out the long sword and lifted it high. A horrific force like that of a Holy Aura spread out all of a sudden.

“I, who am also the Child of Radiance…” Fehra’s Incarnation slowly spoke.

“Child of Radiance…”

The hearts of the leaders and powerhouses around who were watching the ceremony instantly trembled. The long-circulated Child of Radiance had finally officially appeared today. It was rumored that he was the powerhouse with an infinite potential who could confront the Child of Hell and the existence of the Voids upfront. It was just that no one knew who he was.

Now everything was finally clear.

“The Child of Radiance…” Anselon’s eyes had completely turned white.

He raised his sword high as if it was the most precious treasure in the world.

At this moment, everything of him was sublimated, whether it was the soul or the flesh.

Fehra’s Incarnation opened his mouth again.

“This is the Holy Glory Sword, blessed by the Gods, and it will be your…”

Whish!!!

In an instant, everything stood still…

The white golden sword had unexpectedly penetrated between the eyebrows of Fehra’s Incarnation.

Anselon’s face was calm as he held the sword and fiercely exerted extra force forward.

Whish.

The blade once again stabbed deeper.

“You…!!” Fehra’s Incarnation was completely stunned. Even he did not expect that the person he chose to be the Light of the World would actually do this to him…

The leaders and the crowd around were also stunned.

Everyone’s mind went blank.

This was the Holy Light Cathedral, the most central part where countless powerhouses gathered together. The holy arrival of Fehra’s Incarnation actually had his head pierced through by a sword at the conferring ceremony?

“Is… is this just a joke…?” A Demigod’s face was slightly blanched.

“Is this some kind of a special ceremony?” The chief judge and others did not dare to think in the direction of profaning the God.

“Yeah, maybe it’s a special ritual which requires Fehra the Major God to use his Incarnation as an offering to the sword?” Some people looked for a reason to justify.

Pop…

A drop of holy blood dripped from the edge of the blade to the ground.

A very deep black began to diffuse from the center of Anselon’s pupils.

There was a savage and strange smile on his face.

“What a pity… the blessings of the Gods, countless glory in one body, fame and fortune, prestige, and credibility; you have it all. Even I myself, a king, am a little enticed…” His voice suddenly became like that of a woman, sharp and demonic.

“You… who are you!!??” Fehra wanted to break free, but he discovered that a very horrific and powerful black field had wrapped around him tightly so that he could not move at all.

Hiss…

The Excalibur was slowly pulled out, and it brought out a slick of white golden blood.

“I’m the Star Region Demon Master, Tinn Yinger…”

The blade was pulled out.

Only then did all the Cathedral leaders were completely awakened and realized what had actually happened.

However, everything was already too late. Just when countless holy lights were about to erupt, a bloody red light ball with a mixture of black suddenly exploded, completely shrouding the entire Holy Light Cathedral. The horrifying and intense evil force caused even the countless holy lights to be eclipsed.

Chapter 1369: General Trend 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Tinn Yinger, was a peculiar Demon Master from the Void who was proficient in disguise and scam. He orchestrated the bloody massacre at Holy Light Cathedral, causing the downfall of thirteen high-level church members and the death of Pope Chius who was known as the Holy Light.

Just as the Void rejoiced, the strengths of the native world could feel the past prime sense of a decline. The culprit, Star Region Demon Master, Tinn Yinger managed to escape from God as well as obtaining light and fire divinity and divine powers, emerging as the ultimate winner.

When news traveled to other three major forces, it has been more than half a month already.

Tinn Yinger was originally an equivalent to a regular Demon Master but killing Fehra’s incarnation with the Excalibur in disguise, he absorbed and engulfed Fehra’s divinity, part of his Divine Persona and divine powers, instantly elevating to be one of the few strongest Demon Master, matching powerful existences the likes of Eye of the Slaughter and Distortion Demon Master.

A Demon Lord categorized the top four strongest into one independent layer, calling it Elona, meaning ‘the strongest’ in the Void Language.

The strengths of Elona level were four from the Void Mother Stream, that is Distortion Demon Master, Eye of the Slaughter, Star Region Demon Master, and the final and strongest True Spirit — Fallen True Soul.

And three from the native world were Fehra, Mother Nature, and God of Purification Twelve Wings Golden Angel. Beneath them were other high-level gods.

No matter how great of an ability, it was way behind the Void. This was the crucial key in the native’s steady retreat.

In the continuous battle, both Eye of the Slaughter and Mother Nature were the first to sustain severe injuries, then Fehra’s incarnation suffered a sneak attack by Star Region Demon Master and his Godhead was damaged extensively.

The strongest two were not in a complete state.

Under such circumstance, the Void finally began its full force attack.

Fallen True Soul was the first to wage war. The Void Temple invaded the Upper Plane under his command and many positive energy planes erupted war. Decades of high-level Demon Lords were bred from this war. They upgraded themselves through slaughter whether adapting tactics through Enneahedron or snatching divinity and Divine Personas.

Distortion Demon Master initiated the war to unify the East and started to kill all believers, sparing only abiding citizens for production activities.

The entire East was drenched in seas of blood. In just mere ten days, it was completely overtaken.

This world would fall in just decades…

The stars representing the Gods in the sky were shaken, dimming into darkness. At times, it could be seen that the stars fell into the mortal world, one by one…

******

Cold Winter Tower.

Garen’s huge dragon body sat with his legs crossed in the biochemical pool. A monster soldier with a head of a wolf and body of a human was tossing all sorts of nutrition and chemicals into the biochemical pool but mostly, it was all kinds of energy crystal cores.

A lot of demon cores and crystal cores from the deep abyss were tossed into the biochemical pool and swiftly melted in it.

In half a month, upon completion of all Soul Connections, Garen continued to delve deep into his practice. Currently, many little crystal balls of various colors were hanging over his head.

This was Divine Personas obtained upon crystallization. Although these were singled-out divinity, the Divine Person derived from it was individualistic, but upon refinement, Garen received up to fifteen single Divine Personas.

This was a terrifying power. This meant that he could create a Demigod with fifteen individual Divine Personas in a short amount of time!

Of course, it would be such a waste to use this stuff to create a Demigod…

Garen naturally had a plan.

“The essence of divinity is the realization of intel. This means that it could be duplicated,” he opened his dragon eyes wide. His iris was gleaming with wisdom.

“And to upgrade my Soul Rings, repetitive realization will be useless. Since there is only a single effect, I could first duplicate a copy of these Divine Personas and store within my Willpower mind. Once these Divine Personas become Soul Rings, I can reconstruct the Divine Personas and even though by then these Divine Personas are useless to me but may be effective to others…”

Garen has a machine-heavy calculating and storing ability that could not be compared with any other existence. Even the most powerful computer of the Mech World was unmatched by his Willpower mind. It was at an unparallel height of wisdom, reaching a limit no Energy Machinists could imagine.

“Logical Divine Persona can help heighten my calculating ability.” Garen swallowed a silver crystal.

After a brief silence, a black ring with silver lights around it appeared behind his head.

His Willpower mind’s calculation speed increased by a large margin.

“Unknown calculation law discovered, absorbing complete data… optimizing calculation structure…”

“Capability upgraded. Overall evaluation, increase of 31% in calculation speed.

His Willpower mind continuously provided feedback.

Garen carefully brought his senses to play. It seemed that Logical Divine Persona, Decaying Divine Persona as well as his Willpower mind blended into the black glowing ring behind his head. The complicated patterns and symbols on it and massive distorted energy in it were spewing columns of many different structures. These structures harbored unimaginable law and reasons.

The black glowing ring was spreading tentacular threads invisible to the naked eye, endlessly absorbing fear and power of faith from the Void.

Garen reached his awareness out into one of the tentacles and a disarrayed wooden cabin in the scorching heat appeared before his eyes. A malnourished skinny boy sat in a corner in fear. He was muttering and praying his name. He was hot all over with a high fever. He seemed to be on his deathbed. It was not limited to Garen, there were also other frost-type gods, evil gods, malicious gods’ names uttered in repetition.

“Andrew’s former territory, huh…” Garen fell into deep thoughts. When he reduced Andrew to submission, that dukedom created a disastrous cold winter that froze several hundred thousand to death.

Now the weather was scorching hot there and these people in turn desperately prayed for his appearance.

“Idiotic Faith. How disinteresting like bundled up threads. Once Faith has fallen, the Gods gradually lose their strong cornerstone,” he did not even have the slightest intention to respond.

The Thread of Faith was the source of energy that could possibly pull the Gods into the astral base. This was not the motive that he was going after.

He turned up to look at the Divine Personas on top of his head. Without hesitating any further, he started to swallow each and every one of these Divine Personas to form Soul Rings.

He held back up copies of these Divine Personas in his Willpower mind. As long as he duplicated from his copies, established his Divine Powers and positioned Divine Domain, he could quickly structure Semi-Divine Personas.

As long as the sacred fire was not lighted or the Divine Kingdom was not built, then he would not be meddling into the Holy War of Faith and he would not be in any trouble.

As he was swallowing, the entire Cold Winter Tower began to tremble and howl loudly, like a living being that was greedy and huge.

The Cold Winter Tower was erected at the highest point of Dragon King Peak. In a range several hundred kilometers, all residing White Dragons, Dragon Beasts, and generals from the abyss who came for the handover, gazed at the direction of the high tower.

They could feel the energy from the Cold Winter Tower gradually surging, sensing its velocity. In a mere hour, there was a 20% increase of the original.

******

Bop.

The mug in Nadia’s hand almost fell onto the ground from the huge tremor. Her face tensed up and she lifted her head to look up.

“It’s Garen…” She had a complicated look on her face, a streak of disappointment flashed past her eyes. “He’s upgrading…” She suddenly knew that she may have missed the best opportunity to level up her ability.

Roar!!

Somewhere at Dragon King Peak, Satwo roared into the sky. His body was growing at a rapid speed visible under the naked eye. His back started to grow thick manes and tentacles like poisonous snakes, a White Dragon with Snakes on his back.

He was obviously under the effect of Garen.

Satwo was originally a Level Six when suddenly under an unknown aura, he felt like he was a sponge absorbing water non-stop and his body’s energy rose to an extreme level.

Level Seven… Level Eight… Level Nine…!!

It was not just him, a few of those with Connected Souls were also rising to great heights.

The rest were Satwo, Rosta, Elphis, Andrew, and Chaotic Abominable Snowman, each of their individual energies rising.

These energies directly rose their levels by one to three levels.

Satwo had the worst foundation of all, hence was raised three levels to reach Level Nine.

As for Andrew and Chaotic Abominable Snowman, as their levels were already high, they only got up one level to reach Level Thirteen.

Even so, it was already horrifying enough.

They were passively triggered by Garen to level up, especially Rosta and Elphis who were pressed to choose an ability that they were proficient at as a core and upgraded straight to Level Ten.

Garen’s engulfment went on for a week.

His aura, too heightened over a week before it ended.

Cold Winter Tower’s ripple level could not be differentiated. With a thick layer of distorted dream power surrounded Cold Winter Tower, no one would know for sure to what stage Garen has reached.

But everyone, every dragon, knew that Garen must have far surpassed Demigod and reached an unknown realm.

******

In the Seventeenth Layer of the Abyss. Barren land.

A shade of yellow mist shadowed the sky, reeling in a heavy and suppressed feeling.

This were the dwellings of the Abyssal Demon Dragons and White Dragon Mountain. As the layer of the Abyss with the biggest changes in temperature, the territories could reach up to several thousand in temperature degree, yet there were also some areas with temperatures so terrifyingly low that everything froze there.

Red, dark red, blood red, golden red, a sea of magma occupied half the region of this plane.

Ice blue, purple-blue, pale blue, black blue, endless glacier snow mountains occupied the other half of this plane.

White Dragon Mountain was at the highest peak at the mid-point of this entire Abyss plane.

In a cavity of a huge snow mountain.

Thousands of White Dragons gathered to attend the frequently-held Elder’s Meeting in the huge square. Standing at the highest point, the evil eyes of ancient dragons and elders glimmered.

They were staring together at a space in a cavity, seemingly waiting for something.

White Dragons here were quite different from Dragon King Peak. The dragons here mostly balanced out the levels of their spellcraft and Draconic Aura. Their entire disposition was far higher than Dragon King Peak.

No one made a sound. Only ripples from voice transmitting spells were ricocheting in the air.

It was dead silence in the cavity.

The leading dragon was the remaining White Dragon’s Great Elder, Gaelain. She was clenching the Frozen Spell Beads tightly in her hands. The beads were Imprint Divine Weapon that represented Royal Chief of the White Dragons.

Hiss…

Finally, a black rift in the shape of an eye ripped open in space. From it, soldiers in white armor marched out with a strong Void aura.

Over ten strong existences were top notch experts far higher than Level Ten.

“White Feather Squadron…” Great Elder Gaelain said in a low voice. She exchanged glances with the other two elders on the side. As one of the few high-level dragons that could transform into human form, she naturally sensed the capability of these existences the first second. The other party did not show any intention to conceal and arrogantly put their individual strong forcefield on full blast.

Following them, was a powerful swordsman dressed in a black heavy armory. It was Andrew, the terrifying general that commanded tens of legion in the Abyss.

Chapter 1370: General Trend 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I represent my Master to take over the forces of White Dragon Mountain. I am Andrew Gordra. Please hand over the authority,” the powerful swordsman removed his helmet, revealing his handsome, fair face. His eyes were burning in purple flames, representing the core ability of him advancing to Level Ten.

“I wonder if Lord Garen…”

“Master is extremely busy and has no time to attend to this little matter,” Andrew cut off the Great Elder’s speech.

“Little matter!!?” The Great Elder expression fell.

The entire White Dragon Clan switching allegiance was a little matter?! She forced down her heart of dissatisfaction and piled up a smile.

“Our main clan is facing the pressure of the Abyssal Demon Dragons and is in imminent peril. I wonder if Lord Garen is…?”

“Master has his own arrangements,” Andrew dully replied. The forcefield of his aura was distorting and tumbling about from the recent upgrade to Level Thirteen. It was difficult for him to control.

Currently, in the entire White Dragon Clan, only the Great Elder and Second Elder were at Level Thirteen. The rest were beneath that. The strongest Level Fifteen chief perished during the battle with Garen and since then the clan has been in an awkward state. It was only when the incarnation of Tiamat fell in the hands of Garen that the White Dragon Clan panicked.

It was during then when the Abyssal Demon Dragons launched their attack, in an attempt to gobble up this piece of fat meat when White Dragon Clan was at their weakest.

Under such ill conditions, everyone underestimated the White Dragon Clan’s limit to their lack of integrity. They begged Garen for mercy. They would have Garen take the place as King of White Dragons and worship Garen as the White Dragon Clan’s new Dragon God.

In exchange for Garen’s assistance to the main clan.

But who would have thought that Garen would only send over one subordinate and only a Level Thirteen one at it!?

Such an ability was not enough to retaliate against the terrifying Abyssal Demon Dragons with Demigod capabilities!

“Master has already personally gone to take care of the Abyssal Demon Dragons. You don’t have to worry about it.”

Andrew’s response was simple. Personally took care of it? To what extent? Was it retreat or defend? There was no further information on it.

“Alright, hand over the Chief’s Divine Weapon,” Andrew looked at the Great Elder, the purple flame in his eyes flickered.

Having reached this stage, Gaelain did not have any more choices, neither did the White Dragon Clan. If they did not want to be diminished to smithereens then this was the only path to take.

Garen played a decisive role between the forces of the Void and Dragons of Disasters and his importance surpassed that of the White Dragon Clan. It did not matter whether White Dragon Clan existed or not.

Gaelain gritted her teeth, flew up gently and landed toward Andrew.

Garen was formally announced as the new King of White Dragons, replacing the White Dragon King as well as Tiamat to be the strongest existence among the White Dragon Clan.

Once the Abyssal Demon Dragons got a hold of this news, they remotely negotiated with Garen and tacitly approved of Garen’s action to merge the White Dragon main clan.

Both parties initiated some small-scale probing and the final verdict was that the Abyssal Demon Dragons acknowledged and honored Garen as the Double-Pupiled White Dragon King.

Meanwhile, a lava sea region turned to become a poisonously dead region in the polar region of the Abyssal plane, that even the strongest Demon Dragon King would not survive there.

******

Time flew by quickly and it was ten years later.

The rumors of Child of Hell spread far and wide that almost all war survivors claimed they saw his existence.

While the Void and native land were at war, it allowed the Child of Hell to accelerate his growth.

Eye of the Slaughter launched a new battlefield with various major elemental planes in the Inner Plane. Distortion Demon Master took the entire East by force, wiping out the forces of the Church again and again.

The Void Temple of Fallen True Soul wantonly launched full attacks with forces of all Gods in the main plane. The attacks did not allow any chance for the Gods to gasp for air or give them to recuperate.

Divine Powers was severely exhausted and the Gods were weakening quickly.

Preying Demon Masters and True Spirits were like hunters on the side observing their hunted’s last struggle, awaiting the Gods to exhaust to death.

No one was willing to sustain the prey’s deathly blow.

The native world was becoming dead that with void rifts appearing in the Abyss and Hell, the multitude of Void Creatures was surprising the Demons and Devils of the two major regions.

The Blood Wars seemed to have transformed into a chaotic battle between Demons, Devils, and Void Creatures.

In these ten years, Garen continued to hunt. The five Generals under him reigned slaughter everywhere. Out of the five, Elfie and Satwo died in war while the remaining three Generals overcame the test of blood and fire, rising to the top.

The divine inventory and creatures that were hunted were transported to Cold Winter Tower.

At the same time, Garen was purchasing various Divinity from Void Creatures.

He had collected all the Divinities that he could in these years, only those that were remote or complicated Divinities were left.

Such as Light and Fire Purifying Divinity, War Divinity, and Lady Shar’s Demon Web Wizardry Divinity.

These belonged to the Upper Compound Divinity. Its complexity was beyond any simple individual Divinity. Its calculation was massive and challenging.

But even so, Garen absorbed more than a hundred different Divinities and Divine Personas through collecting and structuring of Divine Personas.

His Soul Ring structure went from yellow level, stepping into Upper-Level Demon Lord stage, to leaping into unknown boundaries.

Even he did not know if he was considered a True Spirit.

The Soul Rings themselves reached their highest hue, all seven colors were achieved. The accumulation of Soul Rings and even the absorbing of created Divine Personas had his Soul Rings producing a special and different glow from the other Demon Lords.

It was although the entire Soul Ring structure emitted an all-knowing special glow.

The Divinities were easily obtained. The various battlefield brought about the fall of Demigods. Many of the Demigods had more than one Divinity. Garen paid a minimum price in exchange for many Divinities. Through resources and trade, he purchased Divine Power Crystals. He consumed Divine Powers to transform into Divine Personas to be absorbed.

The pile of Divinities represented the complete perception of rules. With the clash of two worlds, these rules became common basic rules in the universe.

Very soon, as he absorbed too much, almost all Divinities started to be immune to him. Many of the Divinities were repetitive and ineffective.

The path that Garen could go forth, was already at its peak…

******

“True Spirit… As its name suggests, is finding the true you. The actual core within your heart,” Deception Demon Master and Garen were strolling on a vast blue ocean.

The sea waters did not fluctuate under their feet. It was as peaceful as the surface of a lake while outside the range of a thousand meter, waves were rumbling and tumbling with chaotic traces of windstorms and tornadoes.

Both of them seemed to be in a blissful heaven.

Deception Demon Master was dressed in a purple-red long robe. She looked like a beautiful and young regular teenager. Purple sparks intertwined between her fingers.

Tall and sturdy, Garen looked like elegant royalty strolling his territory. His shoulders were draped with a wide, white fox-skin cape.

“Divinity can have you upgraded to the highest stage. Now you’re facing the last test of entering True Spirit,” Deception Demon Master smiled. “You’re very close to True Spirit now.”

“But I’m not there yet,” Garen frowned. In recent years, his reputation as the Double-Pupiled White Dragon King was getting popular, especially after his success in escaping the wrath of God of Death. There were people who assumed his abilities has reached Middle-God level.

But no one could prove this.

Higher God was basically being a named Demon Master at a True Spirit level. Up till now, all the current Demon Masters and True Spirits in this world were at a position to face Higher Gods.

“Well, isn’t your Void Original Opus able to merge and comprise everything to discover your heart’s true code?”

Deception Demon Master smiled.

“True Spirit, isn’t that the truest soul? The real nature of souls? Then what is considered true and real?” Garen still had not grasped it. Just this explanation and definition was too ambiguous.

Now that Divinities were ineffective to him, his Soul Rings has crystalized almost every perception of information that was obtainable. Perhaps in all of Demon Masters, he was considered the most complete.

So much so that his Soul Ring structure began emerging in a special glow that he himself could not comprehend.

Word that he could perfect Divinities has long gotten out and many other Demon Masters swiftly did the same and a lot of Divinities and Divine Personas were imitated. Although these other Demon Masters did not have Garen’s powerful calculation ability, there were many of them and everybody was working toward the same goal.

Some of them even sought after Garen to buy the Divinities and Divine Personas required to complete their own Soul Ring structure.

This was a prosperous time for the Void!

Deception Demon Master was the closest to Garen and traded many Divinities and Divine Personas with him. She, too, entered uncharted realms.

“Your accumulation is too much that a regular Demon Lord couldn’t possibly be as well-equipped as you are. Your current structure is basically equivalent to us old folks who have lived tens of thousands of years, maybe even more. With such a collection, you should find one that could comprise all nature with perception. Once you enter True Spirit, your powers will erupt to an unimaginable height.”

“This is an era of achievements. It will be soon when other Demon Lords imitate me,” Garen was not bothered. He took the path of Divinities and Divine Personas and now there were already many Demon Lords imitating him.

“But you’re different,” Deception Demon Master smiled. “Your physique, your dragon body is overwhelmingly powerful…”

Garen was struck in the heart.

His Soul Ring structure could provide him over a thousand Potential Points every day. These Potential Points, together with the endless massacre by his three Generals, provided him with many high-level energy crystal cores and soul energies absorbed from divine weapons. All these added up to five thousand Potential Points each day.

Such a state had been going on for over a year. During this period, he leveled up the most here. All his Potential Points were added to his attributes.

If other Master Demon and True Spirits could imitate, then the surge of Potential Attribute Points was something that no other beings would be able to imitate or learn.

“You’re actually not a true True Spirit anymore. At the very least, the growing rate after becoming a True Spirit wouldn’t reach the strength of your body,” Deception Demon Master casually commented. “After all this time, your Divine Personas are still at the lowest level, then where did the Divine Power crystals that you purchased go?” She smiled mysteriously.

Naturally, they became Potential Points.

Garen did not answer but looked at his overall attributes.

‘Garen — Strength 1120, Agility 1160, Vitality 1160, Intelligence 2400 with potential ???, Soul Limit ???.

12 Soul Rings: Five colorless, red, orange, yellow, green, cyan, blue, purple.

Level 15 Draconic Aura. Level 15 Arcane Art.

Void Original Opus — 100%. Hind Limbs — Evil Soldier, Wings — Seven Lives, Tail — Demonic Book, Front Limbs — Hellfrost Peacock Queen.

Comprehensive evaluation — All-Knowing God: Divinity 1. Title — Double-Pupiled White Dragon King, Evil Eye Dragon King.

Potential qualities — Divine Creature, Void Hunter.’

Chapter 1371: Decisive Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His attributes had reached an absurd stage.

Garen himself did not know how much destruction he would cause if he were to go full force maximum.

He only knew from facing God of Death the last time, it only caused a little harm. He recovered completely after half a day.

“Are you coming with us to the Decisive Battle?” Deception Demon Master invited in a low voice.

“This is the final battle?”

“The last one,” Deception Demon Master nodded. “Your ability has reached its limit. Perhaps the battlefield will bring you realization.”

Garen slowly nodded.

The only thing he could do now was to stir up his attributes so it would level up gradually.

With many of his Potential Points becoming Attribute Points, the calculation of his Willpower mind saw no bottom line. He has not once wielded his powers completely in battle.

With his attributes breaking through a thousand points, he additionally obtained a qualitative change of special supernatural abilities.

His Strength could naturally erupt huge quakes while his Agility produced instant mobility to extremely far distance. He was also immune to all time genre spells.

In terms of Vitality, he has super-fast regeneration ability. He could use his super-fast regeneration ability once a day. As long as his body was at least 50% complete, he could recover entirely. The only thing exhausted would be his Potential Points.

His Intelligence has a double-whammy effect. One hit would instantly combust into double the impact.

Truth be told, even Garen knew that he surpassed that of a regular True Spirit. Just his attributes were terrifying enough and could suppress many existences.

How powerful were a thousand points of Strength? Apart from himself, no one knew. Even Deception Demon Master has not seen him in action for a long time.

******

The seventh battlefield.

Distortion Demon Master opened up the middle section of the Primary Substance Plane, an area of energy distortion between the Alliance of the Gods and Mother Stream Alliance.

The battle between True Spirit Demon Master and the Gods had this region converting into a dead region. The passing of God of Moon and Love even allowed this region to turn into an immeasurable mysterious area.

The dark night camouflaged the entire region. From the outside, it was an ordinary landscape of mountain range, but entering a certain range, one would be taken away from a distorted time-space energy into a different dimensional world.

With no additional cannon fodder army, even high-level generals were not brought along.

The Alliance of the Gods were trapped within a defense ball here, giving their last as trapped beasts.

Garen followed Deception Demon Master to participate with the Void Temple and Mother Stream Alliance team heading to this region. This was the last battle that would decide the fate of this world. In actual reality, anybody would know that there was not any suspense as the fate had been sealed when The Void first invaded.

Mother Stream Alliance was a vast uncountable universe. Each universe bred groups of creatures that was similar to this world. For such a large group to invade such a tiny world, this was the great disparity of strength between the major world.

At war, Void Creatures and True Spirits were tempered to the strongest on record. The power of the Gods was weakened to the extreme as their believers were slaughtered.

It was imaginable that the last battle would be the last in the native world and perhaps then, there would not be any trace of it left behind.

******

Amidst the grey fog, Garen and a team were walking down a path in the forest.

On the side was a cliff erected with wooden railings. The fog extended forward to an unknown distance.

The chirping of birds could be heard indistinctly. It could be an owl or some other creature.

The team was draped in black cape, covering their entire body that their faces could not be seen. Not a spot of their skin was exposed.

Garen was the same. Lifting his head up, he could only see the back of the person walking in front. Just like him, the person was wrapped in a black tattered cape. He could hear sounds of light but hurried footsteps.

He shifted his head over to glance to his right. Deception Demon Master’s somewhat familiar face was hidden beneath the cape. He could only see a little of her silhouette from the side.

“This is the Lost Path. Fallen True Soul teamed up with all True Spirits to use Moon Goddess’s Divine Persona and the Divine Kingdom to overshadow their dream powers and turned this place to a huge world, in other words, a small universe.”

A whisper was heard coming from the front of the team. It was a woman.

Garen was struck, he could hear it was the voice of Distortion Demon Master.

“The Lost Path. Only by following this Black Cape Team that one could enter the real fog or else even a God could not leave this pale blue fog,” Distortion Demon Master said in a low voice.

The Black Cape Team rustled forward, making a turn and heading out further.

A woman in black outfit carrying an umbrella appeared on the path ahead. Covered by the black umbrella, her face could not be seen but her entire person stood firmly in the middle of the road, facing the incoming Black Cape Team without saying a word.

“Don’t look at her!” Garen was about to look in detail when suddenly, Deception Demon Master slapped the back of his hand.

“That is a chaotic symbol that represents confusion!”

“Chaotic symbol?”

“Yes, any existence that glances or sees her face would be completely lost in confusion in this fog. The crystallization of this symbol has entrapped three Middle Gods and one Higher God of this native world,” Deception Demon Master transmitted her voice. “Alright, let’s not talk.”

Garen immediately halted his urge to ask.

Following the team, he slowly walked past the woman with the black umbrella. That woman quietly stood in the middle of the road, letting the Black Cape Team through.

Garen only saw her pair of legs.

That was a pair of female human’s legs. It was pale and fine and wore a pair of red shoes but on them were black dot marks, giving a sense of bad omen.

Passing the woman with the black umbrella, the team walked on a distance before letting out a sigh of relief.

“Everyone, please be careful and do not leave the Black Cape Team. Please also do not come in contact the Black Capes that are not of our members. They are this small world’s natural phenomenon, not substantial and after contact, it is not a matter that I can be in control of.” Distortion Demon Master reminded.

“Now the Gods seemed to have released something that causes the entire little dream world to escape the control of Lord Fallen True Soul. It is flooded with many things that we can’t comprehend.”

Garen was shocked.

Initially, he thought that this Black Cape Team consisted of Demon Masters or True Spirits but now it looked as though that most of them were not.

Becoming wary, he continued with the team to go forth in the fog. On the left was a black forest, wavering with the wind. On the right was a train of black railings and beyond it was a cliff shadowed by fog.

It was unknown how long more did they have to go forward like this.

Finally, about more than half an hour later, the fog surrounding the team grew faint.

Swish!

Garen felt his head sunk. His sight became blurry and he suddenly found himself leaving the originally fog-covered region.

Standing under the dark starry sky, the black forest encircled them. They were still standing on a winding path.

The only difference was, the left of the path was woods while the right was barren trees. The treetops looked like plates holding up the golden red moon.

It was as though the moon in the sky had fallen down and landed on the top of these trees.

“Fallen Divine Region,” Garen heard Deception Demon Master’s voice.

“Garen, be careful. It is the Time-Space Chaos Region here, do not break away from this path. Once you leave, you will be tossed into a deranged time-space rift that you can’t return from.”

“Each one of us can’t see anybody else now. We can only make our choice to head forward. From now on, you may encounter any trapped God on this path. The battle has officially begun. Do not worry about attacking or destroying anything. Even the true form of Fallen True Soul is unable to destroy anything here,” Distortion Demon Master warned.

“Each moon on the big tree represents a fallen Demon Master or God here.”

Garen was on the alert.

This peculiar world that seemed like a dream or rather, Fallen True Soul has moved dreamland into the world of this universe and used a completely different set of dream rules to limit the native advantages of the Gods.

He glanced to his left and right but did not see anybody.

As he paced forward slowly, Garen removed his black cape on it and carefully sensed his surroundings.

As a Higher Demon Lord, even a True Spirit who was not a True Spirit, he was far familiar with the dreamland than any regular Demon Lord and Gods.

After walking a distance, Garen saw two chairs displayed by the roadside at the forest.

The black wooden chairs were facing each other on the grass as though somebody was sitting on them a while ago.

It was eerily quiet. A sense of suppression slowly crept in.

“A chair by the road meant a brief halt and rest.” Garen’s face changed and took large strides towards the chairs.

Cling.

Suddenly, everything before him broke. His vision blurred and he was now in a sea of clouds.

A large whale made of white cloud leaped out from the sea of cloud from afar and jumping back into it.

Blood red balls hung like cocoons in the sky.

“Power of dream…” Garen recognized the nature of these huge balls. This was a commonly used locking tremor of battle tactic by Demon Masters. Each bloody cocoon represented a battlefield. In it was at least one Demon Master or True Spirit at a battle to the death.

More than ten giant balls levitated quietly above the cloud ocean without moving. There was not a sound.

“It’s about time to end everything.” Suddenly a screeching voice was heard behind Garen.

He immediately turned around and saw two golden glowing balls charging from below the cloud ocean, aiming at him.

“Tiamat? And, God of Death?” Garen narrowed his eyes and watched as the two golden glowing balls shot over.

The glowing balls transformed into a white and red figure. One was a weirdo with five heads while another was in a black robe, the face bore a pair blood-shot gleaming eyes.

Two divine auras intertwined and wrapped around Garen.

‘Divine aura territory under coverage… Divine Personas has not reached the minimum standard, Vitality to immunize…’

His Willpower mind provided feedback and the two divine auras were repelled by Garen.

His above thousand points Vitality has reached a never-before stage. As long as it was not from a Higher God, he could immediately repel the majority of divine auras in this world.

“Despicable Void Creature! Even if we are banished together, I will not allow you to obtain this world!!” God of Death bellowed in anger.

“Despicable?” Garen’s brow raised. He watched as the two Gods raised their arms, and five-colored Dragon Breath and black and red colored Ray of Death erupted. Garen’s sight was drowned in multi-colors.

Wham!!

One punch.

Garen only punched out gently.

The Divine Powers-structured attack dispersed like bubbles.

The massive energy overpowered everything until space was smashed into cracking like black spider cobwebs headed towards the two Gods.

Like black twigs, the black spider web crazily spread and surrounded a huge fan area before Garen.

Pow pow!

With two crisp noise, the two Gods swiftly dodged and just about evaded the edge of the spider web.

“Dodge?” Garen’s expression remained unchanged.

He aimed another punch at the both of them.

Wham!!

His punch released a huge tremor. The two swiftly evaded. Just from the quake of his strength ripples, they could tell that Garen’s strength far exceeded a logical range. If God Damnators and Giant Beasts has the power and blaspheming Divinities ability revered by the Gods, then Garen’s powers must have reached its maximum and could destroy every rule.

That tremendous quake was a naturally derived attack.

Chapter 1372: Decisive Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Godhead and Gods merely had stronger attributes on average, a higher resistance towards Spells, sharper perception and fields of vision, and a plethora of powerful regulated Divine Power types of spells in comparison to normal creatures.

However, when they were facing Garen’s regulated strength that was pure to its maximum limit, all of their abilities were simply jokes. Garen’s regulated strength had already reached the Higher God stage. Moreover, since he did not have to consume Divine Power, he could simply squander it freely. The Higher Gods that faced him would only be exhausted to death while they were still alive.

Meanwhile, their Spellcrafting-type of spell control would scatter from the quakes of the intense power vibrations before they could even approach it. Furthermore, Garen’s powerful Vitality and Agility would be directly immune to Space-Time Spells and Negative Spell states.

All attack-type spells had become useless jokes.

The only thing effective would be direct hand-to-hand fights!!

“Damn! This monster!!” God of Death dodged the quake of another punch-like attack. The protective Divine Power shield on his body actually almost collapsed when the attack merely brushed against its edges.

“He’s a great deal stronger than before!”

Tiamat was even worse off. She was scratched twice continuously and half of her body was dripping in Holy Blood, she was near to being critically injured.

“We must definitely buy some time for the Major God Fehra!” Both of the Gods could see the determination in each other’s eyes when their gazes met.

Roar!!

Tiamat transformed into her dragon body immediately. She turned into an enormous dragon with five heads that was over hundreds of meters large and rushed towards Garen fiercely.

God of Death transformed into his original body as well. He was a colossal black monster that resembled a rhino. Strangely, he had rhino heads on both his front and back which made it difficult to distinguish its foremost part from its rear.

The rhino which possessed a body that was over thousands of meters long was charging directly towards Garen.

“Meaningless struggle.” Garen’s expression remained indifferent when he was looking at the two enormous creatures that were charging towards him. He brazenly rushed towards them frontally.

Boom!!

An incomparably violent thunderstorm exploded behind the trio at this moment.

The biggest bloody cocoon in the sky had burst.

Numerous thunderstorms detonated the other bloody cocoons in their surroundings before several continuous explosions rang out.

Boom boom boom boom!

While the numerous explosions rang out, various bouts of bloody Dream Power that was mixed with an abundance of Divine Power storms swept over before a gigantic hole exploded directly through the sea of clouds.

Garen pulled back from the colorful energy storm suddenly and raised his hands to cover his face. He steadied his body as much as he could. However, he was still blown to the point where he was slanted from shaking slightly.

Meanwhile, Tiamat and God of Death were simply sent flying to an unknown place after they were blown away.

These skills that were merely displayed in the blink of an eye had erupted the sea of clouds in the faraway sky into a huge explosion.

Boom!!

There was a golden glossy mushroom-like cloud that rose slowly like a nuclear bomb. There was even a circular blood colored halo beside the floating clouds.

“Fehra, Mother Nature, everything has ended. This world is destined to die out and we’ll turn into nutrients for the Void…” roared an irritable voice.

The assault of the mushroom cloud’s explosion lashed against Garen’s body that was in mid-air.

Whoosh!!!

Numerous energy winds that resembled knives ripped Garen’s clothes and skin. However, there was a light distortive energy field layer on his entire body. It was a special defense that evolved naturally when his Vitality and Strength had reached excessively high levels.

“That’s the battlefield of the Higher Gods which is also the battlefront of the peak True Souls and Demon Masters.” Garen measured his current strength carefully. If he counted backward and recalled the previous energy storm, the energy level of the battle there probably did not surpass his expectations too greatly.

“Fehra and Mother Nature resisted but lose their True Souls and Distortion Demon Master. From the looks of it, I can probably participate in the battles of this level. However, I can only protect myself at best. Moreover, this doesn’t benefit me. I should find a place where the advantages are most abundant.”

He pondered briefly before looking down at the large hole that exploded through the sea of clouds.

There was really an unimaginably enormous battlefield below. Numerous Abyss Hell Demons, Devils, various other elemental creatures, and the Warriors that united this great Plane were currently fighting fiercely and slaughtering the inexhaustible Void Creatures.

Blood and Soul Fragments sputtered around endlessly.

The battlefield resembled a chaotic rubbish dump that was on fire when one looked down at it from a higher place. Gaudy colors and shades of red, white, and black mixed and made it difficult to distinguish the factions clearly.

On the continuous stretch of a white mountain range, the fierce fight between the Demon Lords and Lower Gods had broken the mountaintop directly while several deep ravines and holes were smashed in the ground.

Long stretches of cloudy white explosions could be seen spreading around occasionally. They were either infinite shrouds of red clouds that had exploded after condensing into photospheres or intense thunderstorms.

These were the results of the collapsed energy that was naturally triggered when the various Divine Power Spells mixed with the unnatural powers of the Void.

“Weave is broken…” Garen could sense that holes that were getting bigger and bigger had instantly appeared in Weave which was initially everywhere in space. These tremendous and terrifying energy attacks now made it resembled a torn fishing net.

Space-time had even collapsed, let alone Weave that was established in space.

Ahh!!!

A sharp, blood-curdling shriek of a woman echoed in the distance suddenly.

Numerous bouts of energy that resembled purple electric currents exploded frenziedly and shot towards all four corners in waves like a snake that was extending quickly.

“Another Higher God has fallen.” Garen did not look at the situation over there but merely flew straight towards the great battlefield below.

Every world had its own pivotal points.

Garen had already realized this law. Thus, he was actually seeking the pivotal point of this world.

The legendary Child of Hell.

When he was flying towards the lower part of the sky, he suddenly felt a faint form of loneliness rising in his heart.

After transmigrating through so many worlds and living through various experiences, these transmigrations that happened time and time again were actually a type of weary, repetition.

“Maybe… I should find a place to have a good rest for some time…” Garen suddenly recalled the Earth that he had left in the beginning.

When he was still a normal person, he was merely rushing about and working for the sake of trivial mortality. However, the satisfaction that he received at that time seemed to be much greater than what he was getting now.

The battlefield before his eyes grew closer and clearer while a thought formed in Garen’s mind suddenly.

Once everything had ended, perhaps he should find something that he desired…

Now that he had reached this level, the eternity that he was previously pursuing was already achieved in this realm of Demon Masters and True Souls. His lifespan seemed to resemble the Mother Stream’s own in the sense that it was infinite.

However, what about after eternity?

Large amounts of Soul Fragments rose on the battlefield continuously. They were endlessly swallowed and absorbed into Garen as most of the Demon Lords around him could not challenge him at all.

He resembled an enormous black hole that was flying above in the sky. All of the local creatures and powerhouses that were shrouded by his shadow stood motionless like wax figures instantly before melting and perished.

The impressive abilities of his Natural Poison Region had achieved unimaginable extents and could diffuse out within intervals of several thousand meters.

Numerous souls were transformed into Potential Points by his Divine Weapon. They upgraded Garen’s attributes continuously.

******************

Within a remote ravine on the border of the battlefield.

Bumpy and fragmented ground that was filled with bumps was everywhere inside the white ravine. Rocks were scattered messily and had fallen all around. Corpses, burning poisonous fire, and leftover blue phosphorescence lit the entire ravine somewhat dimly.

This area was the aftermath of collapsed energy. Regardless of whether they were Void Creatures or local creatures, they were all exhausted or dead from their injuries.

Only a few of the strongest survivors were still hiding in the corners while struggling at death’s door. These were either several individuals with feeble Divine Power or Demon Masters that did not have any strength left to fight respectively. Strangely, the two groups who were initially supposed to be hostile factions were apparently standing together side by side now to face the dark shadow in front.

“Child of Hell… you actually… actually wanted to devour us together as well!!” A feeble Divine Power God rebuked the shadow angrily.

Within the brief moment of that explosion, the shadow instantly appeared again. After it had swallowed both of the similar Children of Hell simultaneously, it began pursuing and hunting for their survivors everywhere.

Only five or six survivors out of more than ten of them remained from the factions on both sides now.

The rest of them were all engulfed inside this fellow.

“We are the only hope in this world. Since all you pieces of trash are so useless, wouldn’t it be much better for me to contribute some nourishment?” The shadow materialized slowly and turned into a purely pitch-black Colossal Dragon.

Whoosh!

Two Void Shadows shot over from the sky suddenly. One of them was a woman with long billowing blue hair and rays of blue light flashing across her entire body.

The other one was dressed in a white suit of armor. He wore boxing gloves on both hands and emitted terrifying chills. He was an impressive-looking man.

“Elphis!!” Yelled one of the long black-haired women among the survivors below suddenly.

The blue long-haired woman in the sky paused briefly and looked down before she happened to see the black-haired woman in the group.

“Nadia?”

She shot over and flew there while the man rushed over flying downward frantically as well.

“Didn’t you leave Cold Winter Tower to travel alone?” asked Elphis in a surprised tone.

After considering it previously, Nadia finally decided that she was unwilling to be forced to accept a position from someone else. Since she had obtained an opportunity to improve herself again, she chose to take risks and travel alone to hunt the creatures of this world so that she could upgrade herself.

The current Nadia looked like she had already obtained Level Thirteen powers. It appeared that this past decade was not merely wasted.

However, Nadia instantly felt a faintly unpleasant feeling when Elphis landed.

Elphis and Rosta who were previously under her had apparently already reached the levels of Upper Demon Masters now. Their bodies were naturally emitting Energy Field domains that were similar to the Holy Auras of Lower Gods.

When she associated it with her own challenging and laborious hardships during the past decade and the dangers that she experienced with great difficulty before she could upgrade herself to Level Thirteen, Nadia’s mind was indescribably muddled.

They simply did not have to ask why she had appeared on the battlefield of the Great Decisive Battle. After the Great Decisive Battle, the chance to upgrade rapidly again would disappear completely because the local world would suffer destructive attacks. Next, it would weaken quickly.

Once she had missed this opportunity, it would be highly unlikely that she could even dream of upgrading or evolving again. She would have to waste a lot of time and energy even if it was possible.

“Be careful!” Nadia’s heart trembled suddenly when the shadowy Black Dragon pounced on Elphis from the back abruptly after she had landed.

“Child of Hell?!” Elphis had also noticed the severity as her enemies were apparently the infamous Child of Hell!

This group was extremely troublesome because they could not seem to be killed. They could separate their bodies into numerous individuals that could leap across space as they pleased before they chose a random individual to resuscitate their own bodies. In other words, if all of their bodies were not found completely, it would be impossible to kill them until the end of time.

Chapter 1373: Collapse 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Shield!

A round and transparent shield appeared behind Elphis suddenly before it blocked off Simon’s attack firmly.

However, it was only a second before the round shield broke. A crashing noise rang out as the Dark Colossal Dragon charged at Elphis.

“Lower God’s aura… Die!!” Simon’s black claw suddenly morphed into a black shadow that shot over as if his body did not have a fixed state at all.

Wind Shield!

Elphis stepped backward while her Divine Power stirred her Divine Domain hurriedly as it burst forth.

An enormous crystal shield that was over ten meters tall appeared before her.

Her Divine Domain consisted of defensive and peaceful Divine Power as well as weakened Divine Power. She had yet to establish a Divine Country just like Garen. Furthermore, she was only using her Divine Domain to execute an explosion that could only be used once. Although its sustained combat abilities were greatly weakened by this, she could prevent it from being dragged down by the Thread of Faith.

Pop!

The black shadow claw collided against the crystal shield before numerous black specs of light sputtered. Strangely, these black specs of light condensed back into a black claw behind the shield again before continuing towards Elphis in a grabbing motion.

Shh!

Elphis could not react in time, the claw scratched her arm violently. Her body vanished instantly before it flickered and appeared more than ten meters away from the side of Rosta’s body.

“Freeze!”

Rosta had just happened to release his Divine Authority Ability.

White chills swept over like mist and shrouded every single area around him completely. A form of deathly stillness and absolute silence seeped through the mist. He could vaguely hear a snakelike hissing noise.

“Blasphemy!”

Simon opened his mouth and spat out a similar gust of black gas. It met the surging white mist directly.

Both gusts of mist surged instantly. Rosta’s face stoned for a while before he charged inside the mist on his own.

Simon sneered while his figure turned into a shroud of black smoke that burrowed inside the mist as well.

A series of violent vibrating noises scattered from the mist immediately.

A dull hum rang out before Rosta flew out backward while white-gold Holy Blood trickled from the corner of his mouth vaguely.

Since he was an expert in close combat, he had never expected that victory and defeat would be determined within such a short span of time. It seemed as though the power of his opponent’s strength had reached an outrageous extent.

How did he actually achieve such a high degree when he was merely a Demigod Level Child of Hell not long ago?!

Numerous shrouds of black smoke drifted out of the mist and rapidly turned into an enormous pitch-black Colossal Dragon that was over ten meters long. The dragon roared, shaking and dissipating all of the surrounding white mist.

The tremendous sound waves even quaked this ravine until it shook and swayed endlessly.

Both Rosta and Elphis’ faces paled before they pounced on Nadia simultaneously, seized her and ran!

“Thinking of escaping?!” Simon sneered and leaped towards them quickly. Numerous tentacles that resembled black smoke shot out from his wings suddenly and pierced through the empty space. It burrowed out of the space beside the three people instantly and tied the trio up in a bundle tightly.

“Simon.”

A white silhouette appeared in the space between the black Colossal Dragon and the trio suddenly.

The expression on Simon’s face turned serious immediately while his forehead twinkled and all of his movements halted instantly.

Rosta and the others took this opportunity to struggle free from being bound before they flew away. However, they did not escape but instead floated behind the person who had arrived with respectful looks on their faces.

“Garen…”

Although Simon had devoured numerous Children of Hell and his consciousness was already controlled by Hell’s Will, he still possessed Simon’s original memories.

“You should be calling me ‘Dragon King’.” Garen glanced indifferently at the formerly strongest prodigy of the White Dragon Clan before him who had now changed beyond recognition. He had transformed from a White Dragon to a Shapeless Dragon whose body was occupied by Hell’s Will. An abundance of pain, hatred, discontent, and fury coagulated inside his body and lingered there. He had clearly experienced numerous accounts of unimaginable pain and hardship before he was occupied.

“Why did you come out now?” asked Simon in a somber tone.

“No reason. I just made a special trip to see you in hopes that you would return to my White Dragon Clan once again.” Garen spoke in a calm tone while the overlapping pupils of his dragon eyes stared indifferently at the other party’s eyes. A shapeless tremendous pressure condensed and spiraled beside the two people’s bodies slowly before turning into gusts of wind that became more frenzied…

“Return?” Simon suspected that he had misheard. “You’re asking me to return now even though I’m a Child of Hell? Garen, are you joking or what? You were never so innocent even when you were a Dragon Whelp in the beginning.”

“You walked out of my White Dragon Clan and no one can deny that fact, right?” Garen asked instead.

“Even if that’s the case, so what?” Simon spoke disdainfully. As the strongest White Dragon King since the dawn of history, Garen’s reputation had already spread to the peak extent. Even the Abyssal Demon Dragon race could not retreat from his imposing state. The other Colorful Dragons and Metallic Dragons also acknowledged the supreme authority of the White Dragons’ domination. During these few years, certain Evil Dragon Clans that sought refuge in the Void had even continuously nominated him as the Evil Dragon King to lead the entire Evil and Colorful Dragon Clans towards glory.

Red Dragon Queen and the other major dragon clans did not utter a sound. One could see that the Double-Pupiled White Dragon King’s influence had already reached an immeasurable extent.

“It’s truly because of this that I was hoping that you’d return to the clan,” said Garen softly. “Regardless of whatever state you’ve turned into, the clan is still your home in the end and your birthplace. It’s also a place that you can depend on.”

“Don’t tell me that you’ve forgotten our White Dragon instincts? That’s truly ridiculous, Garen. This isn’t the first time that I’ve seen a White Dragon King like you. You were actually delusional enough to use emotions to move the Child of Hell. Should I call you stupid or innocent?” taunted Simon.

Garen stared at him for a moment before exhaling slowly.

“Are you saying that you’re unwilling?”

“You want me to rely on the Void? Keep dreaming!!” sneered Simon.

“Is there no room for discussion at all?” Garen attempted to redeem the situation.

“That’s enough nonsense from you!” sneered Simon.

Garen’s face turned cold gradually.

“Unfortunately…”

“What’s unfortunate?!”

“Unfortunately… you didn’t have to die initially!”

Boom!!

An unimaginably enormous White Dragon’s claw descended from the sky suddenly and pressed Simon down firmly.

The speed of the dragon’s claw seemed to be faster than lightning. It smashed down with a crash like a flashing white shadow in an instant when everyone had not reacted at all.

The survivors on site could feel themselves being blinded before an enormous White Dragon’s claw that reached the sky from the ground appeared in front of them.

Crack!

The dragon’s claw pressed down on a long stretch of soil before grabbing Simon with it and gripping him in his hand.

The dragon’s entire claw was at least thousands of meters wide on its own while its length had extended towards the borderless sky.

An enormous gaping dragon’s mouth that was over a thousand meters in size appeared behind Garen’s body suddenly. The dragon’s claw stuffed Simon and the soil into its enormous mouth directly before chewing them up intensely.

Pop!

A large amount of light black gas sputtered out of the dragon’s mouth as if it had bitten a balloon and burst it. The gas condensed into a black dragon’s body that was greatly shrunken in mid-air far away.

It was Simon!

He fled into the distance immediately without even turning around.

He had never expected that Garen actually meant it when he said that he would take action. Moreover, the strength that explosion in that split second nearly suffocated him completely, just nearly! Any more and he would have been completely engulfed and eaten by the dragon’s mouth. He had an instinct that once he was devoured by that enormous mouth, he would lose all the strength of this incarnation despite being the Child of Hell. It was important to note that he had invested almost all of his power for the sake of obtaining the greatest victory during this battle. If he was destroyed, everything that he had accumulated during these numerous years would be completely wasted!!

Garen did not chase him but simply looked on silently at Simon who was escaping as fast as he could. Although he did not destroy his opponent’s reincarnation at that moment, he had injured him heavily nonetheless.

His opponent was one of the main characters in this world. Hence, the general trends had decided that if any beings who wanted to kill him would encounter numerous obstructions and trouble.

Garen actually did not have any plans of fully burying his opponent in a grave.

Turning around, the group of survivors behind him was all gazing at each other helplessly. They did not know how to face Garen.

Several Void Creatures reacted instantly and undertook the task to immediately restrict the local powerhouses of this world who were beside them.

The few people did not dare to object and could only laugh bitterly while being captured helplessly as their powers were shackled.

Only then did Garen’s gaze fell on Nadia.

“This isn’t a place that you should’ve come.” He furrowed his eyebrows.

She was simply looking for death when she came here alone with the forces of her Level Thirteen aura.

He did not even permit Andrew to enter despite being a Demigod. The great war this time had seemed to gather the strongest powers of two of this world’s peak existences.

Any accidents that occurred in an arrangement like this would result in earth-shattering and terrifying disasters.

“Why shouldn’t I have come?” said Nadia in a dissatisfied tone. She broke free of Elphis’ protection and floated in mid-air alone.

“Since you managed to rise from the lowest level that year, so can I!!”

She looked at Garen on an equal level determinedly. However, his shapeless Coercion and the Spiritual Poison of his Poisonous Eye caused panic and fear to fill her mind unconsciously.

The Garen who still required her protection previously had already achieved an unimaginable stage now.

‘Actually, I was merely unresigned…’ Painful emotions filled her mind. Her belittlement of Garen in the beginning had now turned to praise. Ultimately, in the end, she was very glad to have met him in this strange world. She was merely unable to let go of her initial pride all along.

Frankly, she really wanted to have a good rest for some time. Depending on her previous friend Garen was not a bad decision but for some unknown reason, she could not open her mouth and request that of him every time they met.

“I will… never yield to anyone! It’d be better for you to give up!” She emphasized strongly again.

“I understand that you’ve made your decision.” Garen nodded faintly.

Bang!

Elphis’ fist collided against Nadia’s abdomen suddenly. The tremendous pain and the cold air that was coordinated by Rosta on the side caused her to faint instantly.

Garen appeared beside Nadia’s body immediately before he lifted her with one hand.

“Let’s go.”

Rosta smiled helplessly.

“Was she really unaware that if the difference was too great, any spiritual activities in front of a Higher God would be easily caught by the other party…”

When Elphis saw how she had fallen out with her previous arch-rival as if they were children, a faintly weird feeling lingered in her heart for unknown reasons.

“Perhaps she was truly unaware…” she added quietly.

The three people teleported immediately and vanished from their original spots.

***************

Main Substance Plane

Vast stretches of the earth were dried up and cracked. Numerous cracks and split marks extended throughout the ground and gradually grew longer and wider before finally turning into deep crevices.

Scorching auras of destruction flared up from these crevices.

The sky was a vast expanse of blood red shades. Long stretches of the corpses of True Soul Gods floated into the sky. Some of them had rotted already and transformed into numerous empty islands while there were other evil beings that had already turned into God Damnators.

The cities and moats of the Primary Plane had collapsed already.

When the Great Decisive Battle started, Star Region Demon Master and Eye of Massacre led numerous armies respectively and began their great slaughter throughout the entire Main Substance Plane simultaneously.

All living creatures including animals, plants, and sea creatures were killed.

The entire Plane was deathly still as even the Undead had no way to live because the Souls were also devoured by the Void Creatures.

Numerous black Spaceships with golden halos in front would fly past occasionally in the sky. They were Void Battleships. These Battleships that had beetle-like exteriors could use their golden halos like pincers to cut off any solid substances or Divine Bodies. They were responsible for managing the various harmful evolved creatures after the war.

This world was on the verge of collapsing.

Chapter 1374: Collapse 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Translation

Dragon King Peak

Several red flashes of lightning would streak across the blood-red sky occasionally.

One after another, the White Dragons formed a defensive forbidding protective circle on the ground and in the sky around Dragon King Peak. Faint halos were being emitted from the very top of Cold Winter Tower. It shrouded the entire area within a vicinity of several thousand kilometers and protected this area from various disasters and threats.

Ultimate strength was the only true safeguard during the periods of calamity.

Inside a hole in the middle level of Dragon King Peak.

Several busts and portraits of Garen when he was in his human form were engraved on the walls that were covered in ice. They seemed like countless pairs of eyes that were staring at the group of guests who were seated in the middle.

Snow City Master brought his daughter Asilia and sat upright on the cushions. Soaring Wing King was in front of him while a few representatives from Snow City had followed him from behind as well as Boris and Leona who had not returned for a long time.

This Level Fifteen Great Arcanist Urvac Dragon had personally brought his daughter here to Dragon King Peak to apologize for his wrongdoings.

He was here to apologize for the previous incident regarding Garen’s banishment. Since White Dragon Mountain had even admitted defeat, on what basis could he refuse to yield?

After White Dragon Mountain had submitted and pledged their allegiance, Andrew made up an excuse to get rid of a large number of high-level individuals and powerhouses who were suspected of targeting Garen in the beginning. The massacre resulted in more than hundreds of White Dragon Corpses. This was an undeniable catastrophe to the entire clan that only had a total population of several thousand.

Great Elder was apparently unable to bear it anymore due to this. They could well imagine the extent that Garen’s current forces and influence had already reached.

Urvac Dragon hurriedly brought his daughter Asilia here to apologize as soon as he had received this information.

Obviously, he was not solely here to apologize for his wrongdoings. He also had plans to request for support and resolve the threats against Snow City when he came forward. Due to this, he had specially invited Leona and Boris, the two White Dragons who had previously left the clan. He had previously heard that they had a pretty good relationship with Garen. They were only forced to leave the clan later to evade Third Elder after they had signed Eternal Contracts.

As Snow City still fell under the jurisdiction of the Empire after all, when the Grey Shadow Society dispersed indescribably not long ago, it caused the Empire’s forces to decrease tremendously. Meanwhile, Void Creatures invaded them extensively and Snow City was incapable of guaranteeing their own safety. The forces on the highest layer were also suppressed.

Particularly when Star Region Demon Master’s large contingents engulfed them, Urvac Dragon had no choice but to yield and compromise by coming forward to Dragon King Peak to seek support. The only person nearby who could help him was Garen, whose powers were an immeasurable abyss.

“His Majesty the Dragon King is currently on an excursion. You came at an unfavorable time,” explained Annie with furrowed eyebrows when she walked into the cave. She was in charge of receiving the guests.

“It doesn’t matter, we can wait,” said Urvac Dragon sincerely. “I brought Snow City’s highest sincerity with me and I was only hoping that His Highness the Double-Pupiled White Dragon King could undertake this task once and help Snow City tide over a difficulty.”

Asilia was seated elegantly on the side. The once innocent and adorable little girl of had already turned into a beautiful and noble lady now.

“We came to apologize for the past. These are means of compensation and even if His Majesty the Dragon King is unwilling to accept it, he should at least look at these presents that represent our apology. Perhaps he may really need these things.”

She spoke unflinchingly but calmly in a tone that was neither haughty nor humble.

Annie looked at her earnestly.

“I’ll relay your intentions.” Next, she exchanged voice transmissions and said something to Leona and Boris who had come forward as well but were now seated behind. They withdrew after that.

There were only two Werewolves with flashes of blue light in their eyes who were guarding the doorway of the cave. The interior of the entire cave returned to a state of complete silence.

Now that they had reached this key moment, the defeat and destruction of the local world were already set in stone. Since they lacked the strength to reverse this desperate situation, it was also excusable that these major forces wanted to find a large tree-like support that they could cling on to evade trouble. It only depended on whether Garen was willing to accept this or not.

It was not necessary for them to exterminate the local creatures fully. After receiving various modifications, these creatures could be turned into Semi-Void Creatures that could be similarly used to transform the strength of the local world and accelerate the destruction methods.

Garen’s Distorted Seeds and Biochemical Pools were modified using this method as well.

Northlands was merely a small area while phenomena like these were constantly appearing in most of the other areas now. Most of the local forces had given up on resisting and sought help from the Void forces instead. The situation was becoming clearer now…

Seconds and minutes passed.

Finally, a group of people entered the cave opening.

The leaders of the group were indeed Garen, Rosta and the others who had escaped from the battlefield of the Decisive Battle recently.

Garen who was dressed in a long white cloak took long strides and walked until he was facing the standing Urvac Dragon before he sat down slowly.

“I don’t have time to listen to your idle gossip. However, I have one condition,” Garen extended his index finger before continuing, “that every single one of you Level Ten beings must accept the modifications of my Distorted Seed.”

Snow City Master became faintly angry. He had inquired clearly about the functions of the Distorted Seed during these past years. It seemed as though his life and death would be completely tied to Garen.

However, he did not have much of a choice since things had reached this stage.

“Alright, I agree!”

“Frankly, Snow City is meaningless towards me now. Its only function is to increase the number of my subordinates slightly. Aside from that, it’s completely useless. Your sincerity probably lies with that Matrix Spirit, right? Bring it over.”

Garen reached his hand out.

The Matrix Spirit that had almost caused him to fall previously was naturally the token of sincerity that the other party had brought forward this time.

As a Higher God Level individual now, his spontaneous spiritual reactions allowed him to directly and instantly understand the psychological behaviors of every single being here. Naturally, no secrets would exist in his eyes anymore.

Snow City Master did not seem surprised at all, he looked at his daughter Asilia. She stood up hurriedly, walked toward Garen slowly and knelt down before him.

“This is the Matrix Spirit.” She offered the black eggplant-like thing in her hands before Garen. “This is an apology for the incident that happened that year and a part of our sincerity. I, too… I am also a gift that is presented to Your Majesty. You may deal with me as you please.”

She lowered her head and bit her lip. Although she had prepared herself mentally for this numerous times long ago, she still had a feeling of despair as if she had finally abandoned everything when uttered this humiliating sentence face to face.

“You are…” Garen could not recognize her at the first moment as he could only discern her slightly. “Asilia? Dragon Wizard?”

“Yes.”

“What would I need you for?” Garen glanced at the eggplant in the hands before looking back at Asilia who resembled a feast for the eyes.

Pfft.

Uncontrollable guffaws echoed from the side. Rosta and his other male subordinates had dubious looks on their faces while the women blushed.

The atmosphere inside the cave became much warmer suddenly.

“That’s enough. Leave the Spirit Matrix, I’ve understood your sincerity. According to my wishes, all of the high-level individuals who are Level Ten and above must come over and accept the Distorted Seeds within three days. You will resolve everything on your own after that.” He waved his hand and stood up. “Where’s Andrew?”

“I am here.”

Andrew who has been waiting outside the cave for a while now walked in.

“Where’s Mander?”

“Captain Mander is with Her Highness Ann. It seems like the situation has developed slightly,” answered Andrew concisely.

“Is that so? I’ll go and take a look personally.”

The Great Decisive Battle had seemed to reach an inevitable outcome. Ann would be a peak Higher God Level military force. Although she was unlike Distortion Demon Master and the rest, her survival strength was second to none. After absorbing the God of Time and Shadow’s Divine Persona, she had reached an unprecedented peak in the survival aspect.

Thus, she had accidentally discovered another key aspect despite not participating in the Great Decisive Battle.

Garen’s current powers had already approached Ann’s immeasurably. Their relationship was also redetermined as Ann now treated Garen as a cooperative partner.

“Garen, aren’t you planning to greet your old friends since they’re already here?”

Annie opened her mouth suddenly to remind him. As a Dragon Guard who had been following Garen all along since the beginning, she was the only one who could speak to Garen more casually.

“You are… Boris, Leona?!”

“Long time no see…” Boris had no alternative but to stand up while Leona smiled and got up as well. Both of them were basically still shrunken versions of White Dragons. They clearly did not achieve Level Nine Arcane Art grades.

“You guys didn’t even inform me that you were here.” Garen’s expression softened immediately.

“We wanted to inform you but the problem was how do we do it?” Boris pursed his lips silently. “We were dragged here this time to come and beg for leniency for Snow City.”

“You’re both at Snow City now?” Garen was surprised.

“Yes, we were initially in the Empire’s kingdom. However, when the Empire was breached three days ago, a large fire burned all of the buildings. The fire has yet to be extinguished even now.” Leona sounded slightly gloomy.

“Your contractors are fine, right?” said Garen while furrowing his eyebrows.

“They’re fine.”

“That’s good. Since you’re already here, you should stay with me. Don’t leave.” Garen made the decision immediately and prohibited the other two from refusing.

When he saw the hesitation on their faces, he continued, “You can bring in those who have good relationships with you. As long as they are less than a hundred, I’ll accept all of them.”

Only then did Leona and Boris sighed in relief.

“We were waiting for you to say that,” said Boris unabashedly.

“It’s better to be frank. There was no reason to wait.” Garen was speechless. “Alright, I still have matters to attend to. You can settle down nearby. Arrange their accommodation for them, Annie.”

“Understood.”

Garen led Andrew towards the outside of the cave. Although the Great Decisive Battle was still ongoing, Garen’s current state of mind was not there anymore. The situation was clear but he was worried about something else.

The local world would not fully collapse so easily…

This was not referring to the creatures here but the others…

************

Bang! Bang! Bang…

Inside the white city that resembled ruins, an enormous black humanoid monster that was made up of numerous skeletons and weapons walked with heavy footsteps. It hunted all the living creatures that had a possibility of existing in this local world.

Whoosh!

Two white silhouettes descended from the sky and landed on the top of one of the ash-covered buildings before they transformed into Garen and Andrew.

The enormous monster walked past these two people but did not even seem to bat an eyelid at them.

“Destruction Corpse Giant, it’s a monster that is born from Void Energy that has been fused with the auras of death and curses of the local world. Monsters like this can be seen everywhere now,” explained Andrew while glancing at the monster.

“Where’s Ann?”

“She’s underground here.”

“Let’s go.”

Both of them walked towards a deep hole-like crevice speedily.

The giant monster on the ground had happened to find a hidden living being. It grabbed it and shoved it directly into its mouth. The living creature was a male human. Both of his legs were struggling outside his mouth. There was a cracking, biting sound before the man stopped moving and blood flowed out of the corners of the monster’s mouth. It seemed as though the entire world was shrouded in a hopeless aura.

Chapter 1375: Endless Reincarnation

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen and Andrew flew along the path of the underground crevice and they soon saw a glimpse of light purple ray.

The corpse of a frightening Eye Demon that was thousands of meters long was stuck in between the crevice silently as his huge body was obstructed by the protrusions from both sides of the walls.

The body of the Eye Demon was entirely covered with blood-streak-filled eyeballs and its tentacles were hanging freely everywhere around it.

The blood capillaries were structured similarly to of a spider web on the sclera as a viscous fluid oozed out from it.

“This is the reincarnation of the Big Mistress…” Garen squinted as he recognized the origin of this corpse.

“Looks like Master has been busy while I’m away.”

“Do you really think you’re the only one working hard?” Ann’s bad-tempered tone came out from the corpse’s core. “Come in quickly.” His tone turned feminine once more. It seemed that his tone-changing phase had arrived.

A huge hole appeared at the side of the Eye Demon’s corpse, revealing a path leading to the inside.

Garen and Andrew went inside together. It was pitch black. They found themselves in a spacious cavity after going through a thin layer of soap-like membrane.

The cavity was dyed completely in red as the walls were densely covered with blood capillaries. Ann and Golden-Winged Dragon Mother were staring together at a tall red crystal monitor.

Ann turned around and looked at Garen as she heard his movement.

“I’ve discovered something and your team captain Mander has been sent out by me to collect some samples. Have a seat.” He pointed down on the ground as stools made from meat and blood appeared.

Garen frowned as he walked towards it and sat down.

“What’s going on? This is the first time I’ve seen Master looking so serious.”

Ann took a deep breath.

“It’s not that I’m being serious, it’s just that the problem is extremely troublesome. Golden-Winged, please explain it to him.”

Golden-Winged Dragon Mother who was standing by the side walked towards them.

“We’ve discovered something. It’s man-made and seems to be something that is naturally spread out by the Child of Hell. It’s very dangerous and troublesome as if it’s some sort of a curse.”

Her face was extremely somber.

“A curse?” Garen repeated.

“Yes. A curse that is specifically targeted at Time.” Golden-Winged Dragon Mother said softly. “The Gods have their own methods in dispelling the curse. It seems to be a powerful contagion invented by them to use it against us Void Creatures.”

“So what? Since we’ve discovered it, we should have found a solution by now, right?” Garen did not believe a curse would be able to defeat the unrivaled Ann and this Demon Master True Soul.

“If only it’s that simple. It’s not hard to dispel it.” Ann continued the story. “The key thing is that when I’ve entered the Big Mistress’ reincarnated Eye Demon’s body after killing her to search for the crystals, I’ve accidentally discovered the distortion in space when I’ve connected her corpse’s unique visionary senses. There is also a blight spreading among the distortion! It’s specifically targeted at space itself.”

“You’re saying…” Garen’s expression became serious as well as he listened.

“Yes.” Ann nodded. “These two things are no longer the same and have mutated after fusing together.” He sat down and rubbed his forehead, showing a sign of fatigue.

“Master, what happens once they’ve combined together?” Andrew, who was standing by the side could not help but ask.

“The result… I’ve no idea as well.” Ann shook his head. “The best course of action is that we find a solution to this problem before it explodes. If not…”

“Problem is that from the clues that we’ve gathered, we have found out that the time curse is something emitted by the Child of Hell. On the other hand, the root that blights the space comes from no other than the Fallen True Soul!” Golden-Winged Dragon Mother sighed as her helplessness expression was written all over her face.

“The Fallen True Soul…” Garen frowned.

Thud!

Doo doo doo doo…

Out of the blue, an alarming noise came from the red crystal monitor.

Ann and Golden-Winged Dragon Mother turned around and saw blue lights sparking at the center of the revolving black vortices on the screen. It was similar to someone had sprayed paint onto it as they appeared one by one.

“The curse has exploded in some places!”

“It’s the fusion type!” Golden-Winged Dragon Mother quickly explained.

Ann turned around and she looked very serious.

“It looks like we’ll know what the result is…”

Garen stood up and looked at the monitor.

“Go to the scene immediately!”

*******************

Red thunders could be seen constantly spreading across the red sky.

Thunders rumbled in the clouds as it spread from a distance to somewhere nearby. The world had started to turn hazy as the scene looked just like someone viewing the world in a blurry telescope.

The earth, sky, objects such as the bones on the ground, dirt, stones and the wilted and distorted tree were all becoming cloudy.

A minute and strange buzzing sound kept buzzing in the area. The whole place trembled as the scene started to distort and became large and small alternatively.

Woosh!

Ann, Garen, and the others appeared at the edge of this district as they witnessed the scene.

“This is it,” Ann said softly.

Garen stared at the place but he felt that he could not see anything clearly at all. It was as if everything was constantly trembling and transforming.

“Is it the light or something else entirely?” He frowned.

“It’s not the light, it’s space,” Ann explained with a serious look. “Space here can no longer bear the curse and blight and it is falling apart.”

“What’s going to happen?”

“I don’t know.” Ann shook her head. “We’ll soon see the outcome of the curse and blight when they’re merged together. Let’s observe it quietly…” He stared at this district of a few kilometers wide attentively.

Garen did not inquire further as he waited silently as well.

The trembling noise gradually became larger and stronger.

Buzz…

It felt like countless bees were flying around one’s ear and it was irresistibly annoying.

Pew!

Suddenly, a black snake-like shadow appeared on the scene for a very brief moment before it vanished completely.

“What is that?” Garen frowned. “It looked like a snake with a pair of long wings.”

“That’s La,” Ann explained. “I’ve named them as La. It looks very similar to the shadows of the crack but only I know that it is something else entirely!”

He was an Upper God who controlled the Shadow Gods and Time Gods. Naturally, he would have the confidence to declare so.

Boom!!

Suddenly, there was a huge explosion.

The entire place shattered into countless pieces just like how a piece of glass would. These fragments were of different scenes which gave off different colors as they danced about chaotically in front of them.

The fragments dimmed as they became smaller. Then, the entire area had turned into a huge black hole!

The all-powerful gravity started to pull everything in around it.

Dirt, rubbles, wilted trees, bones and even the air. Everything was pulled in by the intense gravity as the black hole turned into a huge black sphere.

“The spacetime has collapsed…” Ann shouted. “Let’s go!”

He waved his hand as he released a layer of black light, covering all four of them. In that instant, the gravitational pull was nullified.

***********

The four of them appeared at another edge of the scene where it was also distorted and blurry. They had managed to escape from the gravitational pull without much danger.

The area was also a deserted plain. The four of them pulled some distance away from this place the moment they arrived.

“The spacetime has collapsed… we’re seriously in trouble!” Garen understood this phenomenon well. When the spacetime collapsed, time and space would be completely distorted, no one could predict or know what would happen next.

The Void Demon Masters, True Souls, and even Gods would not dare to be involved in it either.

Philosophers once theorized that when the spacetime collapsed, it meant there was a chance for one to leave this restricted universe and arrive at a more spacious and bigger universe.

They believed that the current universe was just a small corner of an even larger universe. One could temporarily leave this universe and enter an even larger and more spacious universe where the laws were more complete and with even more endless spacetime.

However, no one could prove it and man could only theorize.

“Spacetime had collapsed once before, but it was just a small area when an Upper God died. It’s nowhere near as big as the current one!” Ann looked extremely imposing. “I’ve seen the God of War fallen with my very own eyes. He was one of the strongest among the Upper God. When he died, the collapse of spacetime was less than half a meter wide. In that instant, all universal laws were nullified and there was only gravity that sucked everything in endlessly to fill in the empty space.”

“How long will the sucking last?” Garen had realized the seriousness of the situation.

“At least ten years…” Ann said. “And this kind of collapse is everywhere!!”

Howl…

A cold wind blew suddenly, carrying along with it the small amount of shadow energy.

Garen was slightly shocked as he quickly exchanged glances with Ann.

He reached out his hand and gently grabbed onto the black wind, which gathered around his nails just like thin threads that were tangling among themselves.

“The Shadow Weave has also collapsed…”

“Has Shar fallen as well? Looks like the war between the Gods is much more intense than we imagined!” Ann nodded.

“Everything is a mess. A complete mess.” Garen stared at the district where its distortion was getting worse.

Boom!

It was the same explosion and shatter as a new black hole appeared in front of them which greedily sucked in everything around it.

Woosh!

Four of them disappeared once more and appeared at another place. The moment they arrived, they instantly teleported once more as they saw a huge area shattered not far away from them. It took them a few teleportations before they arrived at a safe location.

The strong gravity induced a powerful airflow which had turned into a raging wind, blowing four of their cloaks.

“The collapse is getting faster by the minute!” Ann said in a deep tone.

“Should we inform the others?”

“It’s too late!” Ann was firm. “I’m preparing to leave this universe! To distance away from this battlefield.”

“Leave?”

“It’s a gamble! Perhaps this is how the God of Pharmacy left when the spacetime was collapsing.” Ann laughed maniacally suddenly.

Garen stared at him.

“Perhaps it’s better for you to follow me to the Void Universe.”

“It’s pointless. If I’m not wrong, the same phenomenon is happening in your Void as well…” Ann revealed a mocking expression. “This is basically the God’s last resort to perish together.”

He pondered for a moment.

“The only way right now is to find a more stable collapse and enter it by force. No one knows what the end result will be. The only option we have is to find a spacetime collapse that we can enter with a higher chance of survivability.”

“This is also the reason why I’ve been not willing to participate in the war.” He started smiling. “The universe, space and time has a lifespan and can fall sick as well. What else is there to say about the Gods? Back when I was still active, I occasionally saw a few examples of spacetime collapsing. Hence I’m quite well informed on this topic. As long as we can find a collapse that is almost filled up and had yet to disappear, then that should pull the safety factor to the highest. I will set up a stable one-time Teleportation Portal.”

Garen looked at the surrounding area where it had started to distort.

“Perhaps we should observe a while more. It might be possible that the Universe will fix the spacetime collapse on its own.”

“Regardless if it will be fixed, the end result will be dire,” Ann said calmly. “Based on the scale of this progress, We’ll all perish if it fails to fix it. If the universe were to fix the issue successfully, it would require a huge amount of energy and material to fill in the hole. As the strongest existence which the universal law allows, we will be the first one to fill up these holes.”

Garen frowned and did not respond.

He did not have many things to yearn for in this world. However, he was not sure of Ann’s statement before proving his method was ineffective.

Ann did not say further as he seemed to have noticed his hesitation.

“I’ll find and set up a suitable collapse point in two months time. Bring your people along if you wish to leave.”

Woosh!

He and Golden-Winged Dragon Mother turned into shadows and vanished instantly.

Garen and Andrew were still in the area as they looked at the increasingly distorted area.

“Andrew, what are your thought on this?”

“…” Andrew was quiet. He did not know what to say. Unlike Garen, his shackle towards this world is not like that of Garen’s.

Garen sighed as he turned into a shadow figure and disappeared in the air.

**********

The Gods were still at war for the next few days. The huge Sphere of Dream was still shrouded with an endless amount of dream power, isolating all senses from the External World.

The world’s weather started turning strange as if the war had broken the laws too much to the point where the spacetime blight had started spreading chaotically.

Garen went back to the Blackhole District where he first arrived in this world.

He could see Heaven’s fragments during his flying journey. The Void was a complete silence as almost all beings of from all clans had gone to the area where the final battle was ensuing. It was the best place to bring themselves to a whole new level.

As Ann predicted, the black hole was still around. However, when Garen was about to teleport there, he found out that the spacetime on another side of the Void World was much more unstable.

When the spacetime is unstable, it might cause him to teleport to an unknown location deep in the universe.

Garen did not dare to enter recklessly, only observing from the External World for a few days before returning.

He could see black spheres that were caused by the spacetime collapse everywhere. These black spheres were like a black hole that could never be filled up as they kept swallowing all matters and energy around them.

Garen witnessed with his very own eyes, an Astral Space traveler who had just left the Astral Space coincidentally encountered a black sphere. He was sucked in alive and was stretched like a noodle, from a meter plus human to a thin line which spanned hundreds of meters long. Within half an hour, he was completely absorbed by the black sphere and nothing was left behind, including his soul.

The districts that were not being distorted became even more deserted and lifeless. The air became thinner and energy had become less to the point where a lot of living being’s spells had started to degenerate.

He rushed to seek for the Deception Demon Master who had avoided the battle as well.

She, too, noticed the strange phenomenon but she did not notice that it was the sign of the universe collapsing. They believed that it was the result of the war among the Gods. She had collaborated with the Star Region Demon Master to seize all of the territories.

Garen was determined to bring his people along to leave this place after observing for a few more days.

To him, it was just another transmigration regardless if it were true or not. This experience was completely common to a Demon Master and True Soul.

He then quickly gathered his most elite subordinates and close friends.

Garen went straight towards a safe district. Unlike the time he first discovered the collapse of spacetime, he was determined to leave this place.

**************

The sky was painted in dark yellow similar to the sunset. The sun was dimmed as if it had lost its light and the moon could be barely seen and one could only notice its contour.

The earth was dried up and shattered, there was not a single living being. There were only black spheres that were hundreds of meters wide on the surface which kept sucking all matters around it.

A group of people in a protective black-grey half-ball stood at the side of one of the black holes.

Garen brought along Rosta, Andrew, and his remaining subordinates as they stared at the gigantic black sphere in front of them together with Ann, Golden-Winged Dragon Mother, and Lady Vengeance.

“I’m sure this is the one.” Ann stared at the black sphere in front of him as he said earnestly. “We’ll need to enter it in a month to a month and a half. It will enter its unstable phase once this period has passed. I have no way to resist this thing’s distortion. When it comes to these things, all methods that are based on the laws will be ineffective and the only thing you can do is to rely on your physical strength to tank it.”

“Tank? I’m good at that.” Garen nodded to show his comprehension.

“Has everything been settled?” Ann looked at him.

“Of course.” Garen laughed. “I merely arrived at this world looking for a path because of the Mother Stream’s call. It’s only natural for me to leave at this point in time.”

“Good.” Ann went towards him and passed him a ring. It was a black metallic ring with a mosaic round amethyst on it. The side of the ring was covered with a cylindrical metal which had eight different weird symbols on it.

“This is the Ring of the Black Water Crystal. It is made from a mysterious material that can’t be destroyed even if the spacetime has collapsed. It has an effect where it would wake you up once you’ve lost the sense of time… If we’re lucky, we may still meet each other one day.”

“Wake me up?” Garen did not understand what he meant.

However, Ann had stopped explaining as he walked towards the black sphere together with Golden-Winged Dragon Mother and his subordinates. They did not show any sign of reluctance to stay in this world at all.

Garen sent them off, watching their bodies stretching into a noodle-like shape. Soon, they completely disappeared inside the black sphere.

“Are we really leaving?” Andrew spoke suddenly.

“Do you wish to stay?” Garen looked at him. “If so, you can stay behind. We may not be able to see each other forever again.”

Andrew fell into silence.

“Why are you staying back? I plan to see the upcoming world’s progress!” Annie, who was also a native to this world, said without a care in the world.

“Unfortunately, it’s hard for us to arrive at the same place with Lord Dragon King. The complication of transmigrating to other worlds is something you two can’t comprehend.” Nadia mocked since she was very experienced in this matter.

Garen waved his hand.

“You may stay back if you wish to. I won’t force anyone.”

After that, half of the people within the protection walked to the other side hesitantly. Their expressions were complicated as they did not wish to leave this familiar world.

Perhaps it would be better to say that they were hopeful towards the future of this collapsing world. After all, this was their native world where they were very familiar with.

“I respect your decision.” Garen nodded to show his understanding. He then looked at them one last time as everything that had happened in this world flashed across his eyes.

He who had reincarnated into a White Dragon, meeting Ann, entering Snow City, setting his foot in the Abyss. Although it was only a few decades, this world had left a very strong impression on him.

“Let’s go.” He waved his hand, turned around and walked into the black sphere.

This black sphere was in still its stable stage, hence its gravitational force was not that powerful. Garen, Rosta, Elfie, Nadia and Soaring Wing King started walking towards the black sphere.

None of them turned their head around and looked at the people who decided to stay back.

They walked until the black sphere covered their entire vision.

***************

Splash…

The faint sound of water could be heard.

Garen woke up slowly from his dream.

He found it hard to breathe from the water running about freely on his face.

Cough cough cough…

He coughed intensely for a few times as he got up from the floor.

He was inside a small and bright bathroom. The bathroom infrared heater light was switched on and the floor was drenched wet. The heaty steam evaporated from the hot bathing water had condensed into a layer of white mist on the mirror by the side.

The sound of water gushing was extremely jarring.

“I…” Garen was at a loss. His pupil shrunk, he reached out his hand and caressed his neck. He felt that his throat was swollen and it felt hot.

“Wasn’t I bathing?”

He walked towards the mirror and wiped off the layer of mist that was on the mirror.

The mirror reflected a young and yet pale face of a man. The sensation of familiarity and yet unfamiliarity swelled inside him.

“Is this… me?”

He closed his eyes as he recalled the moment when he entered the black sphere.

“Wasn’t I transmigrating to another world?”

However, what transpired in front of him was his starting point. The starting point of his transmigration when he was electrocuted. He was back on Earth.

“Perhaps, everything was just… a dream?”

He hesitantly reached out his hand as he looked at his palm. It was empty and there was not a single trace of the amethyst ring.

“Dream?” He suddenly felt that everything he had experienced were extremely unreal and everything was just a strange dream.

“Perhaps it really was just a dream…” He still had to go to work tomorrow. It was his first day earlier today for the job he had just found and he still had to leave a good impression towards his colleagues and superiors.

He then wiped off the water in his hair.

“Hmm… I need to clean up quickly before I catch a cold…”

He who had become Garen in his dream had experienced a series of journeys. The realism made him feel extremely surprised.

“Perhaps I should turn it into a book. Who knows, maybe it will become a bestseller. Hahaha!” He could not help but chuckle.

He swiftly cleaned the dirt off his body, wiped himself dry with a towel and got dressed.

Click.

Luo Jing switched off the bathroom’s light. As he opened the bathroom door and walked out, he did not notice a purple light flashed on his finger.

A quaint and exquisite sparkling amethyst ring appeared in the mirror that was opposite the door.

Luo Jing seemed to have noticed it. He raised his hand up but did not see anything.

“Why does it feel like there was something flashing just now?” He muttered.

The moment he put down his hand, the amethyst ring gradually appeared, giving off a mysterious and strange light.

An unclear image of a ferocious White Dragon appeared inside the mirror that was facing Luo Jing’s back. It was rotating slowly just like a Totem.

Everything was still very far from ending…